That's collector Corps concert for gonna move on to
If you're in a complex world
You have to manage by creating boundary conditions
Running experiments and responding to what happens
If you're in an audit system you can plan and design
And Chaos is something you can use
To get new insight but you want to invade
How to say engineering diagrams always assume order
The ecosystems.
And this is from Brian Arthur the first book complexity into economics
Rodger defining book corner
The evolution of technology
The trouble is that even scientists don't like complexity very much
Visit means you're dealing with systems Which have perpetual novelty
Get constant change
I sometimes use the metaphor as a children's party to illustrate this
Yeah you wouldn't manager children's party with key objectives targets mission goals project plans and milestones
Because everything would go wrong
You can see a more elaborate version of that on the web
That from that we get another couple of Simple Rules
If you want a very simple rule about when something is complex
If the evidence supports contradictory hypotheses
And you can't resolve the contradiction within the available time
Then it's complex
This is actually where we move into a massive new approach to conflict resolution
Because the whole point here is nobody is right or wrong
Because everything we do will change the system anyway
There's something which might have been right last time could be wrong this time
Anybody's managed to children's party
Yeah a football can catalyser good pattern the play
In the outdoors in summer
But you really don't want to bounce football in your living room in winter
Because the pattern the play will be radically different
The context of shifted
Yeah and damage will be massive
Yeah different things work well in different context
So basically
What we know stuff to do
Is we look at every coherent and coherence is a really important word in complexity
Camps and Philosophy of science
I can say that evolution is coherent to the fact even though we know it's wrong
Where's creationism is incoherent to the fact
It avoids that you were wrong therefore your hypothesis everything is a hypothesis
The issue is what's coherent the fact what incoherent to it
So we'll have to do is to agree your idea is coherent
I don't have to agree you're right in fact that can be pretty sure you're wrong but I agree
Your argument is coherent
At which point you get a small amount of resource
To run what's called the safety foil experiment
Been in the complex world you run small safe to fail experiments
Around every single coherent
Approach
And then you see what happens
And you stabilizer systems
You understand the complex system
By interacting with it
Not by analysing it
Or modelling it
I repeat that because it's key
You can't understand the Complex Adaptive system
Through modelling or analysis
You can only understand it by interaction
With real-time feedback loops
Over multiple agents
So you don't get cognitive bias
This is going like 101 science
And again that's going to change the way we design and work
The only thing I can say with absolute certain about a Complex Adaptive system
Is there ever I do will produce unintended consequences
If I show this in Australia everybody gets it straight away
And that's a cane toad
Introduced to reduce pest is now the dominant pest
Naturally that's important to realise it's alright
If you have a complex system and you intervene
The only thing I can guarantee you
Is it you'll have unintended consequences
That means you are ethically responsible for me
This is a big new thing on government
If you do a massive intervention and something happens you didn't expect
Oh sorry it's a complex system unexpected things were going to happen
It's your responsibility when they do
Which means you want to do small experiments in parallel much faster
So the bad unintended consequences you can destroy
And the good ones you can have T4
Is actually the unintended consequences will be the accepted moments
The discovery of novel ways of working
And that's actually quite important as what we all do
Save from net
We move onto the Canavan framework
And basically
At the camera framework by the way is not drawn like this
It's not drawn like this adding that later just to shut me up
Is actually John like this
No the whole body of theory behind this but basically you don't want a structured model
Canavan is a typology
And in full use the framework emerges from the data
The framework doesn't proceed the date
That's really important
If you give people a categorisation framework
Don't make things fit the framework
Even if they don't
It's the one you're working with sensemaking
You like the model boundaries to emerge from the data itself through Discovery process
And then you can use it and that's a really important distinction
The basically Canavan divided into 2
Spaces where
The relationship
Between cause and effect is obvious
Access example in civilised countries we drive on the left-hand side of the road
There's no particular reason for it I remember when Sweden was civilized until the 1960s
They had a national referendum where the people voted to stay civilised but the government have the sense to ignore the referendum
I'm talking about that example lot at the moment
Yeah and I moved over to driving on the right
Is that a universal I mean
Yeah you don't drive on the left
In the bin Sweden if a child runs on the road in the UK
If a child runs on the road in front of you drive anywhere to avoid them
So there is still exceptions evening rigidly constrained systems
Are there if you have a work Friday that was a bit different I remember
Something moved on the road in front of me in the middle of a Welsh Mountain Road and I stand the brakes on if you do
Discovered it was a sheet that the car was a write off and I phoned up car admin and they said next time kill the sheep pants
Still slightly worried about that one
Yes, had an overdose she put kids in till much later but never mind
I'm so basically and obviously mean we got it we can basically sense categorize respond
And we can apply best practice
Because there is one right way of doing things
Remember went to the complicated demand which is most engineering approaches set
That's actually where there is a relationship
Between cause and effect there is a right answer
Billy can only be discovered through analysis or by the deployment of the right type of expert
Get me can we do expertise as universal by the way
But at this point we can absolutely trust the expert decision
So basically at this point I sent
Amylose respond
And I apply good practice not best practice
Not going to argue at the moment
90% of systems architecture
90% of design sits in that domain
Busy assumption is there a right hand so we can discover it we can design for it that's it
I'll qualify that in a minute
We don't get if we over constrained system here
You get this catastrophic failure
Which is why chaos
Is a temporary space
And I get out of it by accident
Respond
The good news is
I get novelty
Is nothing like a crisis
To produce innovation
If I did a version is all about starvation pressure and perspective shift
If you look at it
Is when we can't use existing frameworks or existing ways of doing things
Then we get invented
Yeah that goes back to the cognitive entrainement patterns earlier
So basically you're saying that we get the complex to me
In the complex domain
What I actually do is
Probe
Sense respond
But I probe in parallel
Not in sync
That's really important
Because if I do one thing it will nearly always work
You know about the Hawthorne effect
Ok that that's
Cable manufacturers in New York State 1920 site of scientific management
Increase lighting levels and people became more productive that's good news
Pistes de with no publisher book
Cold Light
The secret to productivity
And have a certificate and training course based on how to switch on and off lights and change light bulbs
Then they had some pretension to be real scientist so they lowered the lighting level
People became more productive
What they actually found his people respond to novelty
Anything done which is new with attention will work the first time
It doesn't mean it will scale or repeat
Can you get somebody terrible management books that way one of my least favourite at the moment is lean startup if anybody's read that
Guy goes interviews people who know who's been successful as a whole body problems there because the way you remember things have your say
Successful
Is different from the way you remember them if you fail
And both of them are different from the way they actually happened for right so you can't just what people say
Another same time at the conference and did you study the companies who failed and he said no why would we do that
I said we did it when I was in IBM with Dorothy Leonard at Harvard Business School
We discovered all the companies have failed
Did exactly the same things as the companies who succeeded
Sjsu had a market
So a certain percentage would bound to succeed
And that's the trouble we got this very lightweight research throwing at simplistic recipes it's really dangerous
Here we go back to complexity I've tried Sainsbury's phone
And practice here will effectively be a merchant
I will always see a pattern
No important thing in the latest version I can have in call the liminal version
Looks like this
Secrets to liminal spaces
Illuminati is a really important concept in anthropology
And if you really want to understand humans go and do an answer
Topology course alright don't go on some cultural conversion course
Most anthropologists
No more about culture in the first year of studies
And cultural change consultants will now in their entire life Style
I basically liminality is a sense of transition if you put on a mask
Is a point where you start to become what the mask represents but there's a state of transition before you do it
Add a liminal concept in software design
Isobel actually not committing until you really have to
The longer you hold things in the state of transition the more options you've got
And actually in software development which is I know far better than architecture
This is actually where things like scrumpet
Because they are linear iterations based on a defined requirement with a degree of ambiguity
Therefore we're going to explore it
That's the trouble we eliminate ambiguity too early on
Big V12 restricted set to do linear experiments
In a mixed methods approach
What we start to do is to say and I use development that same as I know that better
Yeah there's nothing wrong with water for
Absolutely nothing wrong with Hardy structure processes you can use a togaf framework you can use rigid frameworks
You know exactly what you got to deliver you know the resource with an acceptable time friends why would you not take a waterfall approach
Am I working with telstra on this and telstra just gonna go
Therefore nobody got promoted unless they were Roger
So the waterfall guys rang one year sprint
So they could say they would really add you alright
That's what the thing is very very Common
Human beings a candy
You can't just the way the is language
I'm over here
One of the Big Things We Lost in architecture and I'll swear to concept
The time boxers
A2B got obsessed with two week time boxers
Certainly when I was involved in architect in last decision support systems
We will play around with three months
With a guaranteed delivery at the end of three months
But we very resource or weed very delivery
To meet the date
I actually gave us a lot of flexibility and definition phase and people looking like forgotten that stuff
Was it created the rights of the focus
Over here we're experimenting with radically different approaches and I'll just mention three of them
At this point
When is winter starting to look at an articulated needs
Before we even get
The design of any type
What we need to do is to surface the an articulated needs the things that people don't yet know they what they want
So when the ways we do that
Is we get people to interpret all of their technologies into Watts
Call obstruction metadata
We capture continuous narratives from users about day today for stations about their work
And then we merge the two databases together
Can we look at clusters
Abuser anecdotes with technology
Inside one of those come together
And that gives us novel ideas
He actually did this with Philips lighting
Yeah taking all of the technology capability customer stories
Putting the two together
Five clusters three of which became multi million dollar businesses
Is what you're doing is you're forcing accepted moments or insights
By moving up to a level of abstraction remember I started this on language
Ok if you don't know it we learn to paint
Before we learn to speak
Is a species
Art comes before language in human evolution
And it turns out that has major evolution invented you was an accident when it happened
Somebody sketch some pictures on a wall it can like work for the hunt
But then it started to really work
But if you move up a level of abstraction
You make connections in completely novel works
Engineers
Actually I musicians
Will tell you they have their best problem solving capability
When they play music
Art is critical to human invention
It's where the problem is Stem education is really scary
Because we reducing human beings down to the level of Aon
Hannah Stephanie doing this is about to start with University of California San Diego
And this is actually much more about infrastructure management
If you come to the university to do computing
You have to phone 0300 with somebody from the humanities and somebody from the pure sciences
When you're given pass by the University of Leeds 3 months
What we're doing is building across silent network of people who focus on a task
So that we can bring things together in novel unexpected ways
And a lot of this is about creating an architecture for Discovery
Raven trading architectures deliver
What people have asked for
Did you get the discovery architecture right
The recipe comes a lot easier
Because you got actually more structure in terms of the way you work
I could go on and that but there's a lot more material that was I can move onto
Keeping I want to finish office it's question and modelling
Are you a fine people in complexity Theory
This is what I call the computational complexity guys
My field is cool down through complexity
And the study of complexity in human system
The computational guys think everything is like blocking
Anyway but it's block around in sky schoolboys algorithm
It's follow the next bird max speed avoid collision
At that also works by the way if you want
To drive south of Naples in Italy
It's a much more effective heuristic than following the rules alright if you max speed avoid collision
Yeah and follow the next car you actually have a stressful driving experience even in Sorrento if you assume they follow the rules
Oh forget it alright
That's not the way it works
It will be in that human beings on hands
Because we haven't got see how you can predict
The entire complexity of the termites nest
Visit genetically encoded rules responding consistently to phone them stimulation
The human beings can see things through metaphors
We see things for abstraction
We can change identity overnight when I'm with my children I'm a completely different person than on stage
We don't have single agency we don't have single rules with complex pattern based creatures
So basically human beings on time
And that means you got a real problem with modelling
I gave the keynote of the European complexity conference all academics this Edward I speak about why you can't model of Complex Adaptive
I said no problem nobody told me the entire audience will be academics who built models
Yeah that would like Daniel going into the lines then that was when I met girl man he was the other here
And you can't challenge get on my knees when the world's most famous physicist
He backed me up and said you can't model the human system
The only valid model of human system is a system itself
A map to some extent is where we're starting to go but it's also part of the general concern
About an increase of artificial turf
Official intelligence
This is actually real problems anybody hasn't ready in M Banks books surface detail
I am back is a brilliant science fiction writer tragically died of cancer
Are you then propose to his long-term girlfriend by asking her if she would do the honour of becoming his widow
Is that sort of sense of humour alright
Read that and be terrified I've just been involved in a big think tank in California
General Hughes actor is actually as second most
Highest existential threat
The humanity after nuclear war
And ecological
Change is actually number for
When the reasons is with reducing human beings to information retrieval and process
Nai is better at that
And we won't go onto 101 machines and things like that
We need to be very careful about that because a human being is more than this
And then of course we get all the culture nonsense
Everybody wants to engineer if in doubt blame culture
If your pet project didn't work it was their fault
Because they have the wrong culture or the wrong mindset and this is
Appalling science
There is no such thing as a mindset
Is a complex set of interactions overtimes in a series of
The tropes
But it's not an individual mindset
You get people who will gather people stories that's good news we gather people stories
But we let
People interpret than themselves
We don't interpret them or let computers interpret them
Because that restricts us to text
And by the way you can write down
10% of what you know
Anything which is processing text
Is again dealing with a very very limited set
There's a power issue here as well
Who interprets people's narrative is there
This is from work with just doing with the BBC
Weather presenting cartoons
Employees are choosing cartoons which represent their culture
Interpreting those on the high abstraction metadata
I'm from that with an actually drawing a series of maps
How many reasons does we don't want to fall into one of these traps
Yep mansplaining postcolonialism
All that lovely one about the expert must be right
Ok
I'm giving you three illustration as there
If you really want to understand the human system
You got a hand over the power of interpretation
To the people themselves
Does it mean you don't have a room for experts
We got to distribute the property function you can't tell that centrally
Save from net
That allows us to do some very interest
This example is a dispositional map
And this is actually where we are starting to go with systems architecture
Bolsover things like kanban
So if you look at categories and kanban
Ok the key Concepts and kanban is working progress
Yeah not the representation of those who hear the advocaat she would think it was all about Post-it notes moving between columns
Key Concepts is working progress
In an audit system work in progress is a series of discrete job unit
The kanban Works
In a complex system is a series of unrealised
Potentialities
So the representation has to change
This is actually a landscape drawing from mass observation self interpretation of the point of origin
Anything actually cultural change map so if I actually want to change culture on this one
If my desires Stacey's appear
You can see I've got some things up there sexy
What's a tick in the box
This is very very negative
To move them up there is a Step Too Far
What I do instead is I look at this
And I say what can I do tomorrow
To create more like these
If you would like those
What I'm doing this is a key principle of complex design
Is an shift in the system to an adjacent possible
And once I get enough stability at that point
I can use more conventional approaches
This is what I'm talking about about architect into under the discovery
Before you architect for delivery
Did you actually start with the start with delivery
You miss the discovery phase
Are you going to miss opportunities as well as threats
That's actually from a hospital
Autolyse answer key Concepts call fractal engagement
So the same data can produce frameworks at the level of responsibility of every individual
And again I haven't got time to go into this I'll go to this in the strategy session
Fractal engagement is the way we actually achieve change
People don't make decisions about what other people should do
They make decisions about what they can do tomorrow within their own sphere of competence
Then the system as a whole torrent extra multiple actions
That's a big concept by just hinting at it now
And I thought we call fractal change
EBay
It's all about multiple perspectives
This is actually from again this is work on the whole variety.
This is Peace and Conflict resolution
What we doing here is present in an infographic and when are doing this in system design Discovery architecture
Representing infographics about where we think we should be
We're getting every employee to interpret that
Enjoying the max of the interpretation before anybody talks to anybody else
In that space is actually from Columbia this is
Yeah big one
You can see that blue and green see the same data in such radically different ways
Sitting down to talk to each other is a waste of time
The only thing they both agree on his they hate the red guys
Get the strategy here
Is there actually make these more extreme
Will it be getting new consensus in the middle
The other reason we do this is I want to find outliers
Agama talk about Discovery architecture
I want to see groups of people were seeing the world differently from everybody else
Because those are the things the 17%
Who seen the Cancer nodule
Rob and people were going with orthodoxy so again that's the concept of Discovery architecture
RAM delivery architect
And the final slide finish off on this How You scale a complex system
Again this is a big field but the one thing you don't do is you never scale the complex adaptor
The system
By aggregation or imitation
You don't take everything and aggregated up into some massive diagram
And you don't say that worked will do more of it
What do you actually doing to decompose things and there's a whole body working on this by the way an object orientation
Remember to going back to at the moment
You decompose things to the lowest coherent object
You define protocols for the interactions be
Between the objects
Annual animal patterns to emergency stimulator system
So you staying but scale by decomposition and recombination
Not by aggregation
And not bite imitation
Have a challenge for design the Challenge for architecture
Is the move much further back in the cycle
Video with an articulated knees
To discover on an objective basis
Novel possibilities unexpected consequences
Andy bell systems with the responsive capability
To exploit opportunities as they present themselves
Before they're fully now
In order to do that we need to have a sound understanding of the science
Behind human cognition
And the science behind system
Is under conditions of extreme uncertainty
Falling back for the constraints of natural science gives us security
Falling back to empirical past memories of what work before
Makes it very very random
Thank you very much for your time