好，还有什么你想改进的吗？
是的
你看出来还有不爽的地方吗？
是的。这里全是过程代码，一个方法，一屏幕高
做这个，做那个，做这个等等
就是一些脚本
是的。这里"get the train"就没有用了
所以，我们删掉它
好，现在好多了
现在，我们的问题是，
我们共享了"train"，通常这是要返回领域对象，而不是JSON数据
我们看到我们这里有个物理代理
来扩展WebAPI，来组成一个
适配器，通过适配器模式
我们还会继续来着这段代码，所以不用担心你不知道。对比返回
JSON字符串。
我们让它返回Train对象。好的。
这样我们就可以在函数内处理JSON了
这样可以更面向领域，不会和技术细节
纠缠在一起。你觉着呢？同意。你觉着还好？
所以，我发现这个文件
有一个Train的构造函数
Train。好的。我们看到很多反序列化JSON的东西。
这个文件就是这样
这个不要选中吗？
删掉。好的。
这个也没有用到
我们也删除它
这个也变灰了
或者你可以把它分拆到几个文件中.. 嗯，删掉它。
现在，我们在
Train
这个类中
是的。Train没有太多的行为，除了
解析
JSON
神奇的Resharper
好
我们使用Lambda。好的。好。
我要移动这个了。这里有很多..属性...字段...好。
我们有一个构造函数。全是技术细节了。
你还有什么建议吗？
如果我来喝点水
[观众问题]
这里有个更好的地方来解析JSON
Train是领域模型的一部分，所以，我们不应该在这里做这件事。
好吧，让我们来修改。好，我来创建
一个小[方法]来封装我要移动的代码
我们会做很多次的这种操作。抽取，移动。抽取函数，移动到合适的位置。
我们会在会议中多次使用到。好吧，让我们来做第一次。
我想选中我要的所有代码
来抽取，移动
这个可以吗？
再多一点？好的，这个，好的。
代码太长了
好的，我们抽取了函数，但是它现在依然是实体函数。好的。
这个是
Train topology
因为在解析JSON
所以，
对Train的很多属性做了赋值
不错的方法
这个吗？
所以，抽取函数的人
可以把它
移动到新的位置
一个好的查看依赖的方法。因为我想移动它
但是我不想增加依赖
我知道我想隔离
所以
我使用了静态函数
现在出现了几个下划线
几个下划线
这里，这里，因为它们是静态的
现在我们要修改第二个测试，来看看，是否静态... 出现了错误
好的，来看看如何切断这些
好的，联系。
Results
Yeah mate motion answers
Send an apology as an argument
Yeah that's a good idea but there is something I can do also it's so far
If a is not New Zealand then I increment the results it
Instead of
Changing that value of cos of sitcom.
But we may be able to
Causes of using the potty
And everytime I call the property new property is doing the computer desk so many one way of doing it
Something
Instead of
Lezyne v11 changing the value it will be something like
Set
Return on debt collection of sets so that as well not not at work on
Don't want
Not Nero auntie
Something like that
Result sorry sir cannot thank you for the match
Well for the last rooms
Isomorphic artificial Wales
Drilling waste collection Andrews email address
It so that's not this not
So here when I was writing something like I think the list of the seats and I can't everything's well that Lundy is very
Ring all's well
I don't have a booking at all times his father
So now you can get
Rid of that
Familiar
And this one
Maybe I can
Next
As you propose something similar
ASOS a list
What's an intro song that's made into a fashion I shouldn't because I
Statin function
So
I was still the oceans furniture
I like you
List
Antalya
I received a look-a-like about yesterday now
I return
Sorry, that message into a pension
So that's where we call it we get the results
Direction
So since we added strength ability
University because we have to move it
What's the population
What is the train is because it's because it's running yeah it's a matter of
Ok maybe just trying to message you make it
Perfect
Function so we can move it
Granny off internet
Let's put it it will get back to you I haven't eaten
Well it has been called
Yes
Here we have the train
So it may be interesting instead of having no didn't have energy to get the train to return on train
For men you can put that
Study functioning to the tenderness of his
So let's move
So you must be signed into the train
Weather.co.uk
So far we still have a crown dependency in the
In the train class between infinity Motorcycle
So you make it to open each user
Yes and
The goal is to change the Swan
Madrid train and get train at Everton this year show
2010 original itasca strings attached before it sank
Will requesting a weather API so it's a good offer
I should have died complexity matter
Ok what tree restaurants in Sweden train
Maria Bello
For the business not have to take the train or within subject
Ok so I'm trying to transform the topology
The trend on deserts of the British weather
So we call it that
Identification
But
Currently the train a dog
Received
Citizens Advice
Change that herself still have that lets accepting a list of s*** yeah so it was not the train we will accept it
Mushroom much more easy to
Cliff Richard to play with and remove this phone
So we don't have any kind of references from the train to when you can off
Trend of Us army soldier
So that's
So
No I can
Texas want to get train now is retiring at rentals
So you don't need that anymore
I don't know what is fun
In here
We have some ok but we ask the train we get
I compiled because maybe I ask Reading
Even if it doesn't add components to Green
Brewers compile yes this is we do not test vision Express Enfield
Worcestershire train from Avengers unforgiven topology and this is where we have to do the same way
Have to adjust
The prettiest girl
The prospecting tool
The song on YouTube please YouTube the new one
So
Should
While I'm singing
Ok
Does a foil I don't return back to
Lips
Rebecca was ok
So thank you for all your technical
That we are back of the train and we get put into a politician
Mrs bottles in hospital
So I'm much better
How much mortgage off tomorrow is that good that there's another thing that bother me
Find Stones Let's see the train ok you can you improve the situation but
Ok this is a train
What is it
To a better class result in each other videos
Nottingham Christmas to me and I'm not aware of maybe photo calendar to send once
Instead of object instead of a teenager object or child object
Yes to take responsibilities somehow
Nhgs
Torrentz2
Wrestlers who that's also we have a concept of Sin
Well then I'm trying to talk to you who's the name for that
Actually there is a name for that
Canada men
Travelodge Ilford
Anna Magdalena company and England
So
We are
Lacking
All the percentage of The Dimension of God when we have we have kind of any mixture pin data class
All of the angels in Easy
That's rhythm a Third Kind of collection 6 year
Harry Potter July doing all the magic
What I suggest
Surely it's too
Production Gear Jordan to put it in the population in Tritton Leicester or child objects
You can show something about MOT checker
Roman numerals
Athlone
YouTube
Just since we were doing a lot and it seems really what will we do we have a place
Has be classed as a Wimpy Kid furniture offers on the sofa instance and the Crosby's Alexa.
So what'll we do a lot it's to extract credit
Please type the behavior
Into a method so then you will have a method into the same type
And then we will move it into the population in the train France
At the end of the day would have more actually rating
New Balance
Let me switch back to the planet
Lottery
We will do that
Ok
This train reserve seats personal analysis the first Middle School attendance should not
Maximum capacity of the train
I suggested recycle message here
But maybe does not it does not exceed does not exceed
Overall
Friends episode in concert
Are you ok
Will that work
Depression
Diversity
I will make us a non static method and primaquine to be able to move it
Isn't it
So here I strike that two minutes with that method
Where should I
Move it
Going to
The training and everything
If I said
6 tomorrow
Azure Python passing arguments to an instance of an argument so you can easily move that day
Trainer has a train does not exceed over altering capacity
If I want to replace number of seats
Ok
Actually what we have here is available seats
Real building list of available seats at School of Massage Windsor
Final elements
Wynsors
Filezilla
Nonsense
Turn on statistics on solar movies
So here
If the train does not exceed if I request does not exceed the maximum capacity
Where to find sum of elements
Actually
They said that we may introduce here instead of that
When you finish
NBA profit
Just pretend
Allocation
A specification
Yes
Yeah except of course at the end of the day we will need to try 1800 Portsmouth
Before that's the don't expect was talking a lot about whether I should attend
Set a rear bottom cassette for fine
So I think it's so sweet
Instead of just dealing with available seats a list of Sith
There's a vendor distance of possession from that
But
Yes I sent you something
Original iPhone we are improving the colour blue are at something to to show you
Yeah maybe
Some people know in Japan
It's a tool to check the dependencies that it exists the architect for Java
Of C++
Navigational in your code and the Rising Sun
Warning forever and we were working with you thanks Mike I don't have anybody anyway
Ask him to introduce somewhere to check that turns photos into Cambridge
Author of the name Enterprise it's not a release and we tried to imagine imagine
Can you have a team you have a legacy card and you know the vocabulary of the next
Red Aurora
Scorpio card should rely on your ability language and we see we have some problem and
As you can see we have the list of program and the world not matching correctly
Letters of a gamma camera
We have to
Enter a list of words that are part of Oldham in Lancashire
Reclamation fruitfield
Manual and automatic
What is cheering alpha I think it would be an interesting way to make some
Forgot to issue a kind of smell about that
So Ryan's what was the results for the 3
Yeah I don't want to
Ok so let's get back to to the business we have a solicitor
Available seats
I think that we change that
Send signature on that by introducing the concept of inheritance
For here instead of returning a list of sets
Let's make a trip return reservation
Adult
I'm sorry I'm going to type all Heroes elation at them thank you
Ok
Ok the time doesn't exist so yes I'm aware of that maybe I will ring I need to answer that
Shiraz UK
Say sorry as I was July 10th where is it
Sorry
Yesterday night and I don't I don't think so let's Create it and enter
Three types of violation adult ok
Share
Since
The method is a function is expecting to it'll music and possession all I have to do
Is to install search here
Asian
Little and newer version attempts
Ok
Providing you
The list of sheets I just found
All I have to do is to create the conflict or accepting a list of Sith
Well that's what I said I don't ok
And that's it
Meditation intense I need to
I will need to drop in the sticks
So let me
Set of creating a few let me Create
Let's be real and that
Apprenticeships
National identity history
Maybe to produce a report that said because I will need
Rock with her the tips of that animation of dogs
Ok
So we just thinking to reservation account
Each other property assets
And that it's pretty much
So that the final elements it's now the name is
BBC weather
Any better yet
Fernando massages beautiful passionate earned it
Find a venomous it was in the train and return result shadow temple that
It's ok for everyone
So the card is not complaining anymore because I used to work with a list of seats
So what I need is to rename available to buy in Ashington
And then
Two
Adding directions to the city
Dental work with the list of numbers
Convert 3
Location
S12
Look suits
The squirrel in love
Rob Delaney
Fortran compiler Project
Ok it's compiling still win
For hear what I just did is to
Traits of a cancer directly come from the domain of havisham attempt and I
Replace a simple instruction by a mate
What can I do here I have a debit card
Yeah it's like saying
Doddle
The new film with talking a lot about that song
Let's create a method for that
A cut
Animals in
Fulfilled most complicated formula to find out in writing in English
Birthing kits
It's ok for that
So we asked
What is an isotope are you fulfilled so first X Factor
Cylinder under to gas and then to move it
I'm sorry
Today's weather
So I ate a cartoon of you and I put it into the politician which is awesome
The little something bother me because you passed twice
Citroen request agilitas
You better and if I can provide the 6th question Colts once when we construct
So that we don't need anymore to ask to provide it's every time we want to to check if it's Gucci wallet
Lisburn Auto Care degree go to implementation
Sequestered colds
I will provide it into the closet organisation attempts
Ok
Sorry I think I'm
I need a huge mistake
Up sorry
Ok
So I change the photo on the reservation account
Alton Tower, Cheltenham Hospital yes please sir
Regards
Italy coast to coast Newark what I can do is simply too cheaper
Arena mission meaning it's not finish it will be accessible through here
Outside world
388 in
No I had it
What I can do is to lay right on that
Instead of
The one that is provided
As arguments in the instruction
4 year
I replace it
The bomber dealt with in January I can get cigarettes
Define meta
Since I'm in the shop I can post your mates into property
Xbox One buddy
Ok
This one's that
No I think it's ok ok
So here getting back to the Institute
You said you see
I want to reserve massage I asked that has happened to me the other night then to the train
Albania on the train
Roulette
I just extract
The Mistletoe let's move it into the train
So now I can ask the train please try and give me your attention music
Number 68
Get off its food
Then I can continue
I can't continue to ASDA booking office and also looking at her she is not part of the domain you said always looking
So let's
Stickers of the mend Longridge
The Chase
And then what we do is to iterate or every citizen resolution attempt to assign materials
Maybe we can
Attack the messenger
And put it into the position and then directly which will be a sign
Booking reference
Which one video
Which was the
The devil's a dimension is that time of the minute we are signing with initials
Designer shirts ok
I tried to my son what will be the next
Stephanie
To move ya love to know that I don't
Ok
So we are seeing meteor showers 2010
If we look at the implementation just too funny to fail all we take that looking at house and sign it
To everyone of the seats
Of the multinationals
I was thinking the same thing as you and the Medics was really saying it
We build
The process is to build a reservation agent
And at the end of the day to transform it into hibernation
So yes but I wasn't saying that
Idea
Regression
Actually we thought it's like a technical team builder
Used to do it to use it in technical lead for the next concert
So we have a train station see what it may be sent to more and you haven't
Who is happy fashion within this application of the Year sequel
Yeah it's just everywhere let's see if it's irrelevant you ok
Rabbit
Decoration of the general manager
Then we used to set it into the hospital so intricate Benidorm
Then we clear it interesting
Weekly rates and an unconscious changing the glow in the stretching mediatek Street II
Average average of two figures
Total to clear the cache I don't know what to debit
Ok I hope it's worth
And then we said
The book
English film Olsen the trainer Gok into into the dash
And then that's it
Is that so
Attach where we only save stuff
But think about the hour
Ivana
Windjammer correctly
It's a mistake
As we said before we completely older
Khomeini
So
Autocar venues self service
And why we cash
HR department waiting staff
It's a mistake
You can change it and say yes it says it's going to stupid
Think I would say
Miss Katrina Isabella switch up
I remove it here
Animals that swim of that sand
Hi
Nationbuilder
This is a discussion we we we may have with the National
Thisisnottingham
Recording before win because it's not the first time we run the session.
Yes you're over that this is something that we discussed
Technical details with saying that
Retained amores
Stuff that we get at that time is it correct
According to you
So yeah
So ok we
Directors lodge massage
We get a train then we asked to train
Alex
Overheard in the other twin capacity 3 ask princess yet
Adjustable bookcase remember that I should I dance then we check if it's fulfill that
Nicolas Marin
Outdoor Pursuits
The house in the 24th fences
Wrist tattoo next to the Limit
Then we Oscar booking assholes
Then we assign the booking office and then we booked the seats
And then we return the there isn't
I don't know phone you but now the Mercedes one screen hi
We are addressing a little bit more the concept of the domain and we
After the spreading the news goes into the popular location the Twin Towers Malaysia
The
The seats also
The resolution attempt also
Yes I return money
No what would you suggest because it's important to be time boxed
Haha because I mean you can improve god a lot
What time we have an objective
Celebrity brewers
How to fix a bag
Concept
Return Tesco
Yep absolutely no idea what you're saying that in you what weekend is to get rid of that synergies on here
Any set to return to Amazon
And then return
Itasca because I was on here so that December 3rd is purely Dublin
No strangers on inside a simply recharging the oven in stock
Will do that