Maybe we can have a
Tiny
Punto abarth Aggregates
Daughter just a tiny fight about aggregates aggregates a collection of objects without wanted to know why you tired
AstraZeneca Central Hall
Can you see somebody getting here
Train
Is Gorton aggregate
Why is that
And does not seem to know because aggregates in science
When do the schools need to 22222
Tamiya
Ed Sheeran the only running value for harvesting data training
The I lost I do I must not exceed 70% of the 20% meat
This is a museum Dundee
Coach Aggregates s202
When we discussed with the ministry after you told her that you wanted to have some new rules ready to the coach
So that's a good enough money for funeral so I must not be here
The giving diversity is going to change maternity
Leggetts voice maybe it's getting better
Something interesting
Train coaches and seatbelt devalue types here
As we discussed earlier
If you think about the way we interact with external backend
You're the kind of snapshots
Venice, moment of time
In we will rock on that Snapchat song
With a wall to keep it in cash we just want to rock with all those Aggregates
Francis
So24 that we can make it all when you type so I shouldn't International
That's what we did
So that means that some aggregates may be completely when you type so so
The train here
It's most of the cases leggings with each other
Do it was 11 days where we could have
Just exception
If you have a number you're just going to be interested because
Maternity orangutan letter in the longest run without me do that
Source of how we improved somehow the web ticket manager
And I had a little brother
Kristina Si
Fallout 4 interactive car there is a lot of finger sister now
I think we have gone off
Improve the little bit 61 screen hi it's using the world's of the domain was in the car
Don't recall lyrics Justin
Rifftrax and some of the other new we put it into the popular locations
But there is still something
Weather
Tomorrow started
The swap
This is that we have some Jesus
Booking design into the
The main method
Respiratory telescope strings is also ageism
What we would like to do here is to get rid of that designs train stuff
Attributed by your husband
That's all that's ok that my son will return a reservation
And then
On the positive side
We will transform the liberation into a diesel
Russian
If you have another term for wanting something that is on top of suggest
I will talk a little bit about that I'm sorry I will work on the card
Gaza
You don't seem that it will explain when we get back to the code
So who is the weather for today
Ok good
What is it going to hospital is it secure pattern made by Alistair Cockburn
I called him another day
And it has many benefits
Patel Natasha teacher 11
If an Oyster on breast change it was the first
Eyedea freestyle S2
Plug and unplug
External dependencies plugin and play store
Just talking about the weather system
Ableton tuner plug with many different standards as important many different
Ronaldo sock boots
Broadcast news to broadcast to TV to radio to whatever
So it was Israel and us to have a
Kenneth clean code inside and
Every changes in terms of 400 or way to interact with the system
Premier tournaments 2017 he knew you play your pregnant and you went back up again and that's it
Sorry it's come with us was introduced by that I didn't mind
That's when we think about it babe
I notice that we want to Foster on the domain to make some Cudmore
Volume dealers value inside
Power products
Doing good, technical stuff
I don't know for you but
Very long time I thought it was not even possible to popular speed between domain music and and technical one week
We tried many times.
Refers to lots and in since I discovered that that Patel
It's really nice way to inform that
I also do you want Foster 72 because everything is a pluggable which unlocked
Toaster input output of the systems
This week's inside in
So what you doing for Christmas morning how to put it on the mountain
How does it work
It was considering the world into
Different area
There is a inside and there is no type
Sybarite
No
So the lovely girls know something to area
The insiders of the main it showed unemployed like it I like the train station attendant
The stuff like that
Is it possible to code is at
The outside of show off your system
So this is where you will find your favourite HTTP start
No that his rivals your message oriented middleware every solution what it is it is in cottage cheese
And what we want is to Foster and to improve the Dominican
So we have
How do you know National Insurance sometimes about putting some bum boils around your bum and blood
N
Defining some entry points
29 to 20 centimetres
Funny clip
The Apostle shop good idea sign
Nice community actually because I don't know for you better when you start your stereos Liverpool
You need to improve your skin you need to discover new sink
Need to meet new lot of mistakes
Newton Village Hall Kinross unit
Ul.to to realise at one point that there are some serious stuff like influence you all time rock stuff like that
But before you focus on the on the Dunham really
Experian Boston for some new jungle ability to be able to
To play in the care of playground
I'm ok with that
As much as it does not geopandas
The biggest value in the project and in that case I'm happy with that because there is kind of
Location where you can play It's a playground South Hospital
Try new technology new stuff that are members of Japan is England
I really like you letter is a pattern
So how do you drop because they are ok but I need to
Dementia
To do so in terms of dependencies all dependencies afterwards inside
Leeds away restaurants
But of course I do we could not be aware that alright
Any homework
Avengers on stuff if you like that's all the domain is completely
Independent from any kind of technology even g-strings
So to do so tomorrow to S2
Wolf from the Inside to the outside to ask
New sing to talk with external web apis and do some stuff
We will rely on personalities
Lucifer
We actually use the dependency inversion principle
For that funding so we can go outside and do some stuff
How do you stop a building and recently his test results remember the name and that was
Suggesting the name of
Configurable dependencies
Weather is the worst thing is impossible possible I don't really like because this is like you
Negative way of formulating Sainsbury's
You used to do that
Do the other way round do the inverse
Sorry was trying to find them much more fluent intention way of saying that
So they lead us to a configurable dependencies
So you plug in and plug in your dependencies
Randy alderman
So if we get back to where we Ascend we have posted another talk to enter
I believe the video man
The box
Dirhams to the demand and there are some interfaces like a lollipop here
So here I've got sizes of Suits which is the entry point from the
From the clipper system
So I asked
Phone adaptor hdcp 2.2 asp.net call back
I must call an interface which is a but I forgot it
Naturism you remind me something
I got a reservation in that I have done will
Does irritation between resurrection and regional nationalism
So it's it would be the proper location to do so
Will I need to for my middle school when I need some extra data from EE starting if I have not provided
Maya everything I need from the beginning
There are many ways to do that but
Liberalism say I need to ask you one of the external essence of dependency
You know this via web API we called during the process
We need to accept we need to add something to the outside safe to do so
We asked some parts on Sunday closing time
There is a I book seats
The phrase there is a hypervisor time topology interface
EasyJet booking a source interface
Domain interface the Baskervilles to the domain
Reason why the lollipop in Zulu
But the Adidas is what spirit is in hospital
From anything you wanna do something that's Maps between The Fosters chocolate to the doorman one
Invasion Airsoft
Is the death of all of you
Where is the Latin word for dinner in a minute
So put another girl to go into god
Is it right
Ok but when we try to implement it the first time
Stunt of questions that
Rosin
How many ways to to to do so so will show you one
We have to initialise we are twin it to insulate
20 seater
When you had to build you up the Builder stuff
So I'd like to get a bit of forward to the children with their talk to him to send that to my mate
I tried to explain to you
Prostitutes will talk to you about the composition without your application you know
The place on the opportunity where you get all your dependencies
And then follow a player leave the system is able to work continues his way
So we're talking about.
OCI application
Sort three steps first step is to associate
I need to blow out adaptor
Was there a bus to go to ask to the attention back in please
Give me a topology please.
We are presented to candidates only say that I'm working at all services. I like cheese
To go outside in to ask stuff
Sofa
Purpose tour to St Austin's
Then second Step is
Another skin and wrap them with you if I could I drop them with the
Cinnamon
Medina swimming stuff so it's a way to get manager
So they went to get manager will receive we discuss with dodgy box
Interface to interact
Physics jet A1
And then
Will Associates
We're up the zygote
Whizzer a new adaptor which means Indian actor to be used in a document array into
Redirect miso system
Sweetie I need to go I need to enter data it's easier to communicate with your application
But what we do that or we have to keep your head from an application that picture
On the asp.net web API testing
All I have to keep in mind we're busy
Entrypoint editor
Took over the rest of the Year exactly one and and and adaptors
Its own implementation details what's a builder place
What I have to tip
For my web API pass between is that adaptor what is the entry point for my for my system
Ok
WD-40
The Three Steps looking at the diagram
Weight loss surgery. We need to go out
Sort of view for the three daggers
Then we wrap them with things are going well for Domino's extenze
And then we're up that's the main reason
It's like a Russian don't you know
I need to go out zigzagoon I need to go in
And at the end of the day only keeping your hands say I need to go in
This isn't the only thing that you need to interact with her
The system application test BT
Total entertainment will be only that other girl that you will
Inject into your call back service political 4 hours and stuff like that
Ok
Shut your dumb question
Will guided tour
Hope you will have some questions
Hello
Just to have a logo on the new version
You cannot test now we have a reservation
And the modification has been
Toubkal
Confirm because after this time
I know
Is there is no exception
And I can
Rittal
The resolution
Does the medication on the tester
Is there here with me returning reservation
N
I already cried the beginning of adaptor output adaptor
Wizard app reservation
This disk this function will be
Call
Vitamasque instrument used to move the technical issues in relation to the place exactly
Ok
What is the distance to for me to
Refusing rats first acceptance test
What I will have to do into Maya
Buttercup my Corporation Road ok
So first one is to step 1
List all instances I want to go out adaptor so here
Candida service
Princess we can even recording we know me to come dancing senator
Cabana service
Ze707 it's a proxy to
I'm sending for
That
Adaptor
Ok
Step one instance of the dependencies I need to go to the outside world
Then what I need is to associate
Zigzag
So the attack on here is a web ticket manager
So let's
College
Is it going to here for
Unusual business
Name so please don't tell Eric
Trinidad Express
Toffee TV
Weather for ME2 397 hair
And then instead of going directly the lagoon
All I said before is the application would have to interact with my biometrics
IPhone adaptor so let's introduce it
Supreme
Interested I want to go in adaptor so here
I can do is to what how can we then use it
Providing what should I provide
That sounds like Russian dolls
Those two fasts where providing two things are going here and eggs are going to provide into theatres in UK
Ok so I tried to go to talk because it's so far you just had men aesthetic
From chance ok
Maybe you have to make an attraction and not to inject the web
Ticket manager
Yes actually yes you're right we talked about boxing at the Fox I like interfaces
So what I can do
Maybe is on the web ticket manager here
This information can write and we will change after so let's create an interface for that
Adana CI
Arizer solo
No sorry
I
I used to work in the on the market so we tried to pick a team order to resolve action 600
Weather AccuWeather
Yes but never sent you one
I was asleep I tried to text using Google IP address
Yeah so I asked I had already told on that device
This is a box
This is a box in order to Enter the Dragon
So I'm getting back to the garden yet
Share
What I will provide to the external adaptor it will be the exam but as
Hobbs
Go to politician as a child of 6
I resisted.
Ok
Let me type it into a private folder here I will need it
So I started off as a fashion editor
Ok
Soap
Chillstep
Glyphosate 1127 for that
Biannual need to replace the direct call to zigzagoon
My something going through the adaptor you know
So just to make it compile I will go to the coffee off to work now
Machine the place where I will use that exact same adaptor
Find acoperire
I will need to
My entry point with me together with an Acer Liquid Z2
So I will get to this emotion because it's you
Lyrics to the ladder and the other will get back
Newsagent
Relating to the ocean
So do you so I think that I shall issue is not in the Pop-up Play off
I won't be able to elicit message from the from the desk so I think that maybe
Pencil Project
As long as so I was just created and directories here
Electrical conduit aluminum
Alright in consulate of hop
So that meeting
Stock to splits
Info
How to join party
We are able to speak properly every type into the population
Agitating to merchandise for
Be sure that every 5 much to type so looking at us
What is a schooner
What's the weather
Looking at someone's eyes
It's about men only the name will be different that
Porsche
Romania
Booking a civil service
Dementia
Sunderland
I suggested
Support
To Vauxhall
Domain name
Itrain data service
Alison Edwards into the mains ok
Shane Duffy
Animation
Damental rights
Same
Resolution of video
Something
Animation video also
I said it's much more something to implement a new digital age in there is no added value more than
Sips
The MegaMind
I'm cannot attend because you are more than ins on the prostitute machine undertakings all my projects
So far for 16 and 4
Supervision and after
Ella dearest Battleday
Stratagem
Somerton Festival 2015
Lemon for acne
If anything changes the name
Trailer
Is it the man
Top of the Pops
And what do we have candida summer's
Astrocenter
And went to get manager
Exercising
Read so Sally Skinner's son to St Peter shoulder to get
Lottery
You know it's ok so let's put into the
Best ticketing Limited
Oops sorry I don't know what I'm doing it into the middle before we completely clean the house
And put it into the living
I want some space here for this for the project
So that anyone with me
The puppet
Booty
So what I was saying is I will from the
Sugar
What are system issues
Getting back to the test
Ok
I said that I would like to introduce a way to interact with yellow eyeshadow
So let's
Offensive
It's a Boston jewellery made on M25
New is emotionally present
I don't know if you remove it
I don't know I didn't know
Thanks will also
Revolutionary questions you're here afternoon
Is it on the map Project
Muscle food
Tamilrockers
Next National Lottery draw
Ok
For now I will be able to see what it comes with it
Otherwise it will be baptism with API which has more
Restaurants Southall
So I wish you I will set a new reservation request need to know
This is expedited come up with us to install said that for me but
I will number 10 will be
Centre
Suits
Christian Coulson
And then the other trilogy
For here I'm sitting eating a lot of the season
Museum Ellesmere Port
Etobicoke foresight
Any 2010 in here
Ok so here
I bust a new requested to you
The nearest
This Makita liable to make it clear and 20th anniversary
Celebrity quiz UK
And then I puzzle international consultancy TV presenter
Be able to go in adaptor
Christmas holidays in the Sun
Instead of returning void I will return any string
Tunisia you don't know when
I don't hear it
Returns of the English more like asp.net internal structure to make a response but I won't go into that
Humid
Anniversary presents UK
So here I'm
In the bus
Smythson
Luxury Brittany by diesel
There is another version something like that
Why not
For the other two will you tell me that and I will accept them on that
Instead of all that
Should we call to that
Exacerbated
Yellowtail
So I don't I don't mind
Three Steps to install kodi on firestick
Then when I'm in every method of the other three stability
It's
Prostate is to edit forms are constituted Enderman
Single step is to call the military
And then the first step is to adopt Cumberland
Answer of putting password you want to return it
You know well what is a bottom entry method of had a total list
Making sure
In that case I don't have to adopt you so I will just introduce a new variable
For the number seats
Invitation Rayquaza in real life baby do you have to sterilise Your Say
Southend
Who is similar to step
Because ice. Is that far for us that sometimes you have to
Translate to German
In local variable
The domain object
So here what I just did this to get some diapers but this is where you will have to talk later.
Adjust whatever I text to O2
From here to prawns in the Midlands
So now I called her eggs are gone so he's going that says it's a business domain
I'm the Sword and I put it there
Turn a local variable that end in Dorset
Animosity call me requested
Anymore
I called the exact
It's a written resolution
Cirencester Patterdale Cross
Tyres on a Sunday
Cinta salah search method I will have to await
That's untrue sorry says some July
Simpsons of Mercedes SE
Because it's closer I sync my phone I have to do so and then adapt some of her
Hotels in Benalmadena
And you're a retard
NCIS origination comes a MiDAS music
And then
What I do is true
Adam Birch
Forms of dementia
Provision
Pathogen
Mrs still read what did I miss
Mercia
America
This is Michigan weather in Ashington
Sorry for the wait time 29th
In asp.net
Topsy Regency with one of the process we have done what we have to do is no completion notification
I don't know what you want to do
We have less than 10 minutes I think
What
That part should near the one that we will put into the set-up of the application so I can do that
Dragon tattoos on Weber spirit
Movie spirited to keep some time for questions or for killing rabbits for new thing ok
The weather today will have to run for the return
Uniplate
So
Robert
We started from situation like this we have a web ticket manager
Wizadora positive are good diseases that do that and then the Zen Den
And after all we need to some more
Golf courses Stanton Moor
I don't know what to say at the shops
Rockin concerts
After all the others are scared of something like this
Thing is
Yes pretty much what we had shaved
What's important that we Embrace the long weather for older men
Weed awkward
But we get so Good lyrics rapping
And when we if we had time to executor new panda will have less warnings
Control urinating
Just just informed you
So we are we will come down sticking back to the nations that trend was actually don't put all of this field
Musixmatch
UB40 that is not able to read our code we can read a code in front of him
Nbr yeah being able to have a discussion and he's
Amoxicillin is not what I want for fall for the system start stop
So there is less
Pretenders live gaps between between Plymouth and what she was talking about
Sides
Madonna if you want to follow him
We had some independent show it in a few seconds but just before that no longer
Listen because it takes time to switch
As a father Robin
We will have to 1:50 to make you feel that because all the racecourses in Paris and authorisation weather
Museum on stairs
But it's crucial to talk to your limit expect yet muscle project as it should because delivery note
Allowed to I want to talk to the next.
Performing to know it's a number I think she said not to go to the project if it's like this
But it wasn't looking at the beginning of a carrier so
Text yes it's Takes correct time determination to Twin Falls at
When is crucial otherwise
Who has India done by the Legacy
Because I'm a coach and I learn how to reflect all of the Godzilla people when there is
Dependencies said my code is not testable I surely we can test a nickel
Eniko
So
Don't be daunted by biggest
You may have some dust
Yeah and also do if we don't use a lot of techniques
We basically used to
Betting techniques from the refectory Newcastle knotting Ferrell
It's extracted move message so it's
Pretty Made Simple
As soon as you have a tetanus
Beautiful steps
You can apply to move
Very very easily
The more complicated is to find some
Popular Simon chicken in NN2
Interinvest new older men designer
Do we have greater impact of improvement
If you just send me some of you
Yes this is something that is only doing and I'm inserting
You have been very interesting with that so thank you very much