Ok, something better you?
Yep
Can you see what's still bothering
Ok it's still very procedural code, one method, too screen high
doing this and then doing that and then do this ok
Collection script
Yeah, Here "get the train" is useless
so we cut it
Yeah, It is better
Now, the problem is we
still share the "train", but this one normally return the domain object, not a kind of JSON.
We will see that a trend that have a physical of proxy
to external web API will make into
a adaptor, for in the portal adapter pattern that we will
Have another of view before that, so don't worry if you are not aware of that, instead of returning
a string of JSON let's make that
method return as a train stones. Yeah
So that we can get rid of JSON within the method
To make it more domain and purely and not mixing technical staff with
function domain stuff. Ok for you? Yes. Still Ok for you?
So I discovered that the file
There is a constructor of the train
The train, ok, we see a lot of stuff to deserialize JSON
This is the file actually
This one is not choosed
Delete, OK
this one is never used too
Let's delete it also
also this one is grey
You can split into various files maybe.. Yeah, let's delete
So here we are in the
Train
Class
Yeah, and Train class does not have tons of behaviors I would say except
by parsing a
JSON
My magic resharper
Ok
we use a lambda. OK. Yeah.
I will move this one. There are the members of ... the properties and field of ... Ok.
Then all we have its a constructor. Only technical stuff.
What would you suggest
If I drink
[Audience Question]
There is better location to do some JSON parsing
but the train which is part of the domain and we should not do that here.
Let's us do that. Yeah, Ok, so do that I have to create
a little [method] to encapsulat the code I want to move.
This is something that we will do a lot. Extract and Move, Extract the method and move into the proper location.
We do that a lot during the session. The first time we will do it. Ok.
I take all the code I want
To remove, To extract
This one is ok?
One more, Ok. this one. Okey.
The screen is very high.
So we extract method from that, and it still will be instance method. Yeah.
That
Train topology
Because while passing the JSON.
The thing is
Setting some value to the property of the train
That's a nice method.
Here?
So who is extracting into a new
Method
Probility to move it to continue to use this? Yeah.
A good way to see if I have some dependency because that I want to move this one
But I don't want to add dependency from this one
I know I want to be insulate
So
I use static
And I have some squeezers.
Squeezes
Here and here because this is static
That's where we tried to change the second test also see if it's static, it make some error.
Yeah so how can we cut these
Yeah relationship
Actually we're trying .....
[Audience Question]
it is a good idea. There is something we can do also it's a so far the if the string is not
empty then I increment the
the reserve seats instead of changing that
value of kinds of seats from that point
we may be able to cut the behavior
within the property and every time
call the property the property is doing
the test so it may be one way of
doing it so what do you think? let's try
that and as I set here instead of
letting the method changing the value
it will be something like 'seat' ..
where... not where.. count
not... Something like that..
Richard so it's a kind of think you for
so much aware of Java streams it's a
more functional way of dealing
with collection and with enumerables
it's not so, here below is writing something like I take the
list of the seats and I count every seat
where that lambda is meaning all seats where they don't have a booking at
first. so okay I can I can
surprise this one
so now you can get rid of that
it will be done at the other level
and this one maybe I can make as
you propose something similar associate
to list of.
yeah, show some that
method into a function actually because
it it may be a static function yeah so I
have a seat I change the signature, like a
list of suits it
okay
and then here I change the local
variable, And now I return seat
so we can extract that method into a
function so that where we call it we get the result directly
so...  we adapt train
topology
this is a first step
because we have to move it into the
proper location
why is it trend is...
because it's because it's actually.. it's a matter of time
okay, maybe so you
extract the method you make its static function
so we can move it kind of
easily
let's put it....
if you get back to the method
where it has been called
yes
here we have a get train
yeah
so it might be interesting
instead of having the JSON topology to
get the train
to return a train
maybe we can put that static function into the train data service
yeah
so let's move
so you move the method
into the train data service, okay?
so far we still have a awkward
dependency in the train class but we change it in a second
so you make it to a public
Yes, And
the goal is to change this one
the get train
I will change the signature
so instead of returning a task of string
yeah touches before it's I
think where of requesting a Web API so
it's kind of actually on that complexity
but...
okay
but you have to read it
it's return a train
yeah
to be better. for the business part
I will to take the train...
okay
so you new train track from the topology
but the train doesn't take the
topology we want to adapt the JSON so
we call it that adaption train topology
but currently the train don't receive...
you have to change that
yeah
I have to change that also
instead of that
let's accepting a list of seats
yes
so to instantiate a train we will accept
the list of seats which will be much more easy to discussed yet, to play with
yeah and remove this one
so we don't have any kind of references from the train to any kind of train data service
or a structure code you know
so that so
now I can take this one so 'gettrain'
now is returning a train
so you don't need that anymore
I can remove this
and here we have some...
Okay yes much better
we asked the train data service to get
a train and we get a train
I compiled because maybe I have
break. yeah I read something
something that buzz me is u nconscious even
if it does not compile it still green
yeah it's a kind of bug I would say. It is a ...  Yes this is a ...
within of test we did enough tests we
have made some ... to a train
from a given JSON for given topology
and this is where we have to do the same
we have to adjust the previous code that
we are expecting to ...
signature to the new one
so, compile, it is ok.
fine all right
it's okay it's okay and
you come back to ...
let's get back to the ...
okay so thank you Bruno
yeah
actually we move a topology code that
were part of the train
so I'm much better, much
more comfortable with that code but
there's still lots of things that bother me
for instance let's see the train
okay you clean the deck you improve the situation
but ok, this is a train what is
it? it's a pure data class without any kind of behaviors without any
responsibly
and I'm not aware, maybe it's
a follower that has said
once this kind of object is kind of
teenager object or child object you have to take responsibilities somehow
and yet, so - let's let's do that
also we have a concept of seats yeah seat Wow
there is a name for that
yeah actually there is a name for that
kind of domain you have an idea of what
so we are lacking all the
concept of the domain within our code
but when we have we have kind of data class yeah and all of yours in easy that original method
kind of collections fit here very
positive are doing all the logic what I
suggest if you agree is to try to cap some behaviors
and to put it in the
proper location and try to mass
our child objects
yeah maybe you can
show something about our to check
yeah
maybe we'll slide just since we will do it a lot let's see visually what we will do
we have a Class A Class B
Class A is a web ticket manager has a method for
instance and the Class B is like say the
train so what we will do a lot
it's to extract code to extract the
behavior and to a method so then we will
have a method
into the same type and then we will move
it into the proper location, the train
for instance and at the end of the day
we will have more actually...
good balance
yeah domain and stuff like that
okay
so let me switch back to the code
so I suggest that we will do that
okay each train reserved seats plus it's the
first business rule, a train should not
exceed maximum capacity of the Train
I suggest that we extract a method here
but maybe..
if does not exceed overall train's capacity
once you like that are you okay you know
there are you
yeah capacity
sorry I will make us a
non-static method a public one to be
able to move it easily so here I extract
that big if with that method
where should I move it according to...
the train
yeah and there is a hint if I have said
f6 to move Resharper say okay you pass
an argument a train instance of argument
so you can easily move that behavior to the tain
okay do train I have the train
does not exceed overall train capacity
if I want to request that number of seats
okay actually what we have here is available seats we are building a list of available seats
so let us call a
method with find available seats for
actually
there is some concept that we may introduce here
what do think
[Audience Question]
yeah, at the end of the day we need to have seats in a given coach
but before that the domain expert was
talking a lot about reservation attempts
it's a really important concept for him
so I suggest that we instead of just dealing with available seats
let's build something from that part
before
we are improving the code, Rruno also have something to show you
yeah maybe you some people know and
depend it's a tool to check the
dependency but it exists JArchitect
for Java or C++
basically an advanced tools yes it's analyzing your code and
raising some warnings or error and we were
working with Macau in deep
yeah and we asked him to introduce a way to check that code base, follow the
ubiquitous language, it's a prototype
is not a release and we try to imagine you you have a team you have a
legacy code and you know the vocabulary
of the domain expert and create a rule
it's called your code should rely on
your you ubiquit language and we see
we have some problem and as you can see
we have the list of program
and the world not matching correctly
the cap is there so we have to enter a
list of worlds that are part of our domain
yeah like train etc .. currently we have defined
this list for each domain you want and the tool we tried to check
that so it's still in alpha yeah
but I think it would be interesting where to
make some audit of some
to have a kind of code smell about that
okay okay
so run it
what was the result?
okay so let's get back to to the business
we have some list of
available seats I suggest that we change the signature that
we introducing the concept of reservation attempt
so here instead of returning a
list of seats let's make it return a reservation attempt,
typo here
thank you
okay yeah okay the type does not exist
so yes I'm aware of that maybe I will
rename it also but here as you can see
sorry ..
the reservation temp type does not
exist yet so let's create it I'll tend
to create a reservation attempt
okay?
and here since the
function is expecting to return me that
kind of reservation attempt all I have
to do is to install yet here at the end
return a new reservation attempt
ok?
providing it the list of seats I just found
all I have to do is to create the
constructor accepting a list of seats for that reservation attempt
ok？
And that's it
maybe I will need to to walk with the seats
so let me start off creating a field[parameter] seats
Maybe introduce a read property because I will
need to work with the the seats of that reservation attempt
okay?
so we just introduced a reservation attempt which has a property of seats
and that's it
pretty much so that the findavailableseats now the name is maybe
build reservation temp
would be better
yeah okay
so now the method is built reservation attempt
its find available
seat within the Train and return a
reservation attemp with that
it's okay for everyone
said
so the code is not compiling anymore because I used
to work with the list of seats so what I
need is to rename available seat by
reservation attemp
first step and then to
add the in direction to the seats and to
work with the
the list of the seats
so just let me fill that
three location
f12
oops
got seats
should compile let me check
okay it's compiling is still green
so here what I just did is to create a
concept that is directly come from the
domain a reservation attempt and replace
a simple list of seat
okay ?
what can I do here reservation attempt
here it's like saying the
is reservation
attempt fulfilled, the domain expert
talking a lot about that so let's create
a method for that
extract and move
is fulfilled or not
I think it's it's okay for that
so we asked the reservation attempt are you fullfilled
so first extract still on that
class and then to move it to the up
sorry
I extract to behavior and I put it into
the proper location which is reservationAttempt
let something bother me because you pass twice the seat request count
yeah
you passed there and pass there
you actually can provide
the seat requested count once when we construct the reservation attempt so
that we don't need anymore to ask to provide it every time we want to to
check if it's fulfill
let's do that
okay I agree
go to implementation
seats requested counts I would provide it
into the constructor of the reservation
attempt here okay sorry I thinking I did a huge mistake
so okay so I changed the constructor of
the reservation attempt I'll tend to add
parameter to the constructor
yes please sir do that
and seats requested count here
what I can do is simply to keep a
read-only field meaning it's not public
it won't be accessible by the outside
world
now I had it what
I can do is to leverage on it instead
of the one that is provided as argument in the each fulfill so here I replace it
the parameter with the internal field
and now can get safety delete this
parameter since I'm in C# I can
transform it into property expression body
okay let's let's move that now I
think it's okay okay so here getting
back to the each fullfield usage you
see I'm on a reserve method I asked
to build a reservation attempt to the
Train
oh maybe
you don't move the BuildReservation on the train
below that I move the build attempt method to the Train
first so let's move
it into the Train so now I can ask the
Train, please train build reservation attempt with that number of
seats I want.
get a reservation attempt
and then if it's fulfilled then I can
continue I can continue to ask the
booking reference and also booking ref
is not part of the domain he said always
booking reference yeah so let's stick to
the domain long edge in that case and
then what we do is to iterate on every
seats of the reservation attempt to
assign the booking refs yeah maybe we
can extract a method here and put it
into the reservation attempt directly
which will be assigned booking refs
which one the
the demo of exacting term
of the domain expert we assign a booking refs
to revervation attempt
ok I extract
the method what will be the next chain
stuff to do to move yeah move to the
reservation attempt
ok so we assign
booking refs to the reservation
attempt
ok if we look at the
implementation for you to
follow we take that bookingReference and
assign it to every one of the seats of
the bookingRef
ok?
[Audience Question]
I was thinking the same thing as you
and the domain expert was really saying
the process is to build
a reservation attempt and at the end of the day to transform it into a
reservation so yes but I was the same idea
yeah absolutely
good question
actually we thought it's
like a technical term build you used to
do it to use it in technical but for the
domain expertise it was still a concept of this realm
so we have a train caching to save ...
Wow well maybe it's time to morally
have a cache in this application within
this application, yes you can cache everywhere let's see if it's still
relevant here
ok?
we have a declaration
of the cache here on web ticket manager
then we associate it into the
constructor of the web ticket manager
then we clear it
interesting we clear it
and cause it change the color
it illustrate me that oh it takes 3
second, average of 2 second
to clear the cache I don't know what
it's there but ok I hope it was and then
we save,
yeah the bookingReference and
the train id, ok. into the cache
and then that's it
so the cache where we only save stuff
but think about our
maybe it was a
unfinished item,
maybe that but even
now if we implement correctly it's a
mistake
as we said before
why we cache our topology,
it's a mistake
they can change it
and so yes it's a it's kind of stupid
thing I would say let's get rid
of that, I remove it here I
remove that remove that
I feel better now
[Audience Question]
this is the kind of discussion we may have since it's not here we
call it before because it's not the first time we run the session but
yes I will be with that this is
something that we must discuss about the
strategy without talking about technical details but saying that we can memorize
stuff that we get at that time is it
correct according to you
[Audience Question]
so yeah so ok
we get back to the method we get a train
from train data service
then we have to judge train capacity
if it's not the case we build a reservation attempt yeah then we check
if it's fulfilled or not because we may
run out of seats I see the train is full
for instance or reached the next to the
limit then we ask booking reference service then
we assign the booking reference and
then we booked the seat and then we
return the the result I don't know for
you but now the method is one screen high
we are embracing a little bit more the
concept of the domain