Are you ready? Yeah? Okay, here we go.
First question for you, who experienced some difficulties
to grasp DDD concept at the very beginning
while it's the time to put it into your project or into your code?
Yeah ok. So you're not alone. I have to confess
I see a lot of talk about DDD.
And I
tried to apply on legacy code.
So that's why we've made this session.
Absolutely. At this time here we will mostly talk about technical patterns.
And most likely talking about where and how to put your domain experience of your business
into your code.
Much more than strategical pattern. We'll talk a little bit about it.
But it's rather technical.
on the entire session.
Let's introduce ourself maybe before we move?
Oh yeah. So I'm Bruno Boucard. I'm coming from Paris and I'm a coach.
I'm teaching TDD, BDD and DDD.
And I'm in charge of
BDD meet up in Paris.
Ok, my name is Thomas Pierrain.
I'm working software since 18 years. I'm also co-organize the DDD Paris meetup.
I'm kind of opposite, by use cases and
problems based.
Cause I think we jump too much too soon into the solution based.
All our ? and stuff like that, all solutions.
So this is one of my obsession.
Ok we have some gifts
for you.
So we have two books.
The blue one and the Refactoring by Martin Fowler.
So to win those books you would have to tweet as hell during the session.
Using the #DDDEU.
We have a referee here
So he will have a look at that hash tag. And the most
funny tweet or you can record, you can take picture, you can do jokes about us or about you, whatever
and John will tell us the two winners at the end of the session. All right? Cool.
Our domain for today will be train.
Train is kind of large. Actually so we will focus more on the seat reservation optimazation.
Here is the model of a train. The train which has three coaches. Coach A, coach B, and coach C.
Which has some
seats already reserved in the orange.
Empty seats are in white.
And here we are asking 6 seats
to be reserved there in the train in blue. This is a simple model but that may help to understand something.
something. Okay?
We have two business rules for today for the system. The first one is
We should not reserve more than 70% of the entire train capacity.
Okay this is the first business rule.The second business rule is
When I want to reserve, I want all my seats in the same coach.
We don't want to split families and friends
between coaches. Right?
Simple.
We are taking those rules from Emily Bache's Train Reservation.
And we've put some crappy code on top of that but... ok
Our domain expert couldn't manage to be with us in Amsterdam today but we talked a lot with him before
previous weeks.
So he talked a lot about rain
He talked about train ID or identifier. He talked about seats.
Coaches.
Reservation attempts and whether or not these reservation attemps are fulfilled.
And you know there are also to book. If I'm to book,
Booking reference we have explained what it is.
Reservation, reservation failure.
That's the word from the expert. Yeah you know the session we have, those words
kind of
So we will work for a start-up company which name is Train Train. They provide
seat reservation service which is basically web API.
And this web API to do its work, he has to rely on the
external backends provided by external companies
So in fact it's SNCF
So the first backends provided by SNCF,
which is extermal to our company, it's Train Data
Basically it's a
train topology service.
Meaning we provide a train event for you.
And we get back the topology of the train meaning
all the coaches and for every coach, all the seats and for every seat, whether or not it's available
or already reserved.
Okay. Quantity
Second one is the booking reference. This is a kind of tricky one because... not tricky
When you buy a ticket, you have an ID
on your train ticket. This is the idea actually. Yeah. But this is a service that only provide a unique identifier.
We call it
book anything with that.
All we can do is to get a unique identifier
to play with.
And once seat reservation service on the left will have train topology, find available seats,
then,
Getting a booking reference, we actually book
the reservation
through the national train operator service
through the last train booking service.
All right? In terms of we are kind of down streams. We are a tiny start-up in that
open market that hasn't been opened recently. So these are the back-end provided by the national train.
Is it ok for all of you?
We will continue.
Maybe Bruno we can do a demo of the web API
It will take a few
seconds to
switch.
So
I use postman
where you can see the url to call the web API.
And we can see the body
The payload is with two fields.
Train_id is the identifier of the train.
And the number_of_seats requested.
Ok
So if you post.
Yeah.
Take a while.
Still loading. Okay and we have a answer.
The answer.
The first is the train_id.
Okay?
Second one is a booking reference.
Allocated by service as I said before.
And the list of seats
We get back.
Okay. So basically that's quite simple way to interact with our system. Yeah.
Okay. And basically we have a problem. And this is reason why we are here today.
Train Train start-up, called us because they face recurrent penalties,
Excess of penalties by the national train service.
Why?
Every call
You made on all those back-ends, you pay fees. So that means that start-up the Train Train start-up.
Every time you call one of those web API is charged from these.
So they are expected
to do so. But,
they think they are paying too much.
So they asked us to have a look at the code.
And to see
what may be the reason and can we troubleshoot and fix
if we have something to fix
Okay? But before touching any legacy code, if you are... Bruno and I, what would you recommend
us to do?
(Test?) Test, yes absolutely.
In fact, this is the reason why we miss the keynote. We have a bit test on this this morning.
Discovering the code in trying to highlight
all those business rules. So we've made so far 3 exception tests.
First on is a happy pass. We have a train with only one coach
with 10 seats. And we want allocate or reserve 3 seats.
And as you can see that's exactly what I do with postman. And exactly the same answer.
Simple happy pass. Ok.
Second one is the
Yeah this is the first business rule.  We can't exceed 70%,
for reservation , in all the train. And if we ask 2 seats,
and you can see I already have 6 seats reserved,
Here.
Because I applied the rule,
So 70% is 7 seats in the train you can sit. Exactly. So the way to repond an error
is this one
I get the train ID but the booking reference is empty.
And the list of seats are empty.
This is how Train Train is telling us, no
reservation has been made for you.
Ok.
And the third test was... test highlighting the all seats must be in the same coach please.
The second business rule.
And in that case we found a bug. We found a bug because we asked
here we have a train with two coaches. And one is almost full.
The other is completely free. And when we asked 2 seats,
Actually we get here. One seat in coach A and one seat in coach B, which was unexpected because
we don't want to split families and friends.
So we're thinking about that. Bruno was saying that
it may explain something related to this phase.
You have some ideas about what may explain the extra phase.
Imagine you use
the website.
You call the service.
And you prepare a trip
With your family or your
girlfriend boyfriend.
What happened? （Maybe you want to cancel your reservation because you cannot sit with your firend.)
Yeah. Exactly. The answer is to cancel.
Because I'm not pleased to have 2 seats in 2 different coaches. We cancel maybe retry it.
Cancel retry, cancel retry, at the end of the day I will switch to another provider.
I will left Train Train.
Poor experience.
But it may explain that because every time every attempt will be charged actually.
So that was our hypothesis.
And we discussed it with domain expert and he said, yeah,
maybe a new answer, please
guys can you please fix that bug.
So we are here to fix that bug all together. And we will ask you to help us in the journey.
So what would you recommend to fix that bug?
大家现在有什么建议吗？
What would be your strategy?
We are the train reservation service on the left on the Orange. Here, let me...ok
We are only working on that seat reservation in the yellow.
These are dependencies. We don't have leverage on that actually. (Are you the only cosumer for these)
No we compete with other companies. We are start-up and we compete with other companies.
We need some information from those two and we need to set and to comfirm
and to book
to make transaction with that guy
So
That's kind of interaction we have.
So it's time for the strategy what would you recommend? (Writing tests?)
Write tests.
Yeah write tests.
So actually we already wrote 2 tests so that highlight the bug. So we will have to fix that test. Ok?
So let's dive into the code.
Bruno has
set breakpoints
We can call it here. Yeah absolutely. Just a minute.
It's launching the bug
So here if you
just slide to the left side of the screen
It's a C# code. It's a asp.net code API.
It's simple for those who are doing java spring boot. It's simple for... When we request that post on networks
with that name
We get that call back
And it's a ReservationRequestDto we receive.
Just to have a look at the Dto. It's very simple, exactly the payload of the json.
Absolutely.
And so after all that, we installed that, if you can slide to the left, thank you. So we installed that
webTicketManager which it seems to be the entry point of the system and we call reserve
method on it,
providing train id and the number of seat requested.
Ok so
This is what we have test so far
If we have a look at the tests. These are failing.
We have 3 tests.
It's like kind of exception tests. We consider these items as black bugs.
And we sent some requests and we checked the
json.
The last one is the test
demonstrate the problem. Ok?
So wait. We have a tool, it's name is ?  We see every time we change
something, we type something, we change the code. It will run the test in background, execute it,
and provide us a feedback loop with a colored arrow on the margin.
So green is fine and red is
there's a problem. And there's an arrow in Red.
Bruno, if you...
Yeah I will show. Have another view of the error.
Basically it's the problem. We are expecting to have
2 seats in 1B and 2B. And actually we get
10A and 1B. So this is the bug we discuss earlier.
Ok everyone?
I think it would be a good thing to stop to have another view of what the Reserve method is doing.
I'll just align the code for you.
Let's have a first overview. We discovered that this morning so we will have
a little bit more knowledge about it. So I will try to help you to
to have an overview.
First we ? a list of available seats. That should be
probably the result of the method.
Then we call a get train on a trainDataService.
And we get something like we call jsonTrain. Maybe is a json topology we will see it after.
Then we install a train. A train installs of ? json topology.
And after that train installed, we do some business rules here and there. So here,
if the number of seat already reserved in the train plus the number of seats I'm requesting
is below,
is below something like GetMaxRes, let me check.
Should be some percentage or something like that. Yeah, 70%.
Ok.
70% of the overall train capacity.
So if
I respect the first business rule, I continue.
I continue. The numberOfReserv seems to be an accumulator variable here
And we tried to find some available seats.
An availble seat in that system is the one that the BookingRef is empty.
We have a property and if it's empty string,
that means that seat is available
And then we can add it
into the list.
The list that we will return at the end of the method
Is it okay for you so for?
Then we have a kind of stupid forEach. We haven't seen that in years ago.
Oh then what do we have yes if we can't
find the number of seat requested, what do we do? We get the answer, you know,
the result that is saying that you can't even reserve.
Remember, it's a failing message.
If it work, that when we call the bookingReferenceService, the one in the middle on the right side.
And call GetBookingReference.
Then we
assign a booking reference to every one of the available seat that we have found.
So far
We have a bunch of accumulators here.
And then, again, it's
pretty much the same if. If you look at...Yeah it seems similar. No the first one is negative.
Not really same. But,
if it's still ok, oh we use the cache? Yeah. Interesting.
We will see that...why, okay?
And then what do we... Actually this is the one that is making the booking, you know.
Transaction actually.
It will be the external web API we call to book a seat.
If I
enter that,
let me check,
here the implemetation.
Yeah basically we call a web API.
Real Interesting.
And it seems that if we don't have any kind of exception here,
what do we do? We return the answer.
And the answer is the one dumping the list of seats
we have found so far. Okay?
And the case here, what was it? Yes, in the case of the train capacity limit
has been exceeded,
we return the empty... you can't reserve anything in that train. It's a failure.
Ok for everyone of you?
We will make a few review working on it. But,
do you have some
feedback about that so far？
(Why are you using string concatenation to create json?)
Why are we using string concatenation to create json?
Actually this is not our code.
As a declarer. This is a customer we discover this morning. So yes, but this is a good remark, why do we
append a json here in the middle of something that, it's expected to be some kind of
business logic.
(Prove it with a github link.) We don't even use git in that project. You know.
So I can't do that. (Maybe I think the business logic is quite intermixed all togather in one function?)
Yeah, you are right.
Yeah absolutely. Yeah.
That is a strategy we will try to apply with you. We try to discover
the domain concept through this code.
And we try to figure out how can we improve that because so far there's something that's really bother me.
We were talking about the domain expert
talking with us with tons of concepts.
Can you see apart the train, and the
concept of seat, do you see any
other concept as well?
There's something missing. (Coach isn't explained. )
Yeah. The concept of coach is completely missing here.
And other stuff? (Reservation?)
Reservation, absolutely. No reservation. No reservation at time so far.
So, who have experienced code like this?
In this case. Some of you.
So we are not alone. So the idea here, for us will be to have a kind of way of
improving it.
Because,
since we don't have any kind of coach here,
the strategy for us to fix the bug would be to make it
But before that,
there's so much crappy thing and like that.
So let's clean,
first clean the deck? Yeah.
Do you know the name clean the deck?
The expression clean the deck? No?
Clean the deck
is the first phase when you discover a code,
because you need to be more confident before
to apply deep refactoring.
It's a way to discover, fix a little
names of the variables, for example,
And after,
get into the program. Yeah, it's a way to prepare our mental model in your head.
So come back from the beginning, so clean the deck, you will have another view,
trying to improve a little bit.
but before that.
(You have typo in 63.) We have typo in 63? Yeah yeah, it's for sure, for sure. It's really a legacy code.
But you notice something wrong? We'll fix that.
It's red.
It's difficult to
be confident if my code is red because if I made
a mistake,
I don't see the mistake. I prefer to see green
in my tool. So
to do that,
we'll completely ignore the test and just search the bug.
It's a good technique
if you're in the same situation when the test is failing,
and you need to refactor just before fixing the bug
you ignore that test and just search the bug.
So that it's green you have a test on this. You refactor and then you enable back the test to fix the bug.
So this is what
you're doing. And white
is meaning we don't run the test. And now I'm ready. (Fast question. Does it look better to
create a test, which test the
current behavior,
because when your refactoring, you want to basically
maintain the current behaviour.) Yeah.
(So by creating a new test, so that ignore the old test.) Absolutely. (By creating a new test which test the
current behaviour, you can't basically break it.)
Yeah. That is a technique I like a lot which is a golden master.
Golden master is you take a legacy code,
you clone it,
and you write acceptance tests.
Every time I send that input into the legacy code and the new instance, which is the one I will work on,
I'm expecting to see the same output
on both instances.
So that without
even understanding the legacy,
I can have a test on this.
Making me and forcing me... I don't break any existing behavior.
So this is a strategy that we could have done. But here we are implementing the business rule
as a domain expertise.
So we will stick to that point for now. But it's a good way for refactor.
Just clean the deck Bruno.
The first variable,
this is as noticeable, the variable seat.
I'll just have a look
where is used. Far from the usage. Yeah, far.
So
maybe,
I can decide to move this one
close to the usage.
Here for example. In the back of the room can you see all the code?
Because my test is running in real time I know I'm not breaking the code. It's still green.
The behavior of the C programmer, because I was a C programmer, was to put
all the variable at the beginning of the code.
So this is your...?
No it's not mine. Ok, second one is count.
Count, so... What a name.
Yeah, count, wow.
What a stupid loop. Yeah, we're looping on the list.
Actually it's a list of property count.
It's exactly the same number.
We have a hint here. It's unused. Maybe ? developer want to say something?
So what I can do is maybe to use
availabelSeats.
And apply count property.
Yeah because at the end of the for each loop, count will have the same
value as availableSeats. I can remove this one.
Okay?
Cool, I'll leave it.
On this screen hight, do we have ah...before we...We can check.
One, two.
Two
Two and a half? Two and a half, yeah.
So that was another thing that bother me to have a method like that.
Ok.
Ok, this is a code for the train topology.
Maybe we can rename it?
Yeah. Ok?
Train topology?
Yeah that' fine.
Traintopol and you can...Topology is better. That may explain we were talking about
the  train topology. So that's better. Okay, trainInst.
Instruction? Instance?
We asked domain expert about that, he said no I'm not aware of train instance by domain. So,
should be train install maybe or. So let's treat its name into train. Yeah. So you install a train from a trainTopology ok? Yeah.
What is this guy?
numberOfReserv. Maybe you can just...
Put it here for people in the back to see everything. Ok. You see this one?
numberOfReserv. Is it used? Yeah.
It's a pattern actually.
We use a variable
for nothing and... Just in case the calculation, that count is wrong maybe you can have a...
Maybe that's intends? I don't know.
Some times we don't have to try to understand. This is just silly stuff.
Ok, so I can remove this one.
Ok so you get rid of it. Yeah I get rid of this one.
Ok you can delete it.
Yeah.
Maybe...Each is？ Each...
It's seat. Yes, from collection of Seats, we get a seat.
This is a typo. reservedSet.
We don't talk about set. We've asked the domain expert also, do we even have set? They said no. This is a loop too.
But never used.
Who has already seen that kind of
variables, declarations in the code not even used anymore
Yeah. Legacy code is full of
this kind of stuff.
And it's kind of polluting our mind.
This one.
Have a look at this one. We have
a if here. And we have pretty much the same if at the invest?
Yeah I'll just...
We like symmetry it's much better to compare stuff. To do so, as we suggested, to invest? Yeah, it's a good a idea.
Indent, invest if, and then,
ok we can see pretty much the same...
I will select...No, no, wait.
Just illustrate it.
Here, as you can see there is one if. Here.
And pretty much the same here.
So the idea is since there is nothing in the middle we can cut the code into the if below.
And put it into the end of the first if.
This one, just at the end, to respect the algorithm.
So
it will simplify a little bit the code structure also.
It's really great. Green yeah. Okay?
So now you can...Read
Why are you doing that? Because... It's white. Yeah. Entrnce?, when the code
is not covered,
put a white
indicator.
It's a
good for us. This one is not necessary too.
Ok, you can remove some lines.
So I think we...
have some space? Yeah maybe this one can be closer to the usage.
Ok.
Ok so you
closer the declaration to the usage. And it's not perfect, but
we changed a little bit.
Not so much. It's not really a deep refactory. It's just to be more confident.
It's the first round, the first pass on the code,
when improving our mental model about it
and trying to clean up some mess.
Ok, something better you?
Yep
Can you see what's still bothering
Ok it's still very procedural code, one method, too screen high
doing this and then doing that and then do this ok
Collection script
Yeah, Here "get the train" is useless
so we cut it
Yeah, It is better
Now, the problem is we
still share the "train", but this one normally return the domain object, not a kind of JSON.
We will see that a trend that have a physical of proxy
to external web API will make into
a adaptor, for in the portal adapter pattern that we will
Have another of view before that, so don't worry if you are not aware of that, instead of returning
a string of JSON let's make that
method return as a train stones. Yeah
So that we can get rid of JSON within the Reserve method
To make it more domain and purely and not mixing technical staff with
function domain stuff. Ok for you? Yes. Still Ok for you?
So I discovered that the file
There is a constructor of the train
The train, ok, we see a lot of stuff to deserialize JSON
This is the file actually
This one is not choosed
Delete, OK
this one is never used too
Let's delete it also
also this one is grey
You can split into various files maybe.. Yeah, let's delete
So here we are in the
Train
Class
Yeah, and Train class does not have tons of behaviors I would say except
by parsing a
JSON
My magic C#
Ok
we use a lambda. OK. Yeah.
I will move this one. There are the members of ... the properties and field of ... Ok.
Then all we have its a constructor. Only technical stuff.
What would you suggest
If I drink
[Audience Question]
There is better location to do some JSON parsing
but the train which is part of the domain and we should not do that here.
Let's us do that. Yeah, Ok, so do that I have to create
a little [method] to encapsulat the code I want to move.
This is something that we will do a lot. Extract and Move, Extract the method and move into the proper location.
We do that a lot during the session. The first time we will do it. Ok.
I take all the code I want
To remove, To extract
This one is ok?
One more, Ok. this one. Okey.
The screen is very high.
So we extract method from that, and it still will be instance method. Yeah.
That
Train topology
Because while passing the JSON.
The thing is
Setting some value to the property of the train
That's a nice method.
Here?
So who is extracting into a new
Method
Probility to move it to continue to use this? Yeah.
A good way to see if I have some dependency because that I want to move this one
But I don't want to add dependency from this one
I know I want to be insulate
So
I use static
And I have some squeezers.
Squeezes
Here and here because this is static
That's where we tried to change the second test also see if it's static, it make some error.
Yeah so how can we cut these
Yeah relationship
Yeah mate motion answers
Send an apology as an argument
Yeah that's a good idea but there is something I can do also it's so far
If a is not New Zealand then I increment the results it
Instead of
Changing that value of cos of sitcom.
But we may be able to
Causes of using the potty
And everytime I call the property new property is doing the computer desk so many one way of doing it
Something
Instead of
Lezyne v11 changing the value it will be something like
Set
Return on debt collection of sets so that as well not not at work on
Don't want
Not Nero auntie
Something like that
Result sorry sir cannot thank you for the match
Well for the last rooms
Isomorphic artificial Wales
Drilling waste collection Andrews email address
It so that's not this not
So here when I was writing something like I think the list of the seats and I can't everything's well that Lundy is very
Ring all's well
I don't have a booking at all times his father
So now you can get
Rid of that
Familiar
And this one
Maybe I can
Next
As you propose something similar
ASOS a list
What's an intro song that's made into a fashion I shouldn't because I
Statin function
So
I was still the oceans furniture
I like you
List
Antalya
I received a look-a-like about yesterday now
I return
Sorry, that message into a pension
So that's where we call it we get the results
Direction
So since we added strength ability
University because we have to move it
What's the population
What is the train is because it's because it's running yeah it's a matter of
Ok maybe just trying to message you make it
Perfect
Function so we can move it
Granny off internet
Let's put it it will get back to you I haven't eaten
Well it has been called
Yes
Here we have the train
So it may be interesting instead of having no didn't have energy to get the train to return on train
For men you can put that
Study functioning to the tenderness of his
So let's move
So you must be signed into the train
Weather.co.uk
So far we still have a crown dependency in the
In the train class between infinity Motorcycle
So you make it to open each user
Yes and
The goal is to change the Swan
Madrid train and get train at Everton this year show
2010 original itasca strings attached before it sank
Will requesting a weather API so it's a good offer
I should have died complexity matter
Ok what tree restaurants in Sweden train
Maria Bello
For the business not have to take the train or within subject
Ok so I'm trying to transform the topology
The trend on deserts of the British weather
So we call it that
Identification
But
Currently the train a dog
Received
Citizens Advice
Change that herself still have that lets accepting a list of s*** yeah so it was not the train we will accept it
Mushroom much more easy to
Cliff Richard to play with and remove this phone
So we don't have any kind of references from the train to when you can off
Trend of Us army soldier
So that's
So
No I can
Texas want to get train now is retiring at rentals
So you don't need that anymore
I don't know what is fun
In here
We have some ok but we ask the train we get
I compiled because maybe I ask Reading
Even if it doesn't add components to Green
Brewers compile yes this is we do not test vision Express Enfield
Worcestershire train from Avengers unforgiven topology and this is where we have to do the same way
Have to adjust
The prettiest girl
The prospecting tool
The song on YouTube please YouTube the new one
So
Should
While I'm singing
Ok
Does a foil I don't return back to
Lips
Rebecca was ok
So thank you for all your technical
That we are back of the train and we get put into a politician
Mrs bottles in hospital
So I'm much better
How much mortgage off tomorrow is that good that there's another thing that bother me
Find Stones Let's see the train ok you can you improve the situation but
Ok this is a train
What is it
To a better class result in each other videos
Nottingham Christmas to me and I'm not aware of maybe photo calendar to send once
Instead of object instead of a teenager object or child object
Yes to take responsibilities somehow
Nhgs
Torrentz2
Wrestlers who that's also we have a concept of Sin
Well then I'm trying to talk to you who's the name for that
Actually there is a name for that
Canada men
Travelodge Ilford
Anna Magdalena company and England
So
We are
Lacking
All the percentage of The Dimension of God when we have we have kind of any mixture pin data class
All of the angels in Easy
That's rhythm a Third Kind of collection 6 year
Harry Potter July doing all the magic
What I suggest
Surely it's too
Production Gear Jordan to put it in the population in Tritton Leicester or child objects
You can show something about MOT checker
Roman numerals
Athlone
YouTube
Just since we were doing a lot and it seems really what will we do we have a place
Has be classed as a Wimpy Kid furniture offers on the sofa instance and the Crosby's Alexa.
So what'll we do a lot it's to extract credit
Please type the behavior
Into a method so then you will have a method into the same type
And then we will move it into the population in the train France
At the end of the day would have more actually rating
New Balance
Let me switch back to the planet
Lottery
We will do that
Ok
This train reserve seats personal analysis the first Middle School attendance should not
Maximum capacity of the train
I suggested recycle message here
But maybe does not it does not exceed does not exceed
Overall
Friends episode in concert
Are you ok
Will that work
Depression
Diversity
I will make us a non static method and primaquine to be able to move it
Isn't it
So here I strike that two minutes with that method
Where should I
Move it
Going to
The training and everything
If I said
6 tomorrow
Azure Python passing arguments to an instance of an argument so you can easily move that day
Trainer has a train does not exceed over altering capacity
If I want to replace number of seats
Ok
Actually what we have here is available seats
Real building list of available seats at School of Massage Windsor
Final elements
Wynsors
Filezilla
Nonsense
Turn on statistics on solar movies
So here
If the train does not exceed if I request does not exceed the maximum capacity
Where to find sum of elements
Actually
They said that we may introduce here instead of that
When you finish
NBA profit
Just pretend
Allocation
A specification
Yes
Yeah except of course at the end of the day we will need to try 1800 Portsmouth
Before that's the don't expect was talking a lot about whether I should attend
Set a rear bottom cassette for fine
So I think it's so sweet
Instead of just dealing with available seats a list of Sith
There's a vendor distance of possession from that
But
Yes I sent you something
Original iPhone we are improving the colour blue are at something to to show you
Yeah maybe
Some people know in Japan
It's a tool to check the dependencies that it exists the architect for Java
Of C++
Navigational in your code and the Rising Sun
Warning forever and we were working with you thanks Mike I don't have anybody anyway
Ask him to introduce somewhere to check that turns photos into Cambridge
Author of the name Enterprise it's not a release and we tried to imagine imagine
Can you have a team you have a legacy card and you know the vocabulary of the next
Red Aurora
Scorpio card should rely on your ability language and we see we have some problem and
As you can see we have the list of program and the world not matching correctly
Letters of a gamma camera
We have to
Enter a list of words that are part of Oldham in Lancashire
Reclamation fruitfield
Manual and automatic
What is cheering alpha I think it would be an interesting way to make some
Forgot to issue a kind of smell about that
So Ryan's what was the results for the 3
Yeah I don't want to
Ok so let's get back to to the business we have a solicitor
Available seats
I think that we change that
Send signature on that by introducing the concept of inheritance
For here instead of returning a list of sets
Let's make a trip return reservation
Adult
I'm sorry I'm going to type all Heroes elation at them thank you
Ok
Ok the time doesn't exist so yes I'm aware of that maybe I will ring I need to answer that
Shiraz UK
Say sorry as I was July 10th where is it
Sorry
Yesterday night and I don't I don't think so let's Create it and enter
Three types of violation adult ok
Share
Since
The method is a function is expecting to it'll music and possession all I have to do
Is to install search here
Asian
Little and newer version attempts
Ok
Providing you
The list of sheets I just found
All I have to do is to create the conflict or accepting a list of Sith
Well that's what I said I don't ok
And that's it
Meditation intense I need to
I will need to drop in the sticks
So let me
Set of creating a few let me Create
Let's be real and that
Apprenticeships
National identity history
Maybe to produce a report that said because I will need
Rock with her the tips of that animation of dogs
Ok
So we just thinking to reservation account
Each other property assets
And that it's pretty much
So that the final elements it's now the name is
BBC weather
Any better yet
Fernando massages beautiful passionate earned it
Find a venomous it was in the train and return result shadow temple that
It's ok for everyone
So the card is not complaining anymore because I used to work with a list of seats
So what I need is to rename available to buy in Ashington
And then
Two
Adding directions to the city
Dental work with the list of numbers
Convert 3
Location
S12
Look suits
The squirrel in love
Rob Delaney
Fortran compiler Project
Ok it's compiling still win
For hear what I just did is to
Traits of a cancer directly come from the domain of havisham attempt and I
Replace a simple instruction by a mate
What can I do here I have a debit card
Yeah it's like saying
Doddle
The new film with talking a lot about that song
Let's create a method for that
A cut
Animals in
Fulfilled most complicated formula to find out in writing in English
Birthing kits
It's ok for that
So we asked
What is an isotope are you fulfilled so first X Factor
Cylinder under to gas and then to move it
I'm sorry
Today's weather
So I ate a cartoon of you and I put it into the politician which is awesome
The little something bother me because you passed twice
Citroen request agilitas
You better and if I can provide the 6th question Colts once when we construct
So that we don't need anymore to ask to provide it's every time we want to to check if it's Gucci wallet
Lisburn Auto Care degree go to implementation
Sequestered colds
I will provide it into the closet organisation attempts
Ok
Sorry I think I'm
I need a huge mistake
Up sorry
Ok
So I change the photo on the reservation account
Alton Tower, Cheltenham Hospital yes please sir
Regards
Italy coast to coast Newark what I can do is simply too cheaper
Arena mission meaning it's not finish it will be accessible through here
Outside world
388 in
No I had it
What I can do is to lay right on that
Instead of
The one that is provided
As arguments in the instruction
4 year
I replace it
The bomber dealt with in January I can get cigarettes
Define meta
Since I'm in the shop I can post your mates into property
Xbox One buddy
Ok
This one's that
No I think it's ok ok
So here getting back to the Institute
You said you see
I want to reserve massage I asked that has happened to me the other night then to the train
Albania on the train
Roulette
I just extract
The Mistletoe let's move it into the train
So now I can ask the train please try and give me your attention music
Number 68
Get off its food
Then I can continue
I can't continue to ASDA booking office and also looking at her she is not part of the domain you said always looking
So let's
Stickers of the mend Longridge
The Chase
And then what we do is to iterate or every citizen resolution attempt to assign materials
Maybe we can
Attack the messenger
And put it into the position and then directly which will be a sign
Booking reference
Which one video
Which was the
The devil's a dimension is that time of the minute we are signing with initials
Designer shirts ok
I tried to my son what will be the next
Stephanie
To move ya love to know that I don't
Ok
So we are seeing meteor showers 2010
If we look at the implementation just too funny to fail all we take that looking at house and sign it
To everyone of the seats
Of the multinationals
I was thinking the same thing as you and the Medics was really saying it
We build
The process is to build a reservation agent
And at the end of the day to transform it into hibernation
So yes but I wasn't saying that
Idea
Regression
Actually we thought it's like a technical team builder
Used to do it to use it in technical lead for the next concert
So we have a train station see what it may be sent to more and you haven't
Who is happy fashion within this application of the Year sequel
Yeah it's just everywhere let's see if it's irrelevant you ok
Rabbit
Decoration of the general manager
Then we used to set it into the hospital so intricate Benidorm
Then we clear it interesting
Weekly rates and an unconscious changing the glow in the stretching mediatek Street II
Average average of two figures
Total to clear the cache I don't know what to debit
Ok I hope it's worth
And then we said
The book
English film Olsen the trainer Gok into into the dash
And then that's it
Is that so
Attach where we only save stuff
But think about the hour
Ivana
Windjammer correctly
It's a mistake
As we said before we completely older
Khomeini
So
Autocar venues self service
And why we cash
HR department waiting staff
It's a mistake
You can change it and say yes it says it's going to stupid
Think I would say
Miss Katrina Isabella switch up
I remove it here
Animals that swim of that sand
Hi
Nationbuilder
This is a discussion we we we may have with the National
Thisisnottingham
Recording before win because it's not the first time we run the session.
Yes you're over that this is something that we discussed
Technical details with saying that
Retained amores
Stuff that we get at that time is it correct
According to you
So yeah
So ok we
Directors lodge massage
We get a train then we asked to train
Alex
Overheard in the other twin capacity 3 ask princess yet
Adjustable bookcase remember that I should I dance then we check if it's fulfill that
Nicolas Marin
Outdoor Pursuits
The house in the 24th fences
Wrist tattoo next to the Limit
Then we Oscar booking assholes
Then we assign the booking office and then we booked the seats
And then we return the there isn't
I don't know phone you but now the Mercedes one screen hi
We are addressing a little bit more the concept of the domain and we
After the spreading the news goes into the popular location the Twin Towers Malaysia
The
The seats also
The resolution attempt also
Yes I return money
No what would you suggest because it's important to be time boxed
Haha because I mean you can improve god a lot
What time we have an objective
Celebrity brewers
How to fix a bag
Concept
Return Tesco
Yep absolutely no idea what you're saying that in you what weekend is to get rid of that synergies on here
Any set to return to Amazon
And then return
Itasca because I was on here so that December 3rd is purely Dublin
No strangers on inside a simply recharging the oven in stock
Will do that
we will do that in a circle
but before that we would like to introduce the missing concept
because
when we enter BuildReservationAttempt here
we build it from the
train perspective and not from the coach perspective
we use all seats with no notion of coach
So how to introduce the concept of coach according to you what will be yours
Basiclly the topology is taken from the name of every seats...every seats has the name including a1 a2 a3 b4...
A is the name of the coach...is the name of coach
it's an implict where I'll figure it out these seats belongs to the coach
yeah absolutely..good idea
but how to introduce it
right now
what will be your next move?
yeah okay, but how to do that?
start by what you suggested if you have a keyboard
Yeah
Why not? But we will start with a widget test...absolutely...
from the train we will get ...
we will check that the a train exposed coaches for instance
for example
Because we totally addictive of
TDD
And
we want you
To create so let's add a TrainShould...should...fixture...
But so far we don't...we only have some  architecture tests
That's total system should do
Do this do that do it so we have three tests
And here ...to be our first unit test I would say
It's a time? should
And maybe...to be...should expose coaches something like that?
So we get a train
so should TrainShould expose coaches?
I move this one because I don't...
Should expose coaches
should...expose...coaches
so...yeah...
it totally about it...yeah...yeah...yeah
Actually here I had even in mind some new rules for the related to the coach even he first to fix by then
But
Because money
But he has something in mind to consolidate and to a new business rules
Such as
We should not
Feed a coach more than 40%
for instance
and step like so it we need the population through to make it
So Far we need it
We need to play with the coach
We need to ask it...to ask it
that's yes
If you want to keep it completely private implementation details for your detail capsulated
we won't write that
So just for
some explanation because I use a
A snake
name because we
We use it in the tests to mock some situations...this is a tenth topology table
so he will probably have built a spawning...it's a way to qualify the topology
And it's good to use because I know in this topology
I have two coach and
we stand seat for each coach so it's the reason why I use this one
So you in your test associated a train
Ok providing in the Train
The list of seats adapted from that train
topology
Ok
So let's check
train...coaches...
Yeah I'm sorry
And
I hate coaches but it doesn't exist at this time
We need to
A size of
two...because they have two coaches from the train topology
And you can also check that every coach has 10 seats maybe
It is long because I think it to be like a dictionary for half hour break....coaches["A"], coaches["B"]
Coaches["A"]
the seats...dot seats
A size 10
Because every coach...ya
Ok just to
Just to make it expose what we	have with in train topology...okay...
So it's start to generate something
Yeah...Ok
So you said the dictionary
Name
Coach
doesn't exists yet
The same we will create
type
for Coach...Yeah I would create it because...right time
So here the train will have
A list of coach
And now I can
start as a dictionary
If we have more time we won't expose it as a dictionary also we expose that a read-only dictionary
or even better a concept
The delegate type for that but
Since I would like to show you a lot of other step we want
right here but
To loop on the seats
So here we dig into the concept D I G would be
ok I've got a list of seats we said that the name of coach was an implict
information passed of the name of every seats
So for every seat we just have to check if there is a coach
With their name
Because seats has a proper capacity coach named
And if we don't have an entry in the dictionary yet from that
Coach name let's
add it
to the dictionary
Sorry
Yes we can use an link...yeah. you have a query on seats for the beginning of algorithm I prefer to show without thinking
And
by use to set a new coach...we also set a new coach...and providing info name...set the coach name maybe
So
we iterate on every seats of the train for everyone of them
we added the relating coach into the dictionary on the fly
Then we have to
add the seats
so...coach name
First step second step is to add the seat into the coach
So...coaches...
...coaches...array...seat
seat dot coach name maybe
I introduced available
we called it..can newCoach? No?
Yes
Ok...why not
new coach
add...seat...
Are you doing that for to expose it to use the kind of ? expression but you want to make it work and then we can refactor something like that
It is correct...ok...ok..
Now
Ok. Ok
actually you have to ......I have to refactor at first
the coache is here
coach..coach....coach...and on that coach..you had the seats
So...ok
So I had to
I suppose I have kind of list of seats
So you are
What glue do you use to make USB data switch for handling unit
we will need to make a coach
A nice place to to find our list of seats I would say
But
There is
something that bother me a little bit  in here. But
I'll let you finish
I've like to see greener
The greener
I see, they are green
oh, no, no..just compile...I think is not compiling
anymore, something like that
Oh, yeah...That expose size of seats....topology....encapsulate...and
seats
here...should be green...yeah...it's
ok....I don't really like that kind of
We
Add a seats to a coach...we change the coach
Actually
If you have more time
There is something I would like to do
It's even to make it everything immutable
Because what we do is
basically with when you reserve...we want to reserve	some seats, we get train apology
Which is something that we don't own
It's coming from the outside world
We work on it
And I really don't want us to be tempted somehow to keep it in touch
because it will be stupid
And I would like to offer the fact that's when we get a train apology it should be immutable all I can do is to work with
To find some information or to build reservation attempt
But I don't want to allow my mates
are new joiners in the team...it start
to...to...break that by introducing a cache and a state well
I don't want
to be
So if we had more time when I would like to do is to make your everything immutable, the train will be immutable,the coaches will be
immutable and the seats also
the only
things that will be mutable is the reservation attempt
you see the a formal reservation attempt which will be kind of entity that has a life cycle and $%^&?
But the time changed all over the time
At the end I will transform the reservation attemp to reservation
And the reseravation would be immutable
the reservation to reservation....we it's
yeah, you have question?
Sorry?yeah...yeah...yeah...Absolutely....is of reasoning also if we
get back to the
addseats
What would like is to maybe to one for seats it's to use what we call a closure of operation
its meaning the coach
We have a method which is addSeats so I can add seats for the coache
But instead of mutating me the coache instance
What we would like is to for that guy to reach on me
The New Coach
a new sort of coach installs
So
I called method...add seats on a coach instance
All it can do is to return your new instance
With that seats involved
But without changing the previous instance here that when I call the addSeats
Listen
So
The benefits is the first time with ability	for of course or for passion but also reduce the coupling
It's easier to move code
Here the coach
stand by itself somehow
you know...method on the coach which are mean you have the source of coach
For if I want to move that it's more easy than if the coach where related to a new type which is releated to a new types and s...
step like that.
Okay for everyone
Ok yeah
In any case it's important to discuss with domain expert
unfortunately we used to do that session with one domain expert
on stage with us
and we asked some questions since he's not here we note a lot of stuff
so there is a lot of implict you know in our head
But yes you're right you should have some kind of discussion
But
Here is much more an implementation detail I would say
It's to all folks the fact that I no want to talk any kind of
states relating to something that I don't
I'm not
owner of the topology of the train I'm just a user
and every time a request is it getting back to me
Get a snapshot...walk over snapshots
through my concept of domain and then make a reservation
So
Yeah, absolutely
Ok I think maybe it's not pop up...yeah...absolutely...okay...so...instead of changing the coach here
let's switch a new instance of coach
make it a coach of attention here
So I didn't seats it doesn't mutate the existing coach which will only return
a new coach instance
Coach
Ok
with seat name
with what?
With a list
a new list?
yeah
Acutally session is best form session of three hours we have made in paris ^&*()?
expect outstage our left floor forward
I guess museum story with tons of stuff so
we had to pick a fight for that short version of two hours... there are many things that we may improve what them about
So we can't find that the coach seats a train really value types
So we want to
go into that we will only make that coach immutable
Maybe
There's lots of things to me to improve...and respect the
priacy a sure
Yes
to avoid the
The big issue
to implement the same constructor as before ok
So now we have to fix it
the core
Yeah prefectly
Because existing code
was doing that
so its...maybe steps you know
you fix...this...call...in...^&*(..
So time to change it and to...so
So will be to get the coach
To add seats
So
through it...new coach
Yeah, new coach and then to stalk the new coach by
a ball into dictionary
So it's still red here?
But I guess that after saving that new coach value
Into the dictionary it will be green again
Fully?...new coach
That's right
Inevitable
Yeah...yeah
It was in the test
and the coach...okay
here
Unless you get back to the unit test again
Oh yes yes...you're right
completely right
we will do that because we would like to show you a picture second architecture and lots of other steps...but yes you're right...you're right
Yeah but absolutely that was next point actually we have a train which has
exposed a list of seats and trying to expose the list of coach
Because all seats belong to the coaches so what we should do is
Instead of adding duplicates collection on the train
instead to have a projection
And the list of seats for the train must be the
the projection of all the seats of every coach
of the train
so let's do that
select mini something like that
coaches
let's take every coach
And return the value
select many coach
for every seats
change to c
I just c dot
seats
toList
to a newList
with this kind of linked you again but it's we met a projection
we take
All the seats on every coach
And we return it at the this that's it for the entire train
So we have this one? we don't need to set it anymore because it will be
a get on me...a property
Ok
We need we have the coach...compiled
Yeah it's good now
So maybe we can maybe we can fix the bug
What do you think
So...Ok
Absolutely...villages?...yes
idea is to move the findAvailableSeats or the buildReservationAttempt
to the coach level
Because if we asked to the train level
There is no way of
properly there is a way that kind of crappy
so let's delegated it
To the to The Coach so I'm removing
This one
So we only do this the test it will be red and red
green step
So it's come back to the WebTicket
and as you suggested
Maybe the
buildReservationAttempt is in charge to be verified
and to tweet
Something new
Maybe we can change the algorithm
but respect algorithm
so I based on the coach
Let's put that
logic of looking at seats
at coach level
So for iterate every coach
So we really have you maybe the same thing build a reservation attempt...yeah...I would like to use this one
please coach
beat me build reservation attemp if you can
Ok
And returning you a reservcation attempt
ReservcationAttempt
Is reservationAttempt
Adele
And if...reservation attempt
IsFulfilled
Ok
Then return
reservationAttempt
If not, we continue to iterate it on the next coach ask to the same thing once we have
at least one coach
provide us its fulfill another reservation attempt we are happy with that
So
This one is actually the code I would like to
Completely get pasted
In
So let's create a method
Okay, and I don't like copy and paste actually
but in that case it
So justified
it's green....so we just fix the bug by doing that...maybe you can a red green refactor
Something to refact buildReservationAttempt to the train level
we still...let some code
So
based on the  what's on 'seat'
here we have some kind of
...copy code so let's replace it with a linq...request
So take me please all seats where BookingRef is empty
is empty...string dot is null or empty
if we create a method also yeah...yeah...and
take the number of seats request count
So here we are projecting a list of
Seats
That are available and then we have a list of seats and available seats and then we take
The first three four whatever number we asked...and I replace this one...it does
Exactly the same thing of the foreach loop we have seats here
To prove it you just have to
you have to...just to...get all of them
I remove
Ok
Ok you remove it
Here
Oops
I made a mistake
Now it's ok
So what we can do maybe seems seat constructor missed up anything to attract mosquitoes
things so here is quite difficult with
Inshallah ok
The target method we should be
isAvailable
Since we are working on seats
so non-static public
And we will
extract method and then we will move it into the seats and the seats level
So
Move it
So here now if you can zoom on the link us with a request
light on the seats and we take all the seats that are available
And we take the first number that we need it
We need it. That's we introduced that eariler for the each fulfilled
for another reservation attempt I should to be
to be able to say fulfilled obtain a good reservation it's design choice...yeah...
Ok
We happy because then we fix a bug
fix bug we can imporving a little bit in the code....yeah...
yeah maybe we can have a tiny part
about aggregates yeah so just a tiny
part about aggregates. Aggregates is a
collection of objects which is entity and value types
treated as a conceptual whole. Can
you see some aggregates in here
train? yeah. Is coach an aggregate? no.
why is that?[Audience]yeah some aggregates mayby immutable.
Actually it's
no because aggregates need invariants,
need business rules need something to to
to to
yeah to be enforced I would say. And here
the only variants we have is train level.
they must not exceed 70 percent of the
train tickets limited which is the business I
own and the coach aggregates as to as
to to enforced when we discuss with the
domain expert he told us that he
wanted to add some new rules related to the coach.
so that coach must not be
fulfilled also at must not be exceed
given capacity so in that case it will
turn into an aggregate voice maybe it's
a kind of detail. But something
interesting. Train, coach and seat may
all be value types here. as we discuss
earlier if we think about the way we
interact with the external backend we
get a kind of snapshot valid from a
moment of time and we will work on that
snapshot. so we don't want to keep it in
cache. We just want to work with all those
aggregates. fine cells so to enforce that
we can make it all value types. actually
in the long term Russian we that's what
we did
so that means that some aggregates may
be completely value types also.[Audience] yeah the
trend here it most of the case it's like
this message was to it was one
case where we could have this exception [Audience]
if we have a level-two Business School
to be enforced at the coach level it.
Yeah, in the long version we do that. So so far we
improved somehow the web ticket manager
and the before it was a free screen
high, full of legacy code with lots
of legacy stuff yeah. I think we have
kind of improved a little bit it's one
screen high. It's using the word of the
domain within the code what we call
ubiquitous language. we extract some
behaviors and we put them into the proper
locations, but there is still something
that botheres us. someone has told it
before this is that we have some Json
design into the domain method
and we still have our Task of strings
which is also a jism. yeah what we would
like to do here is to get rid of that
design, and stuff and to replace it by
reserve. sorry, reservation. So
that the Reserve method will return a
reservation. then on the infrastructure side
side and we will transform
the Reservation into a json version,
if we have an adapter if we have
something pluggable. okay so I
suggest I will talk a little bit about
the second equation which slide. I'm
sorry
I will work on the code you
don't see. but it will explain when we
get back to the code and like an
architecture we explain what we have done.
okay
so who is aware of what hexagonal architecture is?
okay cool what hexagonal
architecture pattern is made
by Alistair Cockburn.
I can't remember, the long time ago.
and it has many benefits. it's a pattern
at the architectural level it's known as to
embrace change it was the first idea of
Alistair was to plug and unplug external
dependencies plug and unplug stuff he
was talking about whether system able to
to be plugged with many different
standards as input and many different
stutters as output to broadcast news to
broadcast to TV to radio to whatever.
so it was kind of to have
of clean code inside and every changes
in terms of i/o or way to interact with
the system to be a non-event to be
something like you plug a plug in and
you can plug a plug in and that's it so
it's it's come with it was introduced by
that idea in mind but when we think
about it, it may allow us that we want to
first on the domain to make some code
more value, business value inside to
protect our domain code from the
technical stuff. I don't know for you but
during long time I thought it was not
even possible to properly split between
domain logic and and technical. We
tried many times that we failed a lot and
seems I discovered that pattern.
it's really a nice way to and for that
and I also want to enforce testability because
since everything is a pluggable and
We can stub, we can mock, we can
stub the input output of the
systems, business logic inside and so for
today we will focus much more the how to
protect our domain code. So how does it work?
It works
considering the world in two different
area there is inside and there is
outside
simple, right? No thousands of layers, no...
simply two area, the inside is a domain
it's your domain code like
method like the train, the
reservationAttempt, the stuff like that
and the infrastructure code is at the
outside of your system. So this
is where you will find your favorite
HTTP stack,
your database drivers, your
message middleware, your favorite solution.
or whatever. This is
infrastructure side, code. which I've got
and what we want is to first
improve the domain code so we have
diversity she is some kind of putting
some  barriers around your domain code and
defining some entry points to enter and
to leave the the domain code. So you keep
the infrasturcture code at the other
side. This is a nice capability actually
because I don't know for you but when
you start your career as a developer you
need to improve your skills, you need to
discover new thing you need to do lot
of mistakes you need to implement you
own framework in order to realize
at one point that there are some silly
stuff like implementing your framework
stuff like that. But before you focus on
the domain really, it's still important
for some new young developers to be able
to play in a kind of playground. I'm
okay with that
as much as it does not jeopardize the
business value and the project and in
that case I'm happy with that because
there is a kind of location where you
can play. It's a playground your infrastructure
code. You can try new technology new
stuffs without jeopardizing
the domain code. So this is what I really
like in that pattern. So how does
it work, because there are barriers
but I need to enter and to leave the
building, I would say that, to leave the
domain code. So to do so in terms of
dependencies, all dependencies are
towards inside. believes the
infrastructure code is aware of
reference of domain code, but of course the
domain code should not be aware to any
framework. Even Jesus stuff. It seemed
like that so the domain is completely
independent from any kind of technology
even Json string or thing like that. So
to allow us to move from the
inside to the outside to ask new thing
to talk with external web api and do
some stuff, we will rely on ports and
adapters. And to do so we are actually
using
inversion dependency principle, so that
from the inside we can go outside and do
some stuff. Alistair Cockbrun recently
discussed with an another guy I can't
remember the name and that was
suggesting the name of configurable
dependencies. What Alistair was saying is
dependency injection principle I don't
really like because this is like if
negative way of formulating things. It's
you used to do that do the other way
around do the inverse so he was trying
to find a much more fluent intention way
of saying that, so they lead to
configurable dependencies so you plug
and unplug your dependencies around your main.
So if we get back to a case
here we say we have ports and adapter
to enter and to leave the domain. So
ports belongs to the domain and there
are some interfaces like lollipops here
so here I've got the IReserveSeats which
is the entry point from the
tata system. so I had through an
adapter HTTP adapter IP dot net callback
I must call an interface which is a port
I have another seat, say please reserve
me something and I get a
reservation and that adapter will do the
rotation between the reservation and the
Json version because the Json that so it
will be the proper location to do so
when I need to form a business rule
when I need some extra data some extra
thing if not provided by everything I
need from the beginning there are many
ways to do that but if let say I need to
ask one of the external
SSL dependency you know the three web
api we call during the process, we need
to access, we need to add something to
the outside, so to do so we asked some
ports also made from the inside there is
IBookSeats interface there is IProvideTrainTopology
interface and there is
IGetBookingRef interface. these
are domain interface
the port still
belongs to the domain reason why the
lollipop is in blue
but the adapter is what belongs to infrastructure
so basically adapter is something that
maps between the infrastructure code to
the domain one and vice-versa. Is that OK for
all of you? yeah? we'll see that in
the code in a few minutes. so port and
adapter to go in and to go out. easy, right? okay
but when we try to implement it the
first time there's tons of question that
arouse and there are many ways to
do so. We'll show you one. we have to
initialize we have to init to initiate
you are to build you
have to build the stuff so I like I've
got a metaphor which is a key ring
metaphor to explain that to my
mate I try to explain to you. First step,
its we will talk here about the
composition of utopian application, you
know, the place on your application
where you build all your dependencies
and then voila apply the system is able
to work and to do is work okay so we're
talking about the bootstrap of your
application here so three steps first
step is to instantiate I need to go out
adapters. All the adapters go to ask
to the SSL back-end "please give me a
topology please
so here represented twp Train Data Service Adapter
and Booking Reference Service Adapter
adapter these are like keys to go
outside and to ask stuff, so the first step
is access those keys. Then second step
is I've got those keys, I wrapped them
with
hexagon, with the domain. the hexagon is
where the domain stay so it's a web ticket manager.
So the web ticket manager
will receive within its console ports
interface to interact with the
outside world and then we instantiate we
wrapped the hexagon with a new
adapter which will be the adapter to be
used in order to
interact with our system so it's "I need to enter" adapters
that it's the way to
communicate with our application, but
once we do that all we have to keep in
our hand from an application perspective
from the asp.net Web API perspective all
I have to keep in my hand will be the entrypoint adapter
so all the rest of the hexagon
and adapters it's an implementation
details once I've built the place all I
have to keep from our Web API
perspective is that adapter which is the
entry point from a formal system. okay? to
put it differently those three steps
looking at them in the diagram. First we instantiate
the adapter we need to go out, so
the three back ends then we wrap
them with hexagon
whereas domain logic stands and then we
wrap that domain logic it's like Russian
doll you know I need to go out the hexagon I need to go in and at the end of
the day all you keep in your hands - I
need to go in. This is the only thing
that you need to interact with
system from application perspective
so all you keep in your line will be
only that adapter that you will inject
into your callback I speed up the
corners and stuff like that. okay? sure
you have some question we will call it
or hope you will have some questions. so
just to have a look on the new version
you can notice now we have a reservation
and the modification has been to call a
confirm because after this line I know
there is no exception and I can return
the reservation. so the did, the
modification of the test is there, yeah, we
returned a reservation and I already
create a beginning of adapter, the output
adapter with AdaptReservation.
This function will be called by Thomas in
a few minutes, so you start to move
the technical json implementation to the
proper place. exactly. okay. what I suggest
is to for me to to reduce in that first
acceptance test what I will have to do
into my bootstrap my composition route
okay, so first one is to step one is to
instantiate "I want to go out" adapter. so
here trainDataService for instance we
can even rename it to trainDataServicesAdapter.
it's a bad name, it's still the
service. that's obviously I was there
it's a proxy too. and same thing for
that bookingReferenceServiceAdapter. okay, step one I instantiate
the dependencies I need to go to the
outside world
yeah? all right, then what I need is to
instantiate the hexagon. actually so the
exact on here is a web ticket manager. so
let's call it hexagon only here for
pedagogical school perspective over your
life you don't you will call it with a
business name so please don't tell Eric
that we did that but just it's to focus
on the hexagon and infrastructure here.
it's better for me to rename it hexagon
here and then instead of
calling directly the hexagon
all I have said before is the
application we would have to interact
with my business logic through an
adapter yeah
so let's introduce it. yeah, step 3
instantiate "I want to go in" adaptor, so
here but I can do is to how can we
generation oh yeah you already
came same name, so I will
instantiate it providing what should I
provide. okay I think I got a sense like
Russian dolls so those two first we are
providing to the hexagon here and the
hexagon is provided to the
guy. okay so I create a constructor
because so far you just had made a
static functions. okay maybe you have to
make that abstraction
not to inject what ticket manager yes
actually yes you're right, we talked
about personnel at the ports are like
interfaces so what I can do maybe is on
the web ticket manager here it's
introducing its we changed after so
let's create an interface for that and
let's say I reserve seats, something like that? em...
Sorry, I used to work on the Mac,
so we try to pick a keyboard
IReserveSeats
you work every day on the PC
yes, but not the same keyboard  I tried to find
exeucise, stress yeah so I asked I add
the reserve method on that interface.
here this is a port this is a port in
order to enter the hexagon
so getting back to the code here
what I will provide to the external
adapter it will be the hexagon but as
oops, go to implementation as charlie
reserved seats yeah IReserveSeat.
okay let me keep it into a private field
here I will need it. so I start set a
reservation adapter okay so third step to
associate other nationality let's
introduce a variable for that with our
instance okay my idea will be to replace
the direct call to the hexagon by
something going through the adapter you
know. so just to make it compile I will
go to the controller to web controller
which is the place where I will use that
exact same adapter so in that controller
here I will need to my entry point will
be together reservation request dto so I
will get a reservation request dto
give it to the adapter and the adapter
will get back to me with a Json
relating to the reservation okay? so to
do so I think the reservation dto is not
in the proper place. I won't be able to
access it from the from the test. So
I suggest that we move that and maybe it
will be no envision is quite painful to
create project it's long so I will just
create a directory here. I will create
Train Train domain all right and
infra
so that we can start to split infra
(infrastructure) and so that we
can we are able to speak properly every
type into the proper location. I'd moved
typed into matching files for be sure
that every file match to type so
BookingReferenceService where should I put
domain or infra
service. it's a bad name, the
name will be different but yeah coach
domain yeah IBookingReferenceService
yeah it's an interface so it's a port
yeah actually here so domain yeah. IReservedSeats?
port, so the domain, yeah
ITrainDataservice, its names but
it's a domain is it okay its interface
yeah reservation domain, right?
reserved I shall attempt same
reservation hotel for you , same
reservationFailure also it's a
domain.
actually it's much more something to
implement the biggest law where there is
no added value more than twelve toppling
seats? domain. I'm kind of happy
because you have more domains than the
infrastructur which is not the case in
all my projects so far so SeatJsonPoco
SeatsReservationAdapter? infrastructure, yeah
ThreadsholdTrainCapacity? domain, absolutely even if we
came in through the name. Train? is it
domain and what do we have? TimeDataSservice,
of course which is another time
and WebTicketManager, domain. it's
all exactly but so far it's seen as some
to HTTP rationale that we get rid no
it's okay so let's put it to the... let's
keep it in the middle
let's keep it into the middle before we
completely clean the house and put it in
adjust the namespace
sorry I just enhancement yeah I would
adjust the namespace here for the project.
so that everyone would be at
the proper location okay. so what I was
saying is I will from the should TrainTrainShould
getting back to the test
okay
I said that I would like to introduce a
way to interact with the ReservationAdapter,
so let's say it's a Post dto.
there is a better name to
find but new reservation request
diffuses I don't know if you you move it
I don't know I didn't move thanks below
so ReservationRequestDto I
have to move is it's on the bad project.
move to folder... TrainTrain infra
so now I will be able to reference it
from the test, otherwise it will be part
of the Web API which has no reference so
far okay. so we here I will instantiate a
new reservation request dto. This is ASP.net
which used to instantiate
that for me but our number_of_seats here
will be seatsRequestedCount and
the other train_id
setting the
equivalent of the Json we receive as
the input
it's a poco for it will be
TraineId. here is my train
yeah okay so here I post a new
request dto, maybe this thing's, let's
make it a variable, to make it clean so I've
got a reservationRequestDto and then I
pass the reservation request to the adapter yeah,
I want to go into adapter. create method okay create the
method and instead of returning void I
will return maybe a string which will be
the Json. Here I can
return something much more like asp.net
internal structure to make a
response but I won't go into that here
but as I rationalize it you okay
so here I am in the posts method yeah
that should return me a jsonReservation.
something like that
why not
yeah so the adapter will return me that
and I will assert on that yeah so
instead of all that
jsonReservation should be equal to
that Json. that objective to target you
know that yeah so it's still right
because I didn't plug the adapter. so
adapter has three steps to
instantiate the entire hexagon structure
but when I mean every method of the
adapter has three steps basically its
first step is to adapt from their infrastructure
to the domain
second step is to call the business
logic and then the third step is to
adapt from domain answer to the
infrastructure and to return it. yeah you
know what is it about in every method of
adapter so let's make it here, in that
case I don't have to adapt
here so I will just introduce a new
variable
for the number_of_seats and with a
machine liquid in the real life
maybe you you have to serialize yourself
and we simulate this tech because asp.net
do that for us but sometimes
you have to translate the Json in
local variable for a domain object. so here
what I just did is to get some variables
but this is where you will have to
translate transform adjust whatever it
takes to be able to call the
domain logic. yeah Good. so now I call the
hexagon so hexagon.Reserve, it's
a business domain method and I put it
to put it local variable I get and numberOfSeats
number of let me call me
requested okay I called the hexagon,
its return me reservation, since it is a method a
yeah
so has a ration but since it's an async
method I will have to await that and
truth sorry some like that c# to
obtain the sequence call. but since your
method is I think because it's called
also async method I asked you to do so
and then adapt from domain to this is a
method Bruno already done we had adapter
adapter damage sure I provide a
reservation and I get some string and
yeah I guess, to return. you see I get a
reservation from the business logic and
then what I do is to adapt back from
the domain to the json infrastructure. this
is still red what did I miss
[Music]
you have to await also because
of a weight this is Mexican Russian okay
it's green sorry it was async/await
issue. that's time to implement in SSP
net. so here as you can see within one
acceptance test we have done what we
have to do is in composition note of the
application I don't know what you want
to do, well, we have less than 10 minutes
I think what that parts should be the one
that we will put into the setup of the
application so I can do that plug into
the webosphere but maybe it's better to
keep some time for questions or for kind
of wrap up, what do you think? okay
yeah otherwise I think I will have to
run because we kind of little bit late
yeah so wrap up, we started from
situation like this we have a web ticket
manager with a very procedural code do
this and after we lead to some more
consistent and more, I don't know what to
say, short working code also
after Reserve method was kind of something
like this. thing is yes pretty much what
we achieved what's important is that we
embrace the language of our domain
within our code plus legacy code very
crappy and when we if we had time to
executor and append
we will have less warnings we just you
know in second just just in front yeah
so we are talking
about reservations, trains reception
at term present which is fulfilled you
see so much, even if our domain experts
is not able to read our code we can read
in front of him and
being, yeah, being able to have a
discussion and he's being able to say no
no this is not what I want for that
system. so there is less
friction there is less gaps between what
we implemented what we was talking about.
so it's better if you want to follow him
yeah we had some called ndependent show it in
a few seconds, but just before that
yeah that's because it takes time to
switch as a final wrap-up we did not
have to time to to make you feel that
because automate expertise in Paris and
our first version was with him on stage
but it's crucial to talk to your domain
experts yeah most of the project has
issue because the developers are not even
allowed to talk to domain experts.
so for me so no it's a no-go I finish I
decide not to go to the project if it's
like this, but it wasn't the case at the
beginning of my career so takes yes it
takes courage time determination to
enforce that. but it's crucial otherwise
yeah not as if they don't buy the legacy
because I'm a coach and I learn how to
refactor the code generate people when
there is dependencies said my code is
not testable actually we can test any
code any code so don't be daunted by it
I guess you may have some gut to do so yeah it
cost I but it's doable yeah and also
it's we don't use a lot of techniques
here we basically use two basic
techniques from the refactoring book of
Martin Fowler
it's extract and move methods so it's
pretty much simple as soon as you have a
test Alice which is the first steps you
can extract and move very very easily
the more complicated is to find some
proper semantics and to and to invest in
your domain design they we have great
in track of improvement as you just said
by some of you. yes this is something
that is a living and ensuring you have
yeah you have been very interactive user
so thank you very much
[Applause]