Are you ready
Preparation for new Huawei Ascend g620s
Medical Centre the very beginning
Where's the time to put it into your project onto your phone
Yeah ok so you what you're not alone anymore
A lot of talk about the
The new day
And I tried to apply only go to college
Travelodge map
Absolutely solar system and we will talk like you talk about technical Patel
The most likely talking about ubiquitous for resin how to put the letters on Dominic's Perth Australia
Listen to York Road
Much more than footage equilateral We'll Talk lyrics
What is Betty's brother electrical
Lure fishing
Leicester 24/7
So I'm broken car I'm going from Paris and coach
And teaching to Nadine in the olden and
MMA in Southall
Bdd Meetup in Paris
De minimis website usage even on Twitter
I'm walking to present €18 um also korganizer of the Year Disney Paris meetup
I'm going to upset by yusuke season
Problem space
Good I think we drank too much too soon into the solution space for you
All I wanted Amazon stuff like that all Solutions
So this is one of my obsession
Ok get some gifts
For you
So we have to go
Dubai golf the rwandan
So to Windows books you will have to tweet as hell during the session
Using the estate DVD you thank you
We have a reference here
So you will have a look at that that starred in the most
Honeypreet or you can you can go to contact picture in candy jokes about ocelot you weather
Oliver and John will tell us the truth of the end of the session
Ornamental to Derby train
Tweenies Jennifer Love Actually so we will Focus more on the 6th of vanishing of the musician
Justin Trudeau
Here is a number train no train which has Three Gorges going to be in
Which has some
She's already reserved India Orange
Emphasis synonym white
In here we are asking 66
McGregor training routine simple model that helps to understand
Something ok
Lottery results for today for the system the first one is
You should not wish you not reserve more than 70% of the entire train to the village
Debenhams
Definition of Phil stroganoff all in the pickle middle schoolers
When I want to reserve I want all my sitting to the same coach
I don't want to speak to families and friends
Meeting coaches right
Super
We are taking vitamins from Emily Bosch 28i installation
And we put some crappy code on top of that but ok
Are there any Express couldn't manage to be with us in Amsterdam today but we talked a lot with him before
Princess mix
We talked a lot about rain
I talked about 20 or identifier in talked about 6
Coaches
Reservation accounts and whether or not
You know there was such a book
Booking reference where to find what is it
Representation revision filler
That's the world's from the northern with his world
Jennifer
Images
So we will work for a start-up company which name is Coco they provide
Set animation service which is better for you Wetherby
And this will apply to do his work he has to rely on
External accounts provided by external companies
So I invented SNCF
So the first making provided by agencies
This is external to our company it's a 10 letter
Medical issues
Canterbury Tales
Meaning we provide a train in Australia
When we get back the topology of the train meaning
All the coaches in for every coaches all the seats and for every six whether or not it's available
Already risen
Quantity
Single one is the booking reference in season 31 because not 21
How to get to Aberlady
On your train ticket this is Lady
12 week old
Book anything with that
All we can do is to get a unique ID in Australia
2 billion
In laws of Citizenship service on the list will have get it operations find available seats
Then
Getting a booking at yours we will actually book
The resolution
Through the national train operator service
Through the last train booking service
Write in terms of reaction of done streams we are at a tiny stuffed up in that
Open market that hasn't been opened recently so he knows the back-end provided by the national train departure
Is it ok for all of you
Wilkinson
Minion Willington doing all of the website
Context
2 seconds to
The switch
So
Are you supposed man
Well then you can see them
Call the web API
And we can see the body
The bell Old Windsor to Phil Trinity
Is there a Dunnes in Australia on a train
And the number of seats requested
Ok
So so she posted
Yeah that one
Takeaway
To Nottingham without them seeing dancer
Transfer
The first is a 1080
Ok
Sekonda Waddington playing with booking reference
Hello Kitty by the semi-automatic scriber for
And the list of soup
We get
Knitting back
So basically that's quite simple way to interact with our system
Absolute
Stoned
Citroen mobility
Basically we have a problem in this is really loud I hear today is it
Podcast after calls because they trace recruit spinners
Excess of opportunities by the National Trust
Why
Every call
You made on Lozells back-end duper she's so that means that stuff to talk or Stockton
Every time you call one of those web API is child from
Thought they were expecting
To do so badly
Think they are being too much
So they asked us to have a look at the code
Everything
What measures reasoning and continuous troubleshooting and fix
If you have something to fix
But not touching any record if you are Bruno and NI what would you recommend
Leicester news
Potassium sulfate
But in fact me this is real only miss the keynote February as a business that message this morning
Discovering the above the code in trying to highlight
Alderley the schools so we've met so far except instead
Just one smile is her happy birthday we have a train with only one touch
Extensive and we want it ok to reserve a train seat
An alligator is exactly what I do with postman
Simple octopus
Figure 1 is the
Yeah this is not a bit surprised that we can exchange at 70%
Unearthed reservation in all the train and we we we asked to sit and
You get already 6
Risotto
Because I apply the rule
So 7577 sitting exactly
Is this one
I digital I didn't add the booking reference to Centre
Analyst of the city centre
This is how to avoid telling us no
Riverside minmin
Ok
In the film test what does highlighting the all seats let me know send coach please
The single biggest troll
I need to change my phone we follow we follow because we asked
Here we have a sorry I train with two two cultures and one is almost full
Logo is completely free and when we asked to sit
I can't even get here one sitting coach a one sitting could be which was unexpected because
You don't want to speak Chinese in French
So we're thinking about that is annoying that
It's very spend something related to the sea
You have some ideas about what may extend the export
Cheese
Imagine new user
The website
Recording service
And you prepare a trip
Where's your family also
Girlfriend boyfriend
What happened
Yeah I'd like you to cancel
Brother I am not supposed to have to sit in two different questions about Council maybe we try it
Conservatory conservatory at the end of the day I will switch to another provider
I will left up up
Surprise fails
But the next time that because every time every attempt will be charged
So that was re protected
Who is disgusted with the Medics bathroom furniture
Maybe one so please
Yes can you please free download
So we are here till 6 and then all together and we will ask you to help us in the journey
So what would you recommend to fingerling
What would be your strategy
We are we are the tenderness Tenderness on the left on the Orange
We are only working on that circulation in €18
With all dependencies we don't have never done that
Nothing else now we completely overcome pain
We need some information from those two and we need to sit and talk or 72
Mix
Jamaica connection with that guy
So
He's ok looking Direction wheel
So hung tablet strategy would you recommend
Like that
No write a test
So I didn't we already wrote a test so that I like to do work so we'll have to think that test
Swanage diving to the Garda
Blowers
Set a breakpoint
Can call it
Is Snowden the movie
Run
So it's new if you
Just slide to the left side of the screen
It's a website it says it's a shock recorder to asp.net core API
Is simply for the undoing java spring boot starter simple for when we request that posted on that site
Razak name
We are yet. Call back
So are in each other
Just to have a look underneath your exactly
Absolutely
And so after all that Winston Churchill's you can fly to the left home yet thank you so will be associated
Webticketmanager which is supposed to be the entry point of the system and we call as well
Methyl oleate
Plain English energenie
Velocity Bristol
Ok so
This is what we have test so far
If we have a look at the tests and she's failing
Rotary test
United of acceptance tests we consider this term as a black box
Anyway send some a question with chickpea
Concerning diesel
The last one is attached to
The most read the problem ok
So what we wait we have to let his name and country every time we change the
Something we type something which is because it will run the test centre in background executive
Send providers in back to loop with a cut on a roof on the margins
Grace is fine and ready to serve
There's a problem if there is an arrow in in Red Bull history
Hello
Yeah I love your eyes
Residence the program we are expecting to have
Putting 1BU into me and actually we get
At 10:10 a.m. Wendy so this is me a big we discuss
Ok I will
I don't need to trim a good things to stop to have another view of what the weather messages is doing
I just had a cold for you
Let's have a Frost on holiday lets we discover that this morning so I will have a
A little bit more knowledge about it so I will try to help you to
To have another job
Trust me with a list of available seats.
The result of the other method
Then we call get train on a train data service
And we get something like to call hidden training I need to listen to put as you will see that
Then we used to set the trainer trainer stores London
Topology
It on the trailer starts we do some business rules period so heavy
If the number of seat already reserved in the train plus the number of Seaton requesting
Is below
Is zero something like get my prayers let me check
Show me solicitors or socialising
Ok
30% of 0
Overall 20%
Also if
I respect the first time in this whole continue
I got to do is number of cos I'm ok 0 seems to be an accumulator variable here
In winter heights to find some available seats
Another neighbour sits in the system is the one that's a booking ref is empty
We have our project and if it's empty string
Let me know since it is available
And then we can add it
Intravenous
When is the swimming return at the end of the method
Should I do it for you
Then we have a tariff stupid for insurances out in a cigarette
Oh then what do we have yes if we call
Find University question what we do we do when we get there so you know
Little that is saying that you can even call Brazil
Remember to Fillingham Reading
If it's worth that when we call the booking at 7 so he's the one in the middle on the right
In cold get booking a house
Then we
Assigns a booking a source to every one of the available see that we have found
So far
We are the best of accumulator on here
And then the Genesis
Pre medicine if you're not out in cinema now that's why I get it
Not reassemble
If it's still ok we go we use the cash basis
Yok
And then what we do we do we need to see the one that was making the booking and Rosie
Collection
It will be the external weather API with cold to touch it
If I
And after that
Let me check
Nearly intimidation
Chemistry colder weather piano
Real
Interesting.
Any free SIM card if you don't have any kind of exception here
What do we do with champions
Indian sarees London things on Easter seats
Whitworth Hall Hotel
And in the desert here what's in the desert
Message has been exceeded
Will return the empty you can fit everything in the trainer to fill up
Ok for everyone of you
Next perfume review while working on it.
Russell
Sinbad kebab.
Sofa
What are we string concatenate into president
Agencies local
Aberystwyth
Cellulose appendages only here in a middle of something that is expected to be some kind of
Minestrone
You don't even use GIFs in that Project
I can't do that
Yeah
Yeah absolutely yeah
That is a strategy we would say that I was with you I tried to discover
The domain expert
Gossip
Swiss Guard
Are you trying to figure out how can we improve that's because so far there's something that's really bother me
Writing about the Dublin
Expert
Voting results for Stones of concepts
Can you sing about the air trainer
Indigo centre Sydney train new cne
Other
Concept of the limit
There's something missing
Costco executive coaches company missing here
Nls
River restoration no resolution reservation at 10
Warranty expense gun lasers
In Australia
We are not allowed to wear off
Including it
Because
Since we don't have any tennis courts near
New Year cottages for large two finger burger would be true to make it
Amount
Menu for that it's been
There's so much crap in things like that
So let's clean
Ruskin College
Do you know the name kingswoodec
Refreshing to the right now
Kinderdijk
Is the first phases when you discover a cold
Because you need to be more coffee than before
To apply idp factoring
It's a way to discover 6
A little Wing
Name of the viable spies on tour
And after
Get into the proper way to improve our mental model
Between you don't come back from the beginning
Train to improve a little bit
Yeah but before that
1st April on 63
But you noticed something wrong with you.
It's rather
Is difficult to
The coffee that is like cold or is right because it's another
A mistake
I don't see the mistake I prefer things to see Green
Might also
You do that
Will it completely in your that tested it in the bag
It's a good technique
If you're in the same situation when this feeling
You need to recycle just before hitting the bag
You know that's destiny searching the baby
So that it's green you have a test harness to a factor and then you enable back
So
This is what
You're doing a white
Invoice meaning
Create
Current behavior
When your refactoring
Maintaining the current behaviour
So by creating a new test
Tesco current behaviour
Yes I like a lot which is a golden master
Columbus oh to take a legacy code
Ucluelet
Nuro to write acceptance test
Every time I send that important to the Legacy code and the newest ostriches I will walk
Rockingham
I must I'm expecting to see the same output
On both instances
So that result
Even understanding Gillingham
I can't have just done this
Making me and forcing me do I don't break any existing video
Thought this is a strategy that we could have done better here we are watching TV
Beautiful as an unexpected
So we stick to that event for an agency
Cliftons electrical
The Thunderball
There's no people
Have anybody
Sitar
I haven't just
Ivan Luca
Where is Susan from the user
So
Mimi
I can't decide to move this one
Gloucester V Juventus disease age
In the back of the room can you see all the code
I realise that this is running in real time I know I'm not breaking the computer
The the div are on the c programmer because I was asleep around IT support
Order my everything
At the right now so she's is yours
No it's ok take online it's called
Can't hear what the name
Cold War
Weather stripping new playlist
Italian wines list alphabetical
It's exactly the same number
But we have a hint. Unused may be here yeah
Another cell
Where can I do a smoothie to user
I Never Said
And apply
Contact at the end of the for each loop of council houses the same
Value as available soon as I can remember this file
Ok
True Love lyrics
Prince Harry do we have at the Metro arena
1 2
Two
Between a half hour to an hour
Find that's what another thing is doesn't mean she listens like that
Ok
Ok this is a cold for the trenches
Topology
Mediterranean
Ok
Lunch
Printability
I am trying to power on when you can a topology biology
Images of Adidas men guys ok
Temperature in Stoke
We have to do it expensive and then you say no I am not aware of any training to my dementia
Flybe train stops play New York Polish 39 minutes into train
What is Guy
Number of fatalities in Justice
Philips Hue 4 people in the back ok ok.
The north face helmet used
Visualizer better naturally
Whitney Houston
Fought for nothing and doesn't just in case the creation. Count is wrong maybe you can have her
I need a present perfect
Lol that's true try to understand this is just
Sinister
Ok so I can remove this file
Ok so you get realised
Gaydon Village
Yeah
No no no no
It's 6 I'm going to Chelsea to get it
I miss the 2000s set
We don't talk about set me ask me ask me locations so Solid we will settle
Never use
War of the sumac genus
Variables declared in the country not anymore
Legacy Cottage Fulham
Jealous
Stuff
NEC can I put it in your mind
This one
Have a look at this one we ever
Is here and we are all pretty much the same with the
Yeah I just
We like symmetry it's much better to tune a lot to compare stuff to do so he doesn't universe
Alton Towers offers and then
Ok we can sit and pretty much the same
I wouldn't Trust
Illustrated
As you can see there is a 1/8
Inverness the same here
So did you see there is nothing in the middle we can chat because into the earth below
And put it into the year and the end of the Justice
This one just had to respect her
So
Different simplifying in a business which you also
It's a really great and really ok so you can
Red
But white when I'm doing that because his wife in France while recording
Is that cover up
White
Manuka doctor
Interserve
Liquid Force response necessary to
Chessington really muscle lads
So I think we need
Girls from Space Odyssey
Ok
Ok for you
Close application.
With which other little did not
That's Amore that's really a different actor in the just to be more confident
The first round of Barcelona Gaudi
When improving on one time with them about it
And trying to clean up some some s