Are you ready
Preparation for new Huawei Ascend g620s
Medical Centre the very beginning
Where's the time to put it into your project onto your phone
Yeah ok so you what you're not alone anymore
A lot of talk about the
The new day
And I tried to apply only go to college
Travelodge map
Absolutely solar system and we will talk like you talk about technical Patel
The most likely talking about ubiquitous for resin how to put the letters on Dominic's Perth Australia
Listen to York Road
Much more than footage equilateral We'll Talk lyrics
What is Betty's brother electrical
Lure fishing
Leicester 24/7
So I'm broken car I'm going from Paris and coach
And teaching to Nadine in the olden and
MMA in Southall
Bdd Meetup in Paris
De minimis website usage even on Twitter
I'm walking to present €18 um also korganizer of the Year Disney Paris meetup
I'm going to upset by yusuke season
Problem space
Good I think we drank too much too soon into the solution space for you
All I wanted Amazon stuff like that all Solutions
So this is one of my obsession
Ok get some gifts
For you
So we have to go
Dubai golf the rwandan
So to Windows books you will have to tweet as hell during the session
Using the estate DVD you thank you
We have a reference here
So you will have a look at that that starred in the most
Honeypreet or you can you can go to contact picture in candy jokes about ocelot you weather
Oliver and John will tell us the truth of the end of the session
Ornamental to Derby train
Tweenies Jennifer Love Actually so we will Focus more on the 6th of vanishing of the musician
Justin Trudeau
Here is a number train no train which has Three Gorges going to be in
Which has some
She's already reserved India Orange
Emphasis synonym white
In here we are asking 66
McGregor training routine simple model that helps to understand
Something ok
Lottery results for today for the system the first one is
You should not wish you not reserve more than 70% of the entire train to the village
Debenhams
Definition of Phil stroganoff all in the pickle middle schoolers
When I want to reserve I want all my sitting to the same coach
I don't want to speak to families and friends
Meeting coaches right
Super
We are taking vitamins from Emily Bosch 28i installation
And we put some crappy code on top of that but ok
Are there any Express couldn't manage to be with us in Amsterdam today but we talked a lot with him before
Princess mix
We talked a lot about rain
I talked about 20 or identifier in talked about 6
Coaches
Reservation accounts and whether or not
You know there was such a book
Booking reference where to find what is it
Representation revision filler
That's the world's from the northern with his world
Jennifer
Images
So we will work for a start-up company which name is Coco they provide
Set animation service which is better for you Wetherby
And this will apply to do his work he has to rely on
External accounts provided by external companies
So I invented SNCF
So the first making provided by agencies
This is external to our company it's a 10 letter
Medical issues
Canterbury Tales
Meaning we provide a train in Australia
When we get back the topology of the train meaning
All the coaches in for every coaches all the seats and for every six whether or not it's available
Already risen
Quantity
Single one is the booking reference in season 31 because not 21
How to get to Aberlady
On your train ticket this is Lady
12 week old
Book anything with that
All we can do is to get a unique ID in Australia
2 billion
In laws of Citizenship service on the list will have get it operations find available seats
Then
Getting a booking at yours we will actually book
The resolution
Through the national train operator service
Through the last train booking service
Write in terms of reaction of done streams we are at a tiny stuffed up in that
Open market that hasn't been opened recently so he knows the back-end provided by the national train departure
Is it ok for all of you
Wilkinson
Minion Willington doing all of the website
Context
2 seconds to
The switch
So
Are you supposed man
Well then you can see them
Call the web API
And we can see the body
The bell Old Windsor to Phil Trinity
Is there a Dunnes in Australia on a train
And the number of seats requested
Ok
So so she posted
Yeah that one
Takeaway
To Nottingham without them seeing dancer
Transfer
The first is a 1080
Ok
Sekonda Waddington playing with booking reference
Hello Kitty by the semi-automatic scriber for
And the list of soup
We get
Knitting back
So basically that's quite simple way to interact with our system
Absolute
Stoned
Citroen mobility
Basically we have a problem in this is really loud I hear today is it
Podcast after calls because they trace recruit spinners
Excess of opportunities by the National Trust
Why
Every call
You made on Lozells back-end duper she's so that means that stuff to talk or Stockton
Every time you call one of those web API is child from
Thought they were expecting
To do so badly
Think they are being too much
So they asked us to have a look at the code
Everything
What measures reasoning and continuous troubleshooting and fix
If you have something to fix
But not touching any record if you are Bruno and NI what would you recommend
Leicester news
Potassium sulfate
But in fact me this is real only miss the keynote February as a business that message this morning
Discovering the above the code in trying to highlight
Alderley the schools so we've met so far except instead
Just one smile is her happy birthday we have a train with only one touch
Extensive and we want it ok to reserve a train seat
An alligator is exactly what I do with postman
Simple octopus
Figure 1 is the
Yeah this is not a bit surprised that we can exchange at 70%
Unearthed reservation in all the train and we we we asked to sit and
You get already 6
Risotto
Because I apply the rule
So 7577 sitting exactly
Is this one
I digital I didn't add the booking reference to Centre
Analyst of the city centre
This is how to avoid telling us no
Riverside minmin
Ok
In the film test what does highlighting the all seats let me know send coach please
The single biggest troll
I need to change my phone we follow we follow because we asked
Here we have a sorry I train with two two cultures and one is almost full
Logo is completely free and when we asked to sit
I can't even get here one sitting coach a one sitting could be which was unexpected because
You don't want to speak Chinese in French
So we're thinking about that is annoying that
It's very spend something related to the sea
You have some ideas about what may extend the export
Cheese
Imagine new user
The website
Recording service
And you prepare a trip
Where's your family also
Girlfriend boyfriend
What happened
Yeah I'd like you to cancel
Brother I am not supposed to have to sit in two different questions about Council maybe we try it
Conservatory conservatory at the end of the day I will switch to another provider
I will left up up
Surprise fails
But the next time that because every time every attempt will be charged
So that was re protected
Who is disgusted with the Medics bathroom furniture
Maybe one so please
Yes can you please free download
So we are here till 6 and then all together and we will ask you to help us in the journey
So what would you recommend to fingerling
What would be your strategy
We are we are the tenderness Tenderness on the left on the Orange
We are only working on that circulation in €18
With all dependencies we don't have never done that
Nothing else now we completely overcome pain
We need some information from those two and we need to sit and talk or 72
Mix
Jamaica connection with that guy
So
He's ok looking Direction wheel
So hung tablet strategy would you recommend
Like that
No write a test
So I didn't we already wrote a test so that I like to do work so we'll have to think that test
Swanage diving to the Garda
Blowers
Set a breakpoint
Can call it
Is Snowden the movie
Run
So it's new if you
Just slide to the left side of the screen
It's a website it says it's a shock recorder to asp.net core API
Is simply for the undoing java spring boot starter simple for when we request that posted on that site
Razak name
We are yet. Call back
So are in each other
Just to have a look underneath your exactly
Absolutely
And so after all that Winston Churchill's you can fly to the left home yet thank you so will be associated
Webticketmanager which is supposed to be the entry point of the system and we call as well
Methyl oleate
Plain English energenie
Velocity Bristol
Ok so
This is what we have test so far
If we have a look at the tests and she's failing
Rotary test
United of acceptance tests we consider this term as a black box
Anyway send some a question with chickpea
Concerning diesel
The last one is attached to
The most read the problem ok
So what we wait we have to let his name and country every time we change the
Something we type something which is because it will run the test centre in background executive
Send providers in back to loop with a cut on a roof on the margins
Grace is fine and ready to serve
There's a problem if there is an arrow in in Red Bull history
Hello
Yeah I love your eyes
Residence the program we are expecting to have
Putting 1BU into me and actually we get
At 10:10 a.m. Wendy so this is me a big we discuss
Ok I will
I don't need to trim a good things to stop to have another view of what the weather messages is doing
I just had a cold for you
Let's have a Frost on holiday lets we discover that this morning so I will have a
A little bit more knowledge about it so I will try to help you to
To have another job
Trust me with a list of available seats.
The result of the other method
Then we call get train on a train data service
And we get something like to call hidden training I need to listen to put as you will see that
Then we used to set the trainer trainer stores London
Topology
It on the trailer starts we do some business rules period so heavy
If the number of seat already reserved in the train plus the number of Seaton requesting
Is below
Is zero something like get my prayers let me check
Show me solicitors or socialising
Ok
30% of 0
Overall 20%
Also if
I respect the first time in this whole continue
I got to do is number of cos I'm ok 0 seems to be an accumulator variable here
In winter heights to find some available seats
Another neighbour sits in the system is the one that's a booking ref is empty
We have our project and if it's empty string
Let me know since it is available
And then we can add it
Intravenous
When is the swimming return at the end of the method
Should I do it for you
Then we have a tariff stupid for insurances out in a cigarette
Oh then what do we have yes if we call
Find University question what we do we do when we get there so you know
Little that is saying that you can even call Brazil
Remember to Fillingham Reading
If it's worth that when we call the booking at 7 so he's the one in the middle on the right
In cold get booking a house
Then we
Assigns a booking a source to every one of the available see that we have found
So far
We are the best of accumulator on here
And then the Genesis
Pre medicine if you're not out in cinema now that's why I get it
Not reassemble
If it's still ok we go we use the cash basis
Yok
And then what we do we do we need to see the one that was making the booking and Rosie
Collection
It will be the external weather API with cold to touch it
If I
And after that
Let me check
Nearly intimidation
Chemistry colder weather piano
Real
Interesting.
Any free SIM card if you don't have any kind of exception here
What do we do with champions
Indian sarees London things on Easter seats
Whitworth Hall Hotel
And in the desert here what's in the desert
Message has been exceeded
Will return the empty you can fit everything in the trainer to fill up
Ok for everyone of you
Next perfume review while working on it.
Russell
Sinbad kebab.
Sofa
What are we string concatenate into president
Agencies local
Aberystwyth
Cellulose appendages only here in a middle of something that is expected to be some kind of
Minestrone
You don't even use GIFs in that Project
I can't do that
Yeah
Yeah absolutely yeah
That is a strategy we would say that I was with you I tried to discover
The domain expert
Gossip
Swiss Guard
Are you trying to figure out how can we improve that's because so far there's something that's really bother me
Writing about the Dublin
Expert
Voting results for Stones of concepts
Can you sing about the air trainer
Indigo centre Sydney train new cne
Other
Concept of the limit
There's something missing
Costco executive coaches company missing here
Nls
River restoration no resolution reservation at 10
Warranty expense gun lasers
In Australia
We are not allowed to wear off
Including it
Because
Since we don't have any tennis courts near
New Year cottages for large two finger burger would be true to make it
Amount
Menu for that it's been
There's so much crap in things like that
So let's clean
Ruskin College
Do you know the name kingswoodec
Refreshing to the right now
Kinderdijk
Is the first phases when you discover a cold
Because you need to be more coffee than before
To apply idp factoring
It's a way to discover 6
A little Wing
Name of the viable spies on tour
And after
Get into the proper way to improve our mental model
Between you don't come back from the beginning
Train to improve a little bit
Yeah but before that
1st April on 63
But you noticed something wrong with you.
It's rather
Is difficult to
The coffee that is like cold or is right because it's another
A mistake
I don't see the mistake I prefer things to see Green
Might also
You do that
Will it completely in your that tested it in the bag
It's a good technique
If you're in the same situation when this feeling
You need to recycle just before hitting the bag
You know that's destiny searching the baby
So that it's green you have a test harness to a factor and then you enable back
So
This is what
You're doing a white
Invoice meaning
Create
Current behavior
When your refactoring
Maintaining the current behaviour
So by creating a new test
Tesco current behaviour
Yes I like a lot which is a golden master
Columbus oh to take a legacy code
Ucluelet
Nuro to write acceptance test
Every time I send that important to the Legacy code and the newest ostriches I will walk
Rockingham
I must I'm expecting to see the same output
On both instances
So that result
Even understanding Gillingham
I can't have just done this
Making me and forcing me do I don't break any existing video
Thought this is a strategy that we could have done better here we are watching TV
Beautiful as an unexpected
So we stick to that event for an agency
Cliftons electrical
The Thunderball
There's no people
Have anybody
Sitar
I haven't just
Ivan Luca
Where is Susan from the user
So
Mimi
I can't decide to move this one
Gloucester V Juventus disease age
In the back of the room can you see all the code
I realise that this is running in real time I know I'm not breaking the computer
The the div are on the c programmer because I was asleep around IT support
Order my everything
At the right now so she's is yours
No it's ok take online it's called
Can't hear what the name
Cold War
Weather stripping new playlist
Italian wines list alphabetical
It's exactly the same number
But we have a hint. Unused may be here yeah
Another cell
Where can I do a smoothie to user
I Never Said
And apply
Contact at the end of the for each loop of council houses the same
Value as available soon as I can remember this file
Ok
True Love lyrics
Prince Harry do we have at the Metro arena
1 2
Two
Between a half hour to an hour
Find that's what another thing is doesn't mean she listens like that
Ok
Ok this is a cold for the trenches
Topology
Mediterranean
Ok
Lunch
Printability
I am trying to power on when you can a topology biology
Images of Adidas men guys ok
Temperature in Stoke
We have to do it expensive and then you say no I am not aware of any training to my dementia
Flybe train stops play New York Polish 39 minutes into train
What is Guy
Number of fatalities in Justice
Philips Hue 4 people in the back ok ok.
The north face helmet used
Visualizer better naturally
Whitney Houston
Fought for nothing and doesn't just in case the creation. Count is wrong maybe you can have her
I need a present perfect
Lol that's true try to understand this is just
Sinister
Ok so I can remove this file
Ok so you get realised
Gaydon Village
Yeah
No no no no
It's 6 I'm going to Chelsea to get it
I miss the 2000s set
We don't talk about set me ask me ask me locations so Solid we will settle
Never use
War of the sumac genus
Variables declared in the country not anymore
Legacy Cottage Fulham
Jealous
Stuff
NEC can I put it in your mind
This one
Have a look at this one we ever
Is here and we are all pretty much the same with the
Yeah I just
We like symmetry it's much better to tune a lot to compare stuff to do so he doesn't universe
Alton Towers offers and then
Ok we can sit and pretty much the same
I wouldn't Trust
Illustrated
As you can see there is a 1/8
Inverness the same here
So did you see there is nothing in the middle we can chat because into the earth below
And put it into the year and the end of the Justice
This one just had to respect her
So
Different simplifying in a business which you also
It's a really great and really ok so you can
Red
But white when I'm doing that because his wife in France while recording
Is that cover up
White
Manuka doctor
Interserve
Liquid Force response necessary to
Chessington really muscle lads
So I think we need
Girls from Space Odyssey
Ok
Ok for you
Close application.
With which other little did not
That's Amore that's really a different actor in the just to be more confident
The first round of Barcelona Gaudi
When improving on one time with them about it
And trying to clean up some some s
Ok I'll something better you
Yep
Can you see what still bothering
Ok Tim very Potter joker one method
Justin Higham doing this and then doing that and then loses ok
Tennis predictions tips
Yeah but you begin the train doesn't is usually associated with
Cats
Brazilian
No that's the problem is we
Winston Churchill train at this one normally have to return a dummy
Another again autism
Mr. Attended any kind of plugs into our external weather API will making
Adaptor for England Porton Hotel Patiala Nashville
Have another of uniform that so not sure if you are not aware that but instead of returning
And a string of design let's make that
Method returning Elsa trainers
So that we can get rid of Jesus we did
To register more women in Trinidad and not missing technical staff music
Functionalism in Leominster
So I discovered that the file
There is a gospel tour of the train
The train ok we see a lot of stuff to this Eliza Jesus
Syrian adoption
This one is not
ASDA
So do that ok this one is never used to
Reds
Belated
Also this one is grey
You can speak into my S5 Mini
So here we are in the
Class
Yeah and contrast does not have tons of gfuel that would say except
My booking Aegean
Jigsaw
My genetics t-shirt
Ok
Support bacteria living alone.
Unable to swallow member of Amazon
Confusing ok and I'm always horny
So what do you mean
What would you suggest
If I drink
Should we tip
Dose of Murder locations to do some heat on passing but the train which
Battles of the meaning we should not do that here
Is that ok to do that I have to credit
Don't get too late because I want to move
Don't disagree with synonym
Politician when do that a lot during this time we will do it ok
I take all the colour I want
To remove extract
This one is ok
On that note
How much are
Your
One more ok this one
How to close the screen as very high
So excited listen from Dad's I need to do with Me instrumental
Adaptor
Sent apology
Because while passing the design.
Thing is
Setting some value to the property of the train
Leighton Hospital
Leg
So who is extracting into a new
Method
Furniture mover to move it's stupid change music
A good way to see if I have some dependency because that I want to move this one
But I don't want to add dependency from this one
I know I won't be to insulate
So
Are you static
Am I awesome quiz
Quizzes
Yeah and yeah because this is
Thanks that's where we tried to change the install second instance
Yeah so how can we how can we stop
Yeah Russian ship
Results
Yeah mate motion answers
Send an apology as an argument
Yeah that's a good idea but there is something I can do also it's so far
If a is not New Zealand then I increment the results it
Instead of
Changing that value of cos of sitcom.
But we may be able to
Causes of using the potty
And everytime I call the property new property is doing the computer desk so many one way of doing it
Something
Instead of
Lezyne v11 changing the value it will be something like
Set
Return on debt collection of sets so that as well not not at work on
Don't want
Not Nero auntie
Something like that
Result sorry sir cannot thank you for the match
Well for the last rooms
Isomorphic artificial Wales
Drilling waste collection Andrews email address
It so that's not this not
So here when I was writing something like I think the list of the seats and I can't everything's well that Lundy is very
Ring all's well
I don't have a booking at all times his father
So now you can get
Rid of that
Familiar
And this one
Maybe I can
Next
As you propose something similar
ASOS a list
What's an intro song that's made into a fashion I shouldn't because I
Statin function
So
I was still the oceans furniture
I like you
List
Antalya
I received a look-a-like about yesterday now
I return
Sorry, that message into a pension
So that's where we call it we get the results
Direction
So since we added strength ability
University because we have to move it
What's the population
What is the train is because it's because it's running yeah it's a matter of
Ok maybe just trying to message you make it
Perfect
Function so we can move it
Granny off internet
Let's put it it will get back to you I haven't eaten
Well it has been called
Yes
Here we have the train
So it may be interesting instead of having no didn't have energy to get the train to return on train
For men you can put that
Study functioning to the tenderness of his
So let's move
So you must be signed into the train
Weather.co.uk
So far we still have a crown dependency in the
In the train class between infinity Motorcycle
So you make it to open each user
Yes and
The goal is to change the Swan
Madrid train and get train at Everton this year show
2010 original itasca strings attached before it sank
Will requesting a weather API so it's a good offer
I should have died complexity matter
Ok what tree restaurants in Sweden train
Maria Bello
For the business not have to take the train or within subject
Ok so I'm trying to transform the topology
The trend on deserts of the British weather
So we call it that
Identification
But
Currently the train a dog
Received
Citizens Advice
Change that herself still have that lets accepting a list of s*** yeah so it was not the train we will accept it
Mushroom much more easy to
Cliff Richard to play with and remove this phone
So we don't have any kind of references from the train to when you can off
Trend of Us army soldier
So that's
So
No I can
Texas want to get train now is retiring at rentals
So you don't need that anymore
I don't know what is fun
In here
We have some ok but we ask the train we get
I compiled because maybe I ask Reading
Even if it doesn't add components to Green
Brewers compile yes this is we do not test vision Express Enfield
Worcestershire train from Avengers unforgiven topology and this is where we have to do the same way
Have to adjust
The prettiest girl
The prospecting tool
The song on YouTube please YouTube the new one
So
Should
While I'm singing
Ok
Does a foil I don't return back to
Lips
Rebecca was ok
So thank you for all your technical
That we are back of the train and we get put into a politician
Mrs bottles in hospital
So I'm much better
How much mortgage off tomorrow is that good that there's another thing that bother me
Find Stones Let's see the train ok you can you improve the situation but
Ok this is a train
What is it
To a better class result in each other videos
Nottingham Christmas to me and I'm not aware of maybe photo calendar to send once
Instead of object instead of a teenager object or child object
Yes to take responsibilities somehow
Nhgs
Torrentz2
Wrestlers who that's also we have a concept of Sin
Well then I'm trying to talk to you who's the name for that
Actually there is a name for that
Canada men
Travelodge Ilford
Anna Magdalena company and England
So
We are
Lacking
All the percentage of The Dimension of God when we have we have kind of any mixture pin data class
All of the angels in Easy
That's rhythm a Third Kind of collection 6 year
Harry Potter July doing all the magic
What I suggest
Surely it's too
Production Gear Jordan to put it in the population in Tritton Leicester or child objects
You can show something about MOT checker
Roman numerals
Athlone
YouTube
Just since we were doing a lot and it seems really what will we do we have a place
Has be classed as a Wimpy Kid furniture offers on the sofa instance and the Crosby's Alexa.
So what'll we do a lot it's to extract credit
Please type the behavior
Into a method so then you will have a method into the same type
And then we will move it into the population in the train France
At the end of the day would have more actually rating
New Balance
Let me switch back to the planet
Lottery
We will do that
Ok
This train reserve seats personal analysis the first Middle School attendance should not
Maximum capacity of the train
I suggested recycle message here
But maybe does not it does not exceed does not exceed
Overall
Friends episode in concert
Are you ok
Will that work
Depression
Diversity
I will make us a non static method and primaquine to be able to move it
Isn't it
So here I strike that two minutes with that method
Where should I
Move it
Going to
The training and everything
If I said
6 tomorrow
Azure Python passing arguments to an instance of an argument so you can easily move that day
Trainer has a train does not exceed over altering capacity
If I want to replace number of seats
Ok
Actually what we have here is available seats
Real building list of available seats at School of Massage Windsor
Final elements
Wynsors
Filezilla
Nonsense
Turn on statistics on solar movies
So here
If the train does not exceed if I request does not exceed the maximum capacity
Where to find sum of elements
Actually
They said that we may introduce here instead of that
When you finish
NBA profit
Just pretend
Allocation
A specification
Yes
Yeah except of course at the end of the day we will need to try 1800 Portsmouth
Before that's the don't expect was talking a lot about whether I should attend
Set a rear bottom cassette for fine
So I think it's so sweet
Instead of just dealing with available seats a list of Sith
There's a vendor distance of possession from that
But
Yes I sent you something
Original iPhone we are improving the colour blue are at something to to show you
Yeah maybe
Some people know in Japan
It's a tool to check the dependencies that it exists the architect for Java
Of C++
Navigational in your code and the Rising Sun
Warning forever and we were working with you thanks Mike I don't have anybody anyway
Ask him to introduce somewhere to check that turns photos into Cambridge
Author of the name Enterprise it's not a release and we tried to imagine imagine
Can you have a team you have a legacy card and you know the vocabulary of the next
Red Aurora
Scorpio card should rely on your ability language and we see we have some problem and
As you can see we have the list of program and the world not matching correctly
Letters of a gamma camera
We have to
Enter a list of words that are part of Oldham in Lancashire
Reclamation fruitfield
Manual and automatic
What is cheering alpha I think it would be an interesting way to make some
Forgot to issue a kind of smell about that
So Ryan's what was the results for the 3
Yeah I don't want to
Ok so let's get back to to the business we have a solicitor
Available seats
I think that we change that
Send signature on that by introducing the concept of inheritance
For here instead of returning a list of sets
Let's make a trip return reservation
Adult
I'm sorry I'm going to type all Heroes elation at them thank you
Ok
Ok the time doesn't exist so yes I'm aware of that maybe I will ring I need to answer that
Shiraz UK
Say sorry as I was July 10th where is it
Sorry
Yesterday night and I don't I don't think so let's Create it and enter
Three types of violation adult ok
Share
Since
The method is a function is expecting to it'll music and possession all I have to do
Is to install search here
Asian
Little and newer version attempts
Ok
Providing you
The list of sheets I just found
All I have to do is to create the conflict or accepting a list of Sith
Well that's what I said I don't ok
And that's it
Meditation intense I need to
I will need to drop in the sticks
So let me
Set of creating a few let me Create
Let's be real and that
Apprenticeships
National identity history
Maybe to produce a report that said because I will need
Rock with her the tips of that animation of dogs
Ok
So we just thinking to reservation account
Each other property assets
And that it's pretty much
So that the final elements it's now the name is
BBC weather
Any better yet
Fernando massages beautiful passionate earned it
Find a venomous it was in the train and return result shadow temple that
It's ok for everyone
So the card is not complaining anymore because I used to work with a list of seats
So what I need is to rename available to buy in Ashington
And then
Two
Adding directions to the city
Dental work with the list of numbers
Convert 3
Location
S12
Look suits
The squirrel in love
Rob Delaney
Fortran compiler Project
Ok it's compiling still win
For hear what I just did is to
Traits of a cancer directly come from the domain of havisham attempt and I
Replace a simple instruction by a mate
What can I do here I have a debit card
Yeah it's like saying
Doddle
The new film with talking a lot about that song
Let's create a method for that
A cut
Animals in
Fulfilled most complicated formula to find out in writing in English
Birthing kits
It's ok for that
So we asked
What is an isotope are you fulfilled so first X Factor
Cylinder under to gas and then to move it
I'm sorry
Today's weather
So I ate a cartoon of you and I put it into the politician which is awesome
The little something bother me because you passed twice
Citroen request agilitas
You better and if I can provide the 6th question Colts once when we construct
So that we don't need anymore to ask to provide it's every time we want to to check if it's Gucci wallet
Lisburn Auto Care degree go to implementation
Sequestered colds
I will provide it into the closet organisation attempts
Ok
Sorry I think I'm
I need a huge mistake
Up sorry
Ok
So I change the photo on the reservation account
Alton Tower, Cheltenham Hospital yes please sir
Regards
Italy coast to coast Newark what I can do is simply too cheaper
Arena mission meaning it's not finish it will be accessible through here
Outside world
388 in
No I had it
What I can do is to lay right on that
Instead of
The one that is provided
As arguments in the instruction
4 year
I replace it
The bomber dealt with in January I can get cigarettes
Define meta
Since I'm in the shop I can post your mates into property
Xbox One buddy
Ok
This one's that
No I think it's ok ok
So here getting back to the Institute
You said you see
I want to reserve massage I asked that has happened to me the other night then to the train
Albania on the train
Roulette
I just extract
The Mistletoe let's move it into the train
So now I can ask the train please try and give me your attention music
Number 68
Get off its food
Then I can continue
I can't continue to ASDA booking office and also looking at her she is not part of the domain you said always looking
So let's
Stickers of the mend Longridge
The Chase
And then what we do is to iterate or every citizen resolution attempt to assign materials
Maybe we can
Attack the messenger
And put it into the position and then directly which will be a sign
Booking reference
Which one video
Which was the
The devil's a dimension is that time of the minute we are signing with initials
Designer shirts ok
I tried to my son what will be the next
Stephanie
To move ya love to know that I don't
Ok
So we are seeing meteor showers 2010
If we look at the implementation just too funny to fail all we take that looking at house and sign it
To everyone of the seats
Of the multinationals
I was thinking the same thing as you and the Medics was really saying it
We build
The process is to build a reservation agent
And at the end of the day to transform it into hibernation
So yes but I wasn't saying that
Idea
Regression
Actually we thought it's like a technical team builder
Used to do it to use it in technical lead for the next concert
So we have a train station see what it may be sent to more and you haven't
Who is happy fashion within this application of the Year sequel
Yeah it's just everywhere let's see if it's irrelevant you ok
Rabbit
Decoration of the general manager
Then we used to set it into the hospital so intricate Benidorm
Then we clear it interesting
Weekly rates and an unconscious changing the glow in the stretching mediatek Street II
Average average of two figures
Total to clear the cache I don't know what to debit
Ok I hope it's worth
And then we said
The book
English film Olsen the trainer Gok into into the dash
And then that's it
Is that so
Attach where we only save stuff
But think about the hour
Ivana
Windjammer correctly
It's a mistake
As we said before we completely older
Khomeini
So
Autocar venues self service
And why we cash
HR department waiting staff
It's a mistake
You can change it and say yes it says it's going to stupid
Think I would say
Miss Katrina Isabella switch up
I remove it here
Animals that swim of that sand
Hi
Nationbuilder
This is a discussion we we we may have with the National
Thisisnottingham
Recording before win because it's not the first time we run the session.
Yes you're over that this is something that we discussed
Technical details with saying that
Retained amores
Stuff that we get at that time is it correct
According to you
So yeah
So ok we
Directors lodge massage
We get a train then we asked to train
Alex
Overheard in the other twin capacity 3 ask princess yet
Adjustable bookcase remember that I should I dance then we check if it's fulfill that
Nicolas Marin
Outdoor Pursuits
The house in the 24th fences
Wrist tattoo next to the Limit
Then we Oscar booking assholes
Then we assign the booking office and then we booked the seats
And then we return the there isn't
I don't know phone you but now the Mercedes one screen hi
We are addressing a little bit more the concept of the domain and we
After the spreading the news goes into the popular location the Twin Towers Malaysia
The
The seats also
The resolution attempt also
Yes I return money
No what would you suggest because it's important to be time boxed
Haha because I mean you can improve god a lot
What time we have an objective
Celebrity brewers
How to fix a bag
Concept
Return Tesco
Yep absolutely no idea what you're saying that in you what weekend is to get rid of that synergies on here
Any set to return to Amazon
And then return
Itasca because I was on here so that December 3rd is purely Dublin
No strangers on inside a simply recharging the oven in stock
Will do that
Will do that in a bit
Before that we will like to introduce the missing concept
Because
When will be the weather for Sunday
The village Swansea
Train to Bicester Village from the coach perfect two
Order chicken thighs know that I've got
How to introduce the concept of coaching to know what will be your status
From the website
Hugo Webster
Best kinesiology is
Taken from the name of every city every citizen name including SA18 2ET
Airstream 8480 name of the coach
Where are cigarette out this city
Lyrics to the Good Ship
Absolutely
Do ladybirds how to introduce it
Right now
What will be over next move
Yeah ok yeah ok that's how it is and how to do that we stop by
When you see that struggle
Yeah
Why not memory starts with with a test
I feel it coming from the train we get
Check that the a train exposed
Cwtches fences
Because we've totally addictive
DDD
Anna
We want to
To create that planets are the train shoes
Russell time we don't we only have some acceptance tests
32 total system shows
Do they do that Siri test
I'm here with the Office 2010 I would say
It's a cartoon
How many commission Express Coaches something like that
Will we get a train
Ocean trench food Express Coaches
Everyone is fine because I don't know
Should expose questions
Coaches
So
VAT Dr automatic
Related to the kitchen you want first to fix
About
Veterinary cost money
Matthiasson inline to consolidate and it when you beautiful
Such as
We should not
Favourite coach more than 40%
Constance
Stuff like that so it we need the population through to make it
Should be
So Far Away lyrics
We need to go to play with the coach
We need to ask to ask a vet
Yes
If you want to keep it completely private implementation details for your capsulated rewards
Roundup
So just for
Southwark station because a user
A snake
Name because we
We use it in the Day start to market summer Street until the 24th of June at all
20 billion this morning it's who qualifies apology
And it's good to use because I know in this topology have to sit to coach
It was 10 today for Ascot
Send a result was is fun
Get value in your Tesco associated train yeah
Ok providing in the train
The list of saints adapted Comberton
Dublin
Ok
So let's check
Z
Train train departures
Yeah I'm sorry
L
I hate coaches that doesn't exist
We need to
A size of
True because you have two couches and a friend apology
And you can also check that every coach has 10 seats maybe
It is not because I think it would be like a dictionary for half hour break
Guche
That's it that's it's ok
Atherstone
Because I stay kosher
Ok just to
Just to make it explode what we have and we can return to college OK
So is that did you know it's something
Ok
So you said the dictionary
Name
Coach
Reading is Jet
The Samuel creator
Diaper
For coach
So here the train will have her
A list of coach
And no I can't
Tried as additionally.
From what time we want sex but it doesn't show your story which was it arranged a really nice area
What even better a concept
The dedicated type or not
Material would like to show you a lot of other stuff we want
€11 but
Tulip and stator
So here we had a cup of tea and will be
That'll do another list of citrus said that the name of the coach for Olympics
Information passed of the name of every city
So for every since we just have to check if there is a coach
With that name
Because she doesn't want us to go today
And if we don't have an entry in the dictionary yet from that
Coach name list
Added
Judiciary
Sorry
Yes we can use an inch yeah. Crayon sets for the beginning of vagaries on my professor show because I think
N
Evaluating your coach and your coach and providing in the name
So
Where to return every 5th of the trailer for every one of them
Add the running coach into the dictionary on the fly
Then we have to
At the seats
Sopers Lane
Frosted single step is to undercity into the coach
Good shares
Rs17 ok
Fitbit
Goodnight idiot
Antalis available
Recorded can you coach
Yes
Why not
Record
Add
Are you doing that for us to use for the conclusion for a person but you want to make it work and then we can in fact or something
It is correct not ok
No
Ok. Ok
I have to register first
Pedagogical questions year
I've got you under CTO
So
So I had to
As for the kind of list of
So you are
What glue do you use to make USB data switch for handling unit
Don't too much
A good nice place to to find unused assets I would say
Red
Nearest
Something about Amelia machine here.
I'll let you finish
I've got a cigarette
The Creator
Animal simulator
Best explicit
What's yours
Alton Towers
Mahir
Sunday Graham
I don't really like that channel
We
Add a section to a coach should we change the coach
Actually
If you have more time
There is something I would like to do
It's even to make it everything imageable
Because what we do is
Will you get me when was Elvis when was Theresa fancy to get a train to Perugia
Which is something that we don't own
It's coming from the outside world
We work on it
And I really don't want us to be tempted somehow to keep it in cash
Mila Kunis tribute
And I would like to offer the fact that's when we get to 24 AG it's your name it'll all I can do is to work with
To find some information on O2 bill that I shouldn't
But I don't want to blow my mates
Are you joining the team is starting
Total winter break start by introducing a cash and in the States where
I don't want
Talk to me
So if we had more time when I would like to do is to make your everything imitable the train will be meeting all the coaches will be
Mirror table and the seats also
Nnv only
Singer called me miserable which will be there other than I should attempt
If I was there I should have done which will be kind of entity that has a life cycle and he looked at me
But the time change around a lot of the time
At the end I will transform the other that I showed them to other version
Another machine will be visible to
Otherwise shown is Harrison we it's
The other question
303 Donegal sorted out
The back to the
Today outfit
What I would like to maybe to 21466 to use electrical equation of operation
It's ruining the clutch
We have a method which is at 6 ok I can ask it to a coach
But instead of meeting me the coaching Styles
Well I would like to stay for that guy too rich on me
The New Coach
Universal suffrage
Thought
I called my son absent on the coaching staff
All you can do is to return your Newell stores
With that sits involve
But without changing the view previous instance that when I called the assets
Lytham
So
The benefits is super story mutability for shopping
It's easier to move into new school County Council rates
You're the coach
10 by itself somehow
No method on the coach which I mean you will start off of a coach
For if I want to move that it's morning Janice the coach where related to a new type which is related to Annie
New directions to Sawtry.
If I run
Ok yeah
In any case it's important to discuss with in America
I'm still with us and we asked some questions
Citizenship
We we not a lot of stuff
Sorry there is lots of interesting or in your head
But yes you're right you should have some kind of discussion
But
Serious much more an implementation detail I would say
It's true or False the fact that I don't want to
Door instead of states relating to something that I don't
I'm not under
Author of the definition of the train I'm just a user
NN every time a request is it getting back to me
Get a snapshot walking to snapshots
Somalia Royal concept of the domain and then make a reservation
So
Yahtzee
Yes that's not a problem
Ok so many stone into instead of changing the culture
Crittall annual soft clutch
Makita drill finishing here
So I didn't say it doesn't mean he can think of which will only return and you
Kosher salt
Coach
Ok
Citroen
Quizlet
With a list
And you list
Pissed off
Maternity session is best, efficient of three hours we have made in Paris visit them in expressions
Spurs football was on yesterday
Show me how to fix a fight for for that short version of two hours
Meeting at swimming pool or whatever
So we can unfold define the coach seats at 1 Arena venue types
So we will
Going to that we up we will only make that culture internal audit
Medium
There's lots of things to me and I respect that
Surprised you Sinatra
Yes
Provider
The Business Show
Wing commander cincotta daughters before ok
So now I have to fix it
Serco
Yeah
Is it in good
Was doing that
Toilet many steps you know
You know you're sick of this course is good
So tempted to change rates and to sell
So did you will be to get the coach
To add assets
So
Twins new coach
New Coach Inn dentist all the New Coach
Fire burning to the dictionary
So and it's Cinderella here
But I guess that after saving that new God's value
Into the dictionary 20 Green again
Free
That's why
Inevitable
Yeah yeah
It was in the dust
Bene culture
Yeah
Unless you get back to the unit again
Oh yes this is history
Computer
Will do that because we would like to show you a picture
Yeah but the thing is that wasn't next point we have a train which has explosion Euston
Maternity clothes list of coach
Because it belongs to the coaches so what we should do is
Instead of adding duplicates collection on the train
The central driver projection
And the list of 64 the training as media
The prediction of all the 6th of every coach
AutoTrader
Electric mini something like that
Surbiton coaches
Effective records
And return the value
Sarah Kenny
Ever since
Rococo chocolates
I just see
Weather
How to list
Can you list
What is going to thank you again that is so we met up election
Sex
All the seats on every coach
And we return it at the Institute for the entire time
We have this one we don't need to sell it anymore because it will be
Get on me
Ok
We need we are the coach hire
Yeah it's good now
So maybe we can maybe we can see the burger
When do you think
Ok
Absolutely villages yes
Movie find available since all the need of them and I don't
Who's a good level
Because if we asked to the train level
There is no way of
Probably there is a way that is kind of crappy
Willetts delegated
To the to The Coach so I'm removing her
This one
So we only have a desk when you read and read
Riverford
So it's come back to the web to chat
And as you suggested
Mabiza
University in sharjah today
Twitter
Something new
Maybe we can change as I got a sunbed
Read text
Zaragoza date on the coach
Let's put darts
Musica fruiting 86
Adequately
So Far Away chords
Samuel has tumour descent English I would like to use this one
Stagecoach
Give me other nationality if you can
Ok
Regarding a reservation at 10
Reservation Hotel
Better resolution
Adele
Call
Absolutely lovely
Resolution attempt
Is Rochdale
Ok
Then return
Results Irish Lotto
If not we continue to be tourette's on the next coach asking the same thing as last week
As well I can swim good
Proventia so it would feel that
So
This one is actually the cold I would like to
Compliment in pierced ear
In
So let's create a method
Anuria lycopene best
Finger tendons
So justified
Screen printing we just visited by my doing that let me get a red green effect
Beautician at 10:10 the train level Bastille
Let some curly hair
So
Maisons what's on
Millionaire song Kelis
Where have you gone so let's replace it with an inquest
So take me please all Saints where booking list is empty
Is MGMT training
Does notoriety ok if you get a group rate
Send text to the number of
So here we are projecting your early stuff
Since
That are available and then we have a little sis and available seats and then we check
Dr frost free for whatever number we are and I will place this one does
Exactly the same as the voltage Shrewsbury Avenue from here
To provision just have to
When you have to register it
Tetras that get rid of all the things wild
Ok
Arima
Ok you're in love
Here
Mistake
Remit
Notify
So what we can do anything to attract mosquitoes
Rimowa domino your here one
Inshallah ok
Polimer news
The satanism should be
The neighbour
Since we are working on suits
Prostitute Cannock
And we will
Explosive method and then we will move it into the city and the City level
So
Movie
So here now it is you can zoom in the North West
Without the receipts and we take all the seats that are available
Can you take the softener down that's all we need it
We need it. We finish that on your further instructions
Forgotten
Fighting against Isis
Ok
We happy because then we could go back
Chicken burger you can often pruning delete them in the garden yet
Maybe we can have a
Tiny
Punto abarth Aggregates
Daughter just a tiny fight about aggregates aggregates a collection of objects without wanted to know why you tired
AstraZeneca Central Hall
Can you see somebody getting here
Train
Is Gorton aggregate
Why is that
And does not seem to know because aggregates in science
When do the schools need to 22222
Tamiya
Ed Sheeran the only running value for harvesting data training
The I lost I do I must not exceed 70% of the 20% meat
This is a museum Dundee
Coach Aggregates s202
When we discussed with the ministry after you told her that you wanted to have some new rules ready to the coach
So that's a good enough money for funeral so I must not be here
The giving diversity is going to change maternity
Leggetts voice maybe it's getting better
Something interesting
Train coaches and seatbelt devalue types here
As we discussed earlier
If you think about the way we interact with external backend
You're the kind of snapshots
Venice, moment of time
In we will rock on that Snapchat song
With a wall to keep it in cash we just want to rock with all those Aggregates
Francis
So24 that we can make it all when you type so I shouldn't International
That's what we did
So that means that some aggregates may be completely when you type so so
The train here
It's most of the cases leggings with each other
Do it was 11 days where we could have
Just exception
If you have a number you're just going to be interested because
Maternity orangutan letter in the longest run without me do that
Source of how we improved somehow the web ticket manager
And I had a little brother
Kristina Si
Fallout 4 interactive car there is a lot of finger sister now
I think we have gone off
Improve the little bit 61 screen hi it's using the world's of the domain was in the car
Don't recall lyrics Justin
Rifftrax and some of the other new we put it into the popular locations
But there is still something
Weather
Tomorrow started
The swap
This is that we have some Jesus
Booking design into the
The main method
Respiratory telescope strings is also ageism
What we would like to do here is to get rid of that designs train stuff
Attributed by your husband
That's all that's ok that my son will return a reservation
And then
On the positive side
We will transform the liberation into a diesel
Russian
If you have another term for wanting something that is on top of suggest
I will talk a little bit about that I'm sorry I will work on the card
Gaza
You don't seem that it will explain when we get back to the code
So who is the weather for today
Ok good
What is it going to hospital is it secure pattern made by Alistair Cockburn
I called him another day
And it has many benefits
Patel Natasha teacher 11
If an Oyster on breast change it was the first
Eyedea freestyle S2
Plug and unplug
External dependencies plugin and play store
Just talking about the weather system
Ableton tuner plug with many different standards as important many different
Ronaldo sock boots
Broadcast news to broadcast to TV to radio to whatever
So it was Israel and us to have a
Kenneth clean code inside and
Every changes in terms of 400 or way to interact with the system
Premier tournaments 2017 he knew you play your pregnant and you went back up again and that's it
Sorry it's come with us was introduced by that I didn't mind
That's when we think about it babe
I notice that we want to Foster on the domain to make some Cudmore
Volume dealers value inside
Power products
Doing good, technical stuff
I don't know for you but
Very long time I thought it was not even possible to popular speed between domain music and and technical one week
We tried many times.
Refers to lots and in since I discovered that that Patel
It's really nice way to inform that
I also do you want Foster 72 because everything is a pluggable which unlocked
Toaster input output of the systems
This week's inside in
So what you doing for Christmas morning how to put it on the mountain
How does it work
It was considering the world into
Different area
There is a inside and there is no type
Sybarite
No
So the lovely girls know something to area
The insiders of the main it showed unemployed like it I like the train station attendant
The stuff like that
Is it possible to code is at
The outside of show off your system
So this is where you will find your favourite HTTP start
No that his rivals your message oriented middleware every solution what it is it is in cottage cheese
And what we want is to Foster and to improve the Dominican
So we have
How do you know National Insurance sometimes about putting some bum boils around your bum and blood
N
Defining some entry points
29 to 20 centimetres
Funny clip
The Apostle shop good idea sign
Nice community actually because I don't know for you better when you start your stereos Liverpool
You need to improve your skin you need to discover new sink
Need to meet new lot of mistakes
Newton Village Hall Kinross unit
Ul.to to realise at one point that there are some serious stuff like influence you all time rock stuff like that
But before you focus on the on the Dunham really
Experian Boston for some new jungle ability to be able to
To play in the care of playground
I'm ok with that
As much as it does not geopandas
The biggest value in the project and in that case I'm happy with that because there is kind of
Location where you can play It's a playground South Hospital
Try new technology new stuff that are members of Japan is England
I really like you letter is a pattern
So how do you drop because they are ok but I need to
Dementia
To do so in terms of dependencies all dependencies afterwards inside
Leeds away restaurants
But of course I do we could not be aware that alright
Any homework
Avengers on stuff if you like that's all the domain is completely
Independent from any kind of technology even g-strings
So to do so tomorrow to S2
Wolf from the Inside to the outside to ask
New sing to talk with external web apis and do some stuff
We will rely on personalities
Lucifer
We actually use the dependency inversion principle
For that funding so we can go outside and do some stuff
How do you stop a building and recently his test results remember the name and that was
Suggesting the name of
Configurable dependencies
Weather is the worst thing is impossible possible I don't really like because this is like you
Negative way of formulating Sainsbury's
You used to do that
Do the other way round do the inverse
Sorry was trying to find them much more fluent intention way of saying that
So they lead us to a configurable dependencies
So you plug in and plug in your dependencies
Randy alderman
So if we get back to where we Ascend we have posted another talk to enter
I believe the video man
The box
Dirhams to the demand and there are some interfaces like a lollipop here
So here I've got sizes of Suits which is the entry point from the
From the clipper system
So I asked
Phone adaptor hdcp 2.2 asp.net call back
I must call an interface which is a but I forgot it
Naturism you remind me something
I got a reservation in that I have done will
Does irritation between resurrection and regional nationalism
So it's it would be the proper location to do so
Will I need to for my middle school when I need some extra data from EE starting if I have not provided
Maya everything I need from the beginning
There are many ways to do that but
Liberalism say I need to ask you one of the external essence of dependency
You know this via web API we called during the process
We need to accept we need to add something to the outside safe to do so
We asked some parts on Sunday closing time
There is a I book seats
The phrase there is a hypervisor time topology interface
EasyJet booking a source interface
Domain interface the Baskervilles to the domain
Reason why the lollipop in Zulu
But the Adidas is what spirit is in hospital
From anything you wanna do something that's Maps between The Fosters chocolate to the doorman one
Invasion Airsoft
Is the death of all of you
Where is the Latin word for dinner in a minute
So put another girl to go into god
Is it right
Ok but when we try to implement it the first time
Stunt of questions that
Rosin
How many ways to to to do so so will show you one
We have to initialise we are twin it to insulate
20 seater
When you had to build you up the Builder stuff
So I'd like to get a bit of forward to the children with their talk to him to send that to my mate
I tried to explain to you
Prostitutes will talk to you about the composition without your application you know
The place on the opportunity where you get all your dependencies
And then follow a player leave the system is able to work continues his way
So we're talking about.
OCI application
Sort three steps first step is to associate
I need to blow out adaptor
Was there a bus to go to ask to the attention back in please
Give me a topology please.
We are presented to candidates only say that I'm working at all services. I like cheese
To go outside in to ask stuff
Sofa
Purpose tour to St Austin's
Then second Step is
Another skin and wrap them with you if I could I drop them with the
Cinnamon
Medina swimming stuff so it's a way to get manager
So they went to get manager will receive we discuss with dodgy box
Interface to interact
Physics jet A1
And then
Will Associates
We're up the zygote
Whizzer a new adaptor which means Indian actor to be used in a document array into
Redirect miso system
Sweetie I need to go I need to enter data it's easier to communicate with your application
But what we do that or we have to keep your head from an application that picture
On the asp.net web API testing
All I have to keep in mind we're busy
Entrypoint editor
Took over the rest of the Year exactly one and and and adaptors
Its own implementation details what's a builder place
What I have to tip
For my web API pass between is that adaptor what is the entry point for my for my system
Ok
WD-40
The Three Steps looking at the diagram
Weight loss surgery. We need to go out
Sort of view for the three daggers
Then we wrap them with things are going well for Domino's extenze
And then we're up that's the main reason
It's like a Russian don't you know
I need to go out zigzagoon I need to go in
And at the end of the day only keeping your hands say I need to go in
This isn't the only thing that you need to interact with her
The system application test BT
Total entertainment will be only that other girl that you will
Inject into your call back service political 4 hours and stuff like that
Ok
Shut your dumb question
Will guided tour
Hope you will have some questions
Hello
Just to have a logo on the new version
You cannot test now we have a reservation
And the modification has been
Toubkal
Confirm because after this time
I know
Is there is no exception
And I can
Rittal
The resolution
Does the medication on the tester
Is there here with me returning reservation
N
I already cried the beginning of adaptor output adaptor
Wizard app reservation
This disk this function will be
Call
Vitamasque instrument used to move the technical issues in relation to the place exactly
Ok
What is the distance to for me to
Refusing rats first acceptance test
What I will have to do into Maya
Buttercup my Corporation Road ok
So first one is to step 1
List all instances I want to go out adaptor so here
Candida service
Princess we can even recording we know me to come dancing senator
Cabana service
Ze707 it's a proxy to
I'm sending for
That
Adaptor
Ok
Step one instance of the dependencies I need to go to the outside world
Then what I need is to associate
Zigzag
So the attack on here is a web ticket manager
So let's
College
Is it going to here for
Unusual business
Name so please don't tell Eric
Trinidad Express
Toffee TV
Weather for ME2 397 hair
And then instead of going directly the lagoon
All I said before is the application would have to interact with my biometrics
IPhone adaptor so let's introduce it
Supreme
Interested I want to go in adaptor so here
I can do is to what how can we then use it
Providing what should I provide
That sounds like Russian dolls
Those two fasts where providing two things are going here and eggs are going to provide into theatres in UK
Ok so I tried to go to talk because it's so far you just had men aesthetic
From chance ok
Maybe you have to make an attraction and not to inject the web
Ticket manager
Yes actually yes you're right we talked about boxing at the Fox I like interfaces
So what I can do
Maybe is on the web ticket manager here
This information can write and we will change after so let's create an interface for that
Adana CI
Arizer solo
No sorry
I
I used to work in the on the market so we tried to pick a team order to resolve action 600
Weather AccuWeather
Yes but never sent you one
I was asleep I tried to text using Google IP address
Yeah so I asked I had already told on that device
This is a box
This is a box in order to Enter the Dragon
So I'm getting back to the garden yet
Share
What I will provide to the external adaptor it will be the exam but as
Hobbs
Go to politician as a child of 6
I resisted.
Ok
Let me type it into a private folder here I will need it
So I started off as a fashion editor
Ok
Soap
Chillstep
Glyphosate 1127 for that
Biannual need to replace the direct call to zigzagoon
My something going through the adaptor you know
So just to make it compile I will go to the coffee off to work now
Machine the place where I will use that exact same adaptor
Find acoperire
I will need to
My entry point with me together with an Acer Liquid Z2
So I will get to this emotion because it's you
Lyrics to the ladder and the other will get back
Newsagent
Relating to the ocean
So do you so I think that I shall issue is not in the Pop-up Play off
I won't be able to elicit message from the from the desk so I think that maybe
Pencil Project
As long as so I was just created and directories here
Electrical conduit aluminum
Alright in consulate of hop
So that meeting
Stock to splits
Info
How to join party
We are able to speak properly every type into the population
Agitating to merchandise for
Be sure that every 5 much to type so looking at us
What is a schooner
What's the weather
Looking at someone's eyes
It's about men only the name will be different that
Porsche
Romania
Booking a civil service
Dementia
Sunderland
I suggested
Support
To Vauxhall
Domain name
Itrain data service
Alison Edwards into the mains ok
Shane Duffy
Animation
Damental rights
Same
Resolution of video
Something
Animation video also
I said it's much more something to implement a new digital age in there is no added value more than
Sips
The MegaMind
I'm cannot attend because you are more than ins on the prostitute machine undertakings all my projects
So far for 16 and 4
Supervision and after
Ella dearest Battleday
Stratagem
Somerton Festival 2015
Lemon for acne
If anything changes the name
Trailer
Is it the man
Top of the Pops
And what do we have candida summer's
Astrocenter
And went to get manager
Exercising
Read so Sally Skinner's son to St Peter shoulder to get
Lottery
You know it's ok so let's put into the
Best ticketing Limited
Oops sorry I don't know what I'm doing it into the middle before we completely clean the house
And put it into the living
I want some space here for this for the project
So that anyone with me
The puppet
Booty
So what I was saying is I will from the
Sugar
What are system issues
Getting back to the test
Ok
I said that I would like to introduce a way to interact with yellow eyeshadow
So let's
Offensive
It's a Boston jewellery made on M25
New is emotionally present
I don't know if you remove it
I don't know I didn't know
Thanks will also
Revolutionary questions you're here afternoon
Is it on the map Project
Muscle food
Tamilrockers
Next National Lottery draw
Ok
For now I will be able to see what it comes with it
Otherwise it will be baptism with API which has more
Restaurants Southall
So I wish you I will set a new reservation request need to know
This is expedited come up with us to install said that for me but
I will number 10 will be
Centre
Suits
Christian Coulson
And then the other trilogy
For here I'm sitting eating a lot of the season
Museum Ellesmere Port
Etobicoke foresight
Any 2010 in here
Ok so here
I bust a new requested to you
The nearest
This Makita liable to make it clear and 20th anniversary
Celebrity quiz UK
And then I puzzle international consultancy TV presenter
Be able to go in adaptor
Christmas holidays in the Sun
Instead of returning void I will return any string
Tunisia you don't know when
I don't hear it
Returns of the English more like asp.net internal structure to make a response but I won't go into that
Humid
Anniversary presents UK
So here I'm
In the bus
Smythson
Luxury Brittany by diesel
There is another version something like that
Why not
For the other two will you tell me that and I will accept them on that
Instead of all that
Should we call to that
Exacerbated
Yellowtail
So I don't I don't mind
Three Steps to install kodi on firestick
Then when I'm in every method of the other three stability
It's
Prostate is to edit forms are constituted Enderman
Single step is to call the military
And then the first step is to adopt Cumberland
Answer of putting password you want to return it
You know well what is a bottom entry method of had a total list
Making sure
In that case I don't have to adopt you so I will just introduce a new variable
For the number seats
Invitation Rayquaza in real life baby do you have to sterilise Your Say
Southend
Who is similar to step
Because ice. Is that far for us that sometimes you have to
Translate to German
In local variable
The domain object
So here what I just did this to get some diapers but this is where you will have to talk later.
Adjust whatever I text to O2
From here to prawns in the Midlands
So now I called her eggs are gone so he's going that says it's a business domain
I'm the Sword and I put it there
Turn a local variable that end in Dorset
Animosity call me requested
Anymore
I called the exact
It's a written resolution
Cirencester Patterdale Cross
Tyres on a Sunday
Cinta salah search method I will have to await
That's untrue sorry says some July
Simpsons of Mercedes SE
Because it's closer I sync my phone I have to do so and then adapt some of her
Hotels in Benalmadena
And you're a retard
NCIS origination comes a MiDAS music
And then
What I do is true
Adam Birch
Forms of dementia
Provision
Pathogen
Mrs still read what did I miss
Mercia
America
This is Michigan weather in Ashington
Sorry for the wait time 29th
In asp.net
Topsy Regency with one of the process we have done what we have to do is no completion notification
I don't know what you want to do
We have less than 10 minutes I think
What
That part should near the one that we will put into the set-up of the application so I can do that
Dragon tattoos on Weber spirit
Movie spirited to keep some time for questions or for killing rabbits for new thing ok
The weather today will have to run for the return
Uniplate
So
Robert
We started from situation like this we have a web ticket manager
Wizadora positive are good diseases that do that and then the Zen Den
And after all we need to some more
Golf courses Stanton Moor
I don't know what to say at the shops
Rockin concerts
After all the others are scared of something like this
Thing is
Yes pretty much what we had shaved
What's important that we Embrace the long weather for older men
Weed awkward
But we get so Good lyrics rapping
And when we if we had time to executor new panda will have less warnings
Control urinating
Just just informed you
So we are we will come down sticking back to the nations that trend was actually don't put all of this field
Musixmatch
UB40 that is not able to read our code we can read a code in front of him
Nbr yeah being able to have a discussion and he's
Amoxicillin is not what I want for fall for the system start stop
So there is less
Pretenders live gaps between between Plymouth and what she was talking about
Sides
Madonna if you want to follow him
We had some independent show it in a few seconds but just before that no longer
Listen because it takes time to switch
As a father Robin
We will have to 1:50 to make you feel that because all the racecourses in Paris and authorisation weather
Museum on stairs
But it's crucial to talk to your limit expect yet muscle project as it should because delivery note
Allowed to I want to talk to the next.
Performing to know it's a number I think she said not to go to the project if it's like this
But it wasn't looking at the beginning of a carrier so
Text yes it's Takes correct time determination to Twin Falls at
When is crucial otherwise
Who has India done by the Legacy
Because I'm a coach and I learn how to reflect all of the Godzilla people when there is
Dependencies said my code is not testable I surely we can test a nickel
Eniko
So
Don't be daunted by biggest
You may have some dust
Yeah and also do if we don't use a lot of techniques
We basically used to
Betting techniques from the refectory Newcastle knotting Ferrell
It's extracted move message so it's
Pretty Made Simple
As soon as you have a tetanus
Beautiful steps
You can apply to move
Very very easily
The more complicated is to find some
Popular Simon chicken in NN2
Interinvest new older men designer
Do we have greater impact of improvement
If you just send me some of you
Yes this is something that is only doing and I'm inserting
You have been very interesting with that so thank you very much