we will do that in a circle
but before that we would like to introduce the missing concept
because
when we enter BuildReservationAttempt here
we build it from the
train perspective and not from the coach perspective
we use orders with no notion of coach
So how to introduce the concept of coach according to you what will be yours
From the website
Hugo Webster
Best kinesiology is
Basiclly the topology is taken from the name of average everything name including a1 a2 a3 b4...
A is the name of the coach
it's an implict where I'll figure it out these seats belongs to the coach
Lyrics to the Good Ship
yeah absolutely..good idea
but how to introduce it
right now
what will be your next move?
yeah okay, but how to do that?
start by what you suggested if you have a keyboard
Yeah
Why not? But we will start with a widget test...absolutely...
from the train we will get ...
we will check that the a train exposed coaches
for instance
Because we totally addictive
TDD
And
we want you
To create so let's add a trend...should...fixture...
But so far we don't...we only have some  acceptance tests
32 total system should do
Do they do that do it so we have three tests
And it will be our first unit test I would say
It's a time? should
And maybe should expose coaches something like that?
So we get a train
so should trend show the expose coaches?
Everyone is fine because I don't know
Should expose coaches
....coaches
so...yeah...
he talked a lot about it...yeah...yeah...yeah
Actually here I had even in mind some new rules for the related to the coach even he first to fix by then
But
Because money
But he has some inline to consolidate and to a new business rules
Such as
We should not
Feed a coach more than 40%
for instance
and step like so it we need the population through to make it
So Far we need it
We need to play with the coach
We need to ask it...to ask it
that's yes
If you want to keep it completely private implementation details for your detail capsulated
we won't write that
So just for
some explanation because I use a
A snake
Name because we
We use it in the tests to mark some situations this is a tenth topology table
so he will probably have built a spawning...a way to qualify the topology
And it's good to use because I know in this topology
I have to coach and
Stand sit for each coach so it's the reason why I use this one
You in your test associated a train
Ok providing in the Train
The list of seats adapted from that train
topology
Ok
So let's check
train...coaches...
Yeah I'm sorry
And
I hate coaches but it doesn't exist at this time
We need to
A size of
two...because they have two coaches from the topology
And you can also check that every coach has 10 seats maybe
It is long because I think it to be like a dictionary for half hour break....coaches["A"], coaches["B"]
Coaches["A"]
the seats...dot seats
A size 10
Because every coach...ya
Ok just to
Just to make it expose what we	have with in trend topology...okay...
So it's start to generate something
Ok
So you said the dictionary
Name
Coach
doesn't exists yet
The same we will create
type
for Coach...Yeah I would create it because right time
So here the train will have
A list of coach
And now I can
start as a dictionary
If we have more time we won't expose it as a dictionary also we expose that a read-only dictionary
or even better a concept
The delegate type for that but
Since I would like to show you a lot of other stuff we want
right here but
To loop on the seats
So here in within the concept D I G would be
would be ok I've got a list of we said that the name of coach was an implict
information passed of the name of every seats
So for every seat we just have to check if there is a coach
With that name
Because seats has a capacity coach named
And if we don't have an entry in the dictionary yet from that
Coach name let's
add it
to the dictionary
Sorry
Yes we can use an link...yeah. you have a query on seats for the beginning of algorithm I prefer to show without thinking
And
by use to set a new coach...we also set a new coach...and providing info name...set the coach name maybe
So
we iterate on every seats of the trainer for every one of theme
we added the relating coach into the dictionary on the fly
Then we have to
add the seats
so...coach name
First step second step is to add the seat into the coach
......
......okay
seat dot coach name maybe
Goodnight idiot
I introduced available
we called it..can you coach?
Yes
Ok...why not
new coach
add...seat...
Are you doing that for to expose the kind of ? for a person but you want to make it work and then we can refactor something like that
It is correct not ok
No
Ok. Ok
actually you have to ......I have to instance at first
the coache is here
coach..coach....coach...and on that coach..you had the seats
So
So I had to
I suppose I have kind of list of seats
So you are
What glue do you use to make USB data switch for handling unit
we will need to make a coach
A nice place to to find our list of assets I would say
But
There is
something that bother me a little bit  in here. But
I'll let you finish
I've got to see greener
The greener
I see
just complain
What's yours
Alton Towers
Mahir
here...should be green
I don't really like that kind of
We
Add a seats to a coach...we change the coach
Actually
If you have more time
There is something I would like to do
It's even to make it everything immutable
Because what we do is
basically with when you reserve...we want to reserve	some seats, we get trand apology
Which is something that we don't own
It's coming from the outside world
We work on it
And I really don't want us to be tempted somehow to keep it in cash
because it will be stupid
And I would like to offer the fact that's when we get a trent apology it should be immutable all I can do is to work with
To find some information or to build reservation attempt
But I don't want to allow my mates
are new joiners in the team...it start
to...to...break that by introducing a cache and a state well
I don't want
to be
So if we had more time when I would like to do is to make your everything immutable, the train will be immutable,the coaches will be
immutable and the seats also
the only
things that will be mutable is the reservation attempt
you see the a formal reservation attempt which will be kind of entity that has a life cycle and $%^&?
But the time changed all over the time
At the end I will transform the reservation attemp to reservation
And the reseravation would be immutable
Otherwise shown is Harrison we it's
yeah, you have question?
Sorry?...Absolutely....is of reasoning....if we
get back to the
addseats
What would like is to maybe to one for sense it's to use what we call a closure of operation
its meaning the coach
We have a method which is addSeats so I can add seats for the coache
But instead of mutating me the coache installs
What we would like is to for that guy to reach on me
The New Coach
a new aston soccer coach
So
I called method...add seats on a coach
All it can do is to return your new sorts
With that seats involved
But without changing the previous instance here that when I call the addSeats
Listen
So
The benefits is the first time with ability	for of course or for passion but also reduce the grouping
It's easier to move to move code
Here the coach
stand by itself somehow
you know...method on the coach which are mean the source of coach
For if I want to move that it's more easy than if the coach where related to a new type which is releated to a new types and step like that
and step like that.
for everyone
Ok yeah
In any case it's important to discuss with theme
unfortunately we used to do that session with one domain expert
on stage with us
and we asked some questions since he's not here we know a lot of stuff
so there is a lot of implict you know in our head
But yes you're right you should have some kind of discussion
But
Here is much more an implementation detail I would say
It's to all folks the fact that I no want to talk any kind of
states relating to something that I don't
I'm not
owner of the topology of the train I'm just a user
and every time a request is it getting back to me
Get a snapshot walk over snapshots
through my concept of the man and then make a reservation
So
Yeah, absolutely
Ok I think maybe not pop up...okay, let's turn it to instead of changing the coach here
let's switch a new sort of instance
make it a coach of attention here
So I didn't seats it doesn't mutate the existing coach which will only return
a coach installs
Coach
Ok
with seat name
with what?
With a list
a new list?
yeah
Acutally session is best from a session of three hours we have made in Paris ^&*()?
expect outstage our left floor forward
I guess museum story with tons of stuff so
we had to pick a fight for that short version of two hours... there are many things that we may improve
So we can't fault that the coach ships a train seats our really value types
So we would
go into that we will only make that coach immutable
Maybe
There's lots of things to me to improve...and respect the
producing a sure
Yes
to avoid the
The big issue
to implement the same constructor as before ok
So now I have to fix it
the code
Yeah
we could existing code
was doing that
so maybe steps you know
you should call this..
So time to change it and to...so
So will be to get the coach
To add seats
So
through it...new coach
Yeah, new coach and then to stalk the new coach by
a ball into dictionary
So it's still red here?
But I guess that after saving that new coach value
Into the dictionary it will be green again
Fully?
That's right
Inevitable
Yeah yeah
It was in the test
and the coach
Yeah
Unless you get back to the unit test again
Oh yes you're right
completely
we will do that because we would like to show you a picture second architecture and lots of other stuff...but yes you're right...you're right
Yeah but absolutely that was next point actually we have a train which has
exposed a list of seats and trying to expose the list of coach
Because all seats belong to the coaches so what we should do is
Instead of adding duplicates collection on the train
instead to have a projection
And the list of seats for the train must be the
The projection of all the seats of every coach
of the train
so let's do that
select mini something like that
coaches
let's take every coach
And return the value
select many coach
dot seats
change to c
I just see
better
toList
newList
this kind of linked you again better so we met a projection
we take
All the seats on every coach
And we return it at the this that's it for the entire train
So we have this one? we don't need to set it anymore because it will be
a get on me
Ok
We need we have the coach...compiled
Yeah it's good now
So maybe we can maybe we can fix the bug
What do you think
Ok
Absolutely villages yes
idea is to move the findAvailableSeats or the buildReservationAttempt
to the coach level
Because if we asked to the train level
There is no way of
properly there is a way that kind of crappy
so let's delegated it
To the to The Coach so I'm removing
This one
So we only do this test it will be red and red
green step
So it's come back to the web ticket
and as you suggested
Maybe the
buildReservationAttempt is in charge to be verified
and to tweet
Something new
Maybe we can change the algorithm
but respect
so I go submit based on the coach
Let's put that
logic of looking at cheat sheets
at coach level
So Far Away every coach
So we will have you maybe the same thing build a reservation attempt...yeah...I would like to use this one
please coach
beat me build reservation attemp if you can
Ok
And returning you a reservcation attempt
ReservcationAttempt
Is reservationAttempt
Adele
And if...reservation attempt
IsFulfilled
Ok
Then return
reservationAttempt
If not, we continue to iterate it on the next coach ask to the same thing once we have
at least one coach
Proventia us its fulfill another reservation attempt we are happy with that
So
This one is actually the code I would like to
Compliment get pasted
In
So let's create a method
Okay, and I don't like copy and paste actually
but in that case it
So justified
it's green....so we just fix the bug by doing that...maybe you can a red green refactor
Something to refact buildReservationAttempt to the train level
we still...let some code
So
based on the  what's on 'what'
here we have some kind of
...copy code so let's replace it with a link you request
So take me please all seats where booking list is empty
is empty...string dot is null or empty
if we create a method of yeah...yeah...and
take this number of request
So here we are projecting a list of
Seats
That are available and then we have a list of seats and available seats and then we take
The first three four whatever number we asked and I replace this one...it does
Exactly the same thing of the foreach loop we have seats here
To prove it you just have to
you have to...just to...get all of them
I remove
Ok
Ok you remove it
Here
Oops
I made a mistake
Now it's ok
So what we can do maybe seems we try to missed up anything to attract mosquitoes
things so here is quite difficult with
Inshallah ok
The semester we should be
it's available
Since we are working on seats
so non-static public
And we will
extract method and then we will move it into the seats and the seats level
So
Move it
So here now if you can zoom on the link us with a request
light on the seats and we take all the seats that are available
And we take the first number that we need it
We need it. That's we introduced that eariler for the each fulfilled
for another I should attempt
to be able to say fulfilled obtain a good reservation it's design choice...yeah...
Ok
We happy because then we could go back
fix bug you can imporving a little bit in the garden....yeah...