instance find a vein bolts it's okay
non-static PP also remove it so here if
the trend does not exceed if I request
does not exceed the maximum trend
capacity we find some available seats
actually
there is some concept that we may
introduce here instead of that what do
you think a location a specification yes
[Music]
yeah certain coach at the end of the day
we need to have seats in a given coach
but before that the domain expert was
talking a lot about reservation attempts
it's a really important concept for him
so I suggest that we instead of just
dealing with available seats a list of
seats let's build an instance of
preservation attempt from that part
something yeah yeah good you know before
we are improving the code below as
something to show you
yeah maybe you some people know and
depend it's a tool to check the
parenthesis but it exists G architect
for Java or C++ basically an advanced
tools yes it's analyzing your code and
raising some warnings or mo and we were
working with ethics Macau etc in deeper
yeah and we asked him to introduce a way
to check that code base follow the
ubiquitous language for followed along
with the of the demand it's a prototype
is not a release and we try to imagine
imagine you you have a team you have a
legacy code and you know the vocabulary
of the domain expert and create a rule
it's called your code should rely on
your you basically language and we see
we have some problem and as you can see
we have the list of program and the
world not matching correctly irrevocable
the cap is there so we have to enter a
list of worlds that are part of our
domain yeah like train Cochise
a federation fulfilled etc currently we
have to define this list for each domain
you want and the tool we tried to check
that so it's still in alpha yeah but I
think it would be interesting where to
make some audit of some good is to is to
have a kind of code smell about that
okay okay so run it and what was the
result was a three yeah I I don't want
to actually okay so let's get back to to
the business we have some list of
available seats I suggest that we change
that you change the signature of that by
introducing the concept of reservation
attempt so here instead of returning a
list of seats let's make it return a
reservation attempt typo here the nation
at and thank you
okay yeah okay the type does not exist
so yes I'm aware of that maybe I will
rename it also but here as you can see
sorry I shouldn't wear did ya hear yes
the resurrection item type does not
exist yet so let's create it I'll tend
to create a presentation attempt okay
and here since the method is the
function is expecting to return me that
kind of reservation attempt all I have
to do is to install yet here at the end
return a new reservation attempt ok
providing it the list of seats I just
found all I have to do is to create the
constructor accepting a list of seats
for that reservation attempt ok and
that's it maybe return I shall attempt I
need to I will need to to walk with the
seats so let me start off creating a
field let me create now let's be real
and that it will be sits as a rational
attempt has a list of C and maybe to to
introduce a read property because I will
need to work with the the seats of that
reservation attempt okay so we just
introduced a reservation attempt which
has a property of seats and that's it
pretty much so that the fine available
seats now the name is maybe build
another Russian attempt would be better
yeah okay so now the method is built as
a Russian attempt its find available
seat within the Train and return a
resolution a talk with that it's okay
for everyone said okay yeah so the code
is not compiling anymore because I used
to work with the list of seats so what I
need is to rename available seat by
reservation turns first step and then to
add the in direction to the seats and to
work with the
the list of the weather of seeds of the
hydrogen atoms so just let me fill that
three location f12
oops got seeds left well okay that
should compile let me check
okay it's compiling is still green
so here what I just did is to create a
concept that is directly come from the
domain a reservation attempt and replace
a simple list or seat by a mate okay
what can I do here
reservation at tab that's it dot count
here it's like saying dot the
reservation attempt or easel reservation
attempt fulfilled the double experiment
talking a lot about that so let's create
a method for that extract and move
either fulfilled not complicated for me
to find out who writing in English okay
I think it's it's okay for that so we
asked the organization a table are you
fulfilled so first extract still on that
class and then to move it to the up
sorry
to the resurrection returned so I
extract to behavior and I put it into
the proper location which is as a
rational let something bother me because
you pass twice the seat
request kanji that is yeah you passed
there and pass you actually can provide
the seat requested code once when we
construct the resurrection attempt so
that we don't need anymore to ask to
provide it every time we want to to
check if it's fulfill a lot let's do
that okay I agree go to implementation
she requested counts I would provide it
into the constructor of the veneration
attempt here okay sorry I thinking I did
a huge mistake
so okay so I changed the constructor of
the reservation attempt I'll tend to add
parameter to the constructor yes please
sir do that and she requested code here
like what I can do is simply to keep a
read-only field meaning it's not public
it won't be accessible by the outside
world
freedom capsulated and now I had it what
I can do is to leverage on that instead
of the one that is provided as argument
in the each fulfill so here I replace it
the parameter with the internal field
and now can get safety nets this
parameter since I'm in c-sharp I can
transform it and to property expression
body okay let's let's move that now I
think it's okay okay so here getting
back to the each food fielder usage you
see I'm on a resume third I asked Reza
to build a reservation attempt to the
Train oh maybe you don't move on the
train
below that I shall attempt should be a
method from the Train so let's I just
extract the method first so let's move
it into the Train so now I can ask the
Train please train build me or as a
Russian attempt with that number of
seats I won't get a reservation attempt
and then if it's fulfilled then I can
continue I can continue to ask the
booking reference and also looking life
is not part of the domain he said always
booking reference yeah so let's stick to
the domain long edge in that case and
then what we do is to iterate on every
seats of the reservation attempt to
assign the booking levels yeah maybe we
can extract a method here and put it
into the resurrection attempt directly
which will be assigned booking reference
which one the which was the
the demo of the damage in the exact term
of the domain expert we assign a booking
ASEAN's
to someone I shall attempt ok I extract
the method what will be the next chain
stuff to do to move yeah move to the
other action attempt ok so we assign
booking a falls to the reservation
attempt ok if we look at the
implementation just two for you to
follow we take that booking a house and
assign it to every one of the seats of
the booking officials
ok I was thinking the same thing as you
and the domain expert was really saying
that we build we the process is to build
a reservation attempt and at the end of
the day to transform it into a
reservation so yes but I was the same
[Music]
idea yeah absolutely
good question actually we thought it's
like a technical term build you used to
do it to use it in technical but for the
domain expertise it was still a concept
of this realm so we have a train caching
save Wow well maybe it's time to morally
have a cache in this application within
this application on the yes you can yeah
- everywhere let's see if it's still
relevant here ok we have a declaration
of the cache here on what you get
manager then we associate it into the
constructor of the web ticket manager
then we clear it interesting we clear it
and crunch is changing the color in the
illustrating me that oh it takes 3
second average average of 2 second - -
to clear the cache I don't know what
it's there but ok I hope it was and then
we say yeah the book English fails and
the train I do care into into the cache
and then that's it it's just a so a
cache where we only save stuff
but think about our maybe it was a nap
tent unfinished that maybe that but even
now if we implement correctly it's a
mistake
as we said before we compete with all
the companion
so also company use of same service and
why we cash our topology American stuff
it's a mistake they can't change it
and so yes it's a it's kind of stupid
thing I would say let's get rid let's
burn that which up I remove it here I
remove that remove that and how it's
better I feel better now this is the
kind of discretion we may have with the
domain experts since it's not here we
call it before because it's not the
first time when you run that station but
yes I will be with that this is
something that we must discuss about the
strategy without talking about technical
details but saying that we can memorize
stuff that we get at that time is it
correct according to you so yeah so ok
we get back to the method we get a train
from 22 service then we have to train
our weeks of exceeded the over trial
capacity if we asked which it's yeah
if it's not the case we build a
reservation attempt yeah then we check
if it's fulfilled or not because we may
run out of seats I see the train is full
for instance or reached the next to the
limit then we ask booking a falls then
we assign the booking of a horse and
then we booked the seat and then we
return the the result I don't know for
you but now the method is one screen hi
we are embracing a little bit more the
concept of the domain
and we have kind of spreading the
behaviors into the proper location the
trend are some behavior the the seats
also the reservation attempt also yes we
can maybe now what would you suggest
because it's important to be time-boxed
so high because you can improve code a
lot but from some time we have an
objective so the objective below us is
to fix the bag to fix the bug yeah
concept yeah absolutely
you're right you are saying that you
what we can is to get rid of that CBG
zone here and it said to return to
travel as a national turn into a
reservation and then return a task of
preservation here so that has a method
is purely domain no string design inside
simply returning a reservation instance
we will do that we'll do that in a
circle but before that we will like to
introduce the missing concept because
when we build a reservation attempt here
we bill it from the Train perspective
and not from the coach perspective yeah
we use orders it is no notion of coach
okay so how to introduce the concept of
coach according to you what will be your
[Music]
basically the topology is taken from the
name of average every citizen name
including a 1 a 2 a 3 B 4 a is the name
of the coach it's a name of the coach
it's an implicit where I'll figure it
out these seats belongs to the coach
yeah absolutely yeah good idea but how
to introduce it right now what
we'll be over next move yeah okay yeah
okay
but how to do that how to do that we
start by what you suggest if you have
the keyboard yeah yeah why not but we
will start with widget test absolutely
yeah from from the train we will get we
will check that a train expose Cochise
for instance yeah for example so because
we totally addictive TDD and we want you
to create so let's add a trend should
yeah fixture go so far we don't we only
have some acceptance tests like it's a
system should do they do that do it so
we are three tests and here but it will
be our first unit test I would say it's
a should and maybe it would be should
expose Cochise something like that so we
get a train
so should trend show the expose coaches
yeah every much this one because I
attorney should expose Cochise yeah yeah
he talked a lot about it yeah yeah yeah
yeah actually yeah I had even in mind
some new rules for the related to the
coach he first us to fix that back but
when because money but he has some
inline to consolidate and to a new
business rules such as we should not
feed a coach more than 40 percents for
instance and stuff like that so it will
be the top allocation to to to make
so far we will need it we need to play
with the coach we need to ask to ask it
but yes if we want to keep it completely
private implementation details for your
capsulated we won't write that so just
for some explanation because I use a
snake name because we we use it in the
tests to mark some situations this is a
tenth apology dinner table yeah so he'll
probably have built a spawning yeah it's
a way to qualify the topology and it's
good to use because I know in this
topology I have to seat to coach and we
stand sit for each coach so the reason
why I use this one okay so you in your
test reassociate a train yeah okay
providing the train the list of seats
adapted from that train
topology okay so let's check that train
train the coaches yeah I'm sorry and I
hate coaches but does not exist at this
time we need to a size of true because
we have two coaches in the train
topology and you can also check that
every coach has ten seats maybe yeah
actually it won't be coaches I think it
would be like a dictionary for coach is
a coach is B okay okay I see coach a
that's it
not seats okay sorry a size 10 because I
stay every coach here
okay just to just to make it explore the
the what we have within the Trent
apology okay so it's time to generate
something yeah okay so you said the
dictionary we got first name
coach does not exist yet
the same you will create a type of for
coach yeah I would create because right
time
so here the train will have a list of
coach yeah and now I can start as a
dictionary but if you have more time we
won't expose it as a dictionary also we
expose that to read read only dictionary
or or even better a concept the
dedicated type for that but since we
would like to show you a lot of other
stuff we would rely here but to loop and
the sitter
so here in within the concept or dige it
would be okay I've got a list of we
said that the name of the coach was an
implicit information part of the name of
every six so for every six we just have
to check if there is a coach with that
name because seats has a capacity coach
named and if we don't have an entry in
the dictionary yet from that coach name
let's add it to the dictionary sorry yes
you can use a link you have a query on
sit for the beginning of the algorithm I
prefer to show without thinking ok and
by us to set a new coach a new coach we
also set a new coach and providing him
the name okay maybe so we iterate on
every seats of the trainer for every one
of them we
add the relating coach into the
dictionary on the fly then we have to
add the seats so which name okay okay
first step second step is to add the
city into the coach yeah just got choose
all right okay sit
coach Nate maybe yeah I introduced
available yeah we call it can you coach
no yes okay and new coach Adam sit are
you doing that for to expose the kind of
closure for a person but you want to
make it work and then we can refactor
something like that it's correct okay
okay okay okay
actually you have to associate oh yeah
okay I have to instance at first to
coach the coach is here yes oh yeah
coach Coach coach and on that coach you
had the seats I had to I suppose I kind
of list of sit so you are what blue is
doing is to make him else the data
structure and thing we will need to make
a coach a nice place to to find our list
of seats I would say but there is
something that bother me a little bit in
here but I'll let you finish
I've got to see greener I see just
complain I think it's not quite not okay
anymore so if you like that
oh yeah you have to expose sheets ah
yeah you're right
well sure yeah yeah yeah should be green
yeah it's okay
but it's really I don't really like that
kind of we add assets into a coach and
we change the coach actually if we have
more time there is something I would
like to do it's even to make it
everything immutable because what we do
is basically with when you reserve we
want to reserve some we get a Trent
apology which is something that we don't
own it's coming from the outside world
we walk on it and I really don't want us
to be tempted somehow to keep it in cash
because it will be stupid and I would
like to offer the fact that when we get
a Trent apology it should be immutable
all I can do is to work with to find
some information or to build a
reservation attempt but I don't want to
allow my mates or new joiners in the
team it start to to to break that by
introducing a cache and an estate where
I don't want to be so if we add more
time what I would like to do is to make
everything in the table the train will
be my table the coaches will be me table
and the seats also and and the only
thing that will be mutable which will be
the FSM I shall attempt you see a formal
direction a table which will be kind of
entity the thing that has a lifecycle