are you ready yeah okay first question
such question for you who already
experienced some difficulties to grasp
DDD concept at the very beginning while
it was the time to put it into your
project or into your code yeah okay so
you you're not alone and we yeah I have
to confess I have a sin problem I see a
lot of talk about DDD and I tried to
apply on legacy akhada
that's not no result why we imagine
cessation absolutely so the as this
camera here we will talk mostly talk
about tactical patterns and lost like he
talking about ubiquitous always and how
to put the long wave of your domain
expert of your business into your code
much more than strategical pattern we
will talk a little bit about it but it's
rather tactical yeah I wanted session
maybe before no no sorry
so I'm blue car I've come from Paris and
coach and teaching and I'm in charge of
BDD meetup in Paris okay my name is
tilapia use case driven on Twitter I'm
I'm working software since 18 euros and
I'm also Corgan either of the DDD Paris
meetup I'm kind of upset by use cases
and problem space because I think we
jump too much too soon into the solution
space we all our golden armors and stuff
like that our solutions so this is one
of my obsession okay we have some gifts
for you so we have two books two Bibles
the blue one and the one and refactoring
by Sola and voila
so to win those books you will have to
tweet as hell during this session using
the abstract DDD you you you thank you
we have a referee here so you will
have a look at that as tagging the most
funny tweet or you can you can quote you
can take picture you can do jokes about
us about you whatever and Jerome will
tell us the two winners at the end of
the shell session all right okay fine
cool all the other men for today will be
trained trainees kind of labs actually
so we will focus more on the city
Federation optimization yeah just in
front here it's the model of a train a
train which has three coaches coach a
could be in coach C which has some seats
already reserved in the orange empty
seats in in in white and here we are
asking six seats to be reserving the
Train in blue this is a simple model but
that may helps to illustrate some
something okay we have two business rule
for today for the system the first one
is you should not we should not with
there more than 70% of the entire
training capability capacity okay so
this is the first rule business rule and
the second business rule is when I want
to reserve I want all my city into the
same coach I don't we we don't want to
split families and friends between
coaches right simple we taking the rule
from amid abashed rank at our
reservation and we put some crappy code
on top of that but okay our domain
expert could have managed to be with us
in Amsterdam today but we talked a lot
with him before previous weeks so he
talked a lot about train I talked about
train IG or identifier it talks about
seats coach's reservation attempts and
whether or not they are not automation
attempt is fulfilled and you know they
also can we find to book working affair
as we explain what is it reservation
reservation failure that's a world from
the yeah you know the session we have
with it those words were the kind of
ubiquitous
so we will work for a startup company
which name is Tata
they provide the reservation service
which is basically a web api and this
will apply to do its work he has to rely
on external backends provided by
external companies so in front it's SNCF
so the first back-end provided by SMSF
which is external to our company it's a
trend data basically it's a hand
topology service meaning we we provide a
trend in Australia and we get back the
topology of the trend meaning the all
the coaches and for every coaches all
the seats and for every seat whether or
not it's available or already reserved
ok quite easy second one is the booking
reference physical kind of tricky one
because not working with when you buy a
ticket you have an ID on your train
ticket this Israeli actually yeah but
this is a service that only provides a
unique identifier so we can't booked
anything with that all we can do is to
get unique identifiers to play with and
once our seat reservation service on the
Left we'll have get a topology find
available seats then getting a booking
reference we actually booked the
reservation
through the National Train appellate of
service through that last train booking
sighs all right in terms of we are kind
of done streams we are a tiny startup in
that open market that has been opened
recently so these are the the back-end
provided by the National Train operator
is it ok for all of you yeah we will
continue maybe a balloon can do a demo
of the Web API so it will takes few
seconds to to switch
yeah ok so I use postman
where you can see the URL to call the
API and we can see the body the payload
with to fail to an ID
is a the notifier of the Train and the
number of teeth requested okay so if you
post yeah that one take a while yeah we
have some same an answer
transfer the first is a train ID okay
second one is a famous booking reference
I located by the serving as Tom I
described before and the list of sit we
get in back okay so basically that's
quite simple way to interact with our
system yes that's okay
basically we have a problem and this is
really why we are here today at startup
call us because they face rechromed
penalties exist excess of penalties by
europe national trainer patents is why
every call you met on all those back
ends you pages so that means that
started crossed our top every time you
call one of those where the pie is
charged from fees so they were expected
to do so but the thing they are paying
too much so they asked us to have a look
at the code and to see what may be the
reason and can can we troubleshoot and
fix if you have something to fix okay
but before touching any legacy code if
you are like Bruno and and I what would
you recommend us to do that test yeah
absolutely
in fact we this is really one we missed
the keynote we have built test arrest
this morning
discovering the the code and trying to
highlights all those business rules so
we've made so far three acceptance tests
first one first one is a happy pasta we
have a trend with only one coach we
stand sit and we
allocate a reserve twisted and as you
can see exactly what I do with postman
yeah and it is exactly the same answer
okay
simple IP pass okay second one is the
yeah this is the first business rule we
can exceed 70 percent for reservation in
all the Train and we if we ask to sit
and you can see I already six C reserved
yeah and because I applies the rule so
70 percent seven seeing exactly transit
the way to response an arrow is this one
I get that will ID but the booking
reference is empty and the list of the
city's empty this is how transfer is
telling us no reservation has been made
for you okay and the third test was test
highlighting the old seat must be in the
same coach please the second business
rule and in that case we found we
followed bag we found about because we
asked here we have a sorry a train with
two two coaches and one is almost full
the other is completely free and when we
ask two seats actually we get here one
seat in coach a one sitting could be
which was unexpected because we don't
want to split families and friends so we
are thinking about that is we know we
were saying that it's may explain some
things related to the field you have
some ideas about what may explain the
extra fees
imagine you use the website you call the
service and you prepare a trip with your
family or your girlfriend boyfriend
what's happen exactly it's to to counsel
because I'm not pleased to have two
seats in two different countries or
Council maybe we try it concern retry
consul retire at the end of the day I
will
which switch to another provider we left
control poor experience but that may
explain that because every time every
attempt will be charged actually so that
was our epithet ease and we discussed it
with Dominic's path through foreign aid
say yeah that might be the one so please
guys can you please fix that bugger so
we are here to fix that back
altogether and we will ask you to help
us in that journey so what would you
recommend to fix that back what would be
your strategy yeah sorry we are we are
the ten data service 20 Direction
service on the left on your range yeah
okay we are only working on that seat
reservation in in yellow these are
dependencies we don't have leverage on
that actually yeah not only consumers
now will complete with all the companion
we all start up and we compete with
other we need some information from
those two and we need to set and to
confirm and to book to make a
transaction with that guy so is that a
kind of interaction we have so in terms
of strategy what will you recommend
right test yeah right to test so
actually we already wrote a test so that
highlighted the bug so we'll have to fix
that test actually okay so let's dive
into the code yeah you know what set a
breakpoint you can call it yeah that's
okay asking me it's lunch in the bug mud
so here if you just to the side of the
screen it's a web it says AC sharp code
it's a high-speed Metco API it's simply
father doing Java spring boots it's tied
so simply for when we request that post
on that so sauce with that name we get
that callback
so and it's an emotional question we
receive just to have a look under the
TiVo is very simple exactly the payload
or the design absolutely and so after
that we instance yet you can slide to
the left so yeah thank you
so we associate a web ticket manager
which is seems to be the entry point of
the system and we call herself method on
it providing the energy you know the
bonus it's requested okay so this is
what we have test so far if we have a
look at the test that is failing our
three test is I kind of acceptance test
we consider the system as a black box
and we send so my quest and we checked
it done syringes on the last one is the
test demonstrate the program okay so
what we why we have a tool that is named
and crunch we see every time we changed
something we type something we change
the code it will run the test in in
background execute it and provide us a
feedback loop with a colored arrow on
the margins or greens is fine and ready
either there's a problem and there is an
arrow in in red below you you know yeah
a lot of you of the arrow is basically
it's the problem we were expecting to
have to sit in one Bo and to be and
actually we get 10 I 10 a and 1 B so
this is the bug we discussed earlier
okay okay all right well I think it
would be a good things to stuff to have
another view of what the hell method is
is doing oh yeah I just aligned the code
okay for you let's have a first author
of you let's we discover that this
morning so we have a little bit much
more knowledge about it so I will try to
help you to to have another view first
we
we associate a list of available seats
that should be probably the ritual of
the of the method then we call a get
trained on a trend at a service and we
get something like we call G's entrain I
need so G's on topology you will see
that yeah then we associate the Train a
trainer stalls from that design topology
and on that trailer stalls we do some
business rules here and there so here we
if the number of seats already reserved
in the Train plus number of sittin being
requesting is below is below something
like get max raise let me check should
be some percentage or something like
that
celebration yeah okay so eighty percent
of the overall trend capacity so if I
respect the the first business rule I'm
continue I continue is a number of K
over K 0 seems to be an accumulative
viable here and we tried to find some
available seats unavailable sits in that
system is the one that a booking life is
empty we have a property and if it's
empty string that means that the seat is
available and then we can add it into
the list beliefs that we will return at
the end of the of the method still ok
for you so far ok then we have a kind of
stupid for which we will see that in a
second then what do we have
yes if we can't find the number of seats
requested but we do we do we get the
answer you know the the answer that is
saying that you can even count reserved
for another spelling around so failing
methods if it work that when we call the
booking FF series 3-1 in the middle on
the right side and called get booking
reference then we assign that booking
reference to every one of the available
see that we have found so far we had a
bunch of accumulator here and then again
it's pretty much the same if if you look
at me right
you know now yeah first one is not
really insane but if it's still okay we
owe we use a cash yeah thirsting see
that why okay and then what we do we do
we actually this is the one that that is
making the booking I know tours i
transaction actually it will be the
external web app I would call through to
book a seat if I enter to that
let me check here the implementation
Emily we call a web app I know plenty is
on to call the web app yeah no real
interest in that and if we assume that
if we don't have any kind of exception
here what do we do we jump the answer
and the answer is the one dumping the
least receipts we were found so far okay
and in the case here what in the case
yes in the case of the trunk capacity
limit as X C has been exceeded we return
the empty
you can't reserve anything in that
trailer at the fella okay for every one
of you we will make a few review while
working on it but do you have some
feedback about that so far what are we
string concatenating to create didn't we
actually this is not awkward as a
disclaimer this is the car we discovered
this morning so yes but this is a good
remark why do we say allies attendees on
here in the middle of something that is
expected to be some kind of business
knowledge yeah sorry
[Laughter]
they don't know they don't even use
gates in that project in you know I
can't do that
yeah yeah yeah you're right yeah
absolutely
yeah that is a strategy we will try to
apply with with you we try to discover
the domain expert concept it's for this
card we try to figure out how can we
improve that because so far there is
something that's really bother me we
were talking about the domain expert
talking with us with terms of concepts
can you see about the Train and the
concept of seat do you Trina
do you see any other concept of the
domain there is something missing coach
coach the concept of coach is completely
missing here and and other stuff
reservation the reservation no
reservation no reservation no
reservation attempt so far so who
already expense code like this in this
carrier has yeah so we are not alone so
the ID here for us will be to have a
kind of way of improving it because
since we don't have any kind of coach
here the strategy for us to fix the bug
would be to make it MLG but before that
it still there is so much crappy thing
in like that so let's clean first came
the deck yeah do you know the name
cleans the deck the expression clean the
deck now clean the deck is the first
phase when you discover a code you
because you need to be more confident
before to apply a deep refactoring it's
a way to discover fix a little name of
the variables for example and after get
into the program it's a way to prepare a
mental model yeah you know heads from
the SCOTUS with
so come back from the beginning
Sookie near the deck you will have
another of you but trying to improve a
little bit yep
but before that is about that yeah well
typhoon 63 yeah yes for sure it's a
really early Jessica but you notice
something wrong with that yeah it's red
it's difficult to be confident if my
color is right because if I measure a
mistake I don't see the mistake I prefer
to see green light oh so to do that
we'll completely in do the test to the
strip in the burgh yeah it's a good
technique if you are in the same
situation why the test failing and you
need to you know so yeah there's a
technique that I like a lot which is a
golden master kundo master is you take a
legacy code you clone it and you wrote
you write acceptance test every time I
send that input into the legacy code and
the new instance which one I will
working on I must I'm expecting to see
the same output on both instances so
that without even understanding the
legacy I can't have a test unless
making me and forcing me I don't break
any existing behavior so this is a
strategy that we could have done but
here we are implementing the business
rule as the domain expert told us so we
will stick to that point for now but yes
it's a good amount so good so let's give
the decks below yes the first variable
this is notable everybody Sita I would
just have a look where it's using stuff
from the user so maybe I can decide to
move this one close to the user goes to
the usage yeah for example in the
backups room can you see all the code
every time I test is running in real
time I know I'm not breaking the code
still green
the div are of a C programmer because I
was a C programmer it was to put all the
way about as we know but right now so
this is your now it's not like okay
second one is called count what the name
yeah yeah count
wow what a stupid loop yeah we're
looping on a list actually the list of
property count it's exactly the same
number so we have a hint here is unused
maybe here
yeah yeah previous developer want to say
something that so why can I do
it's maybe to use I've ever sit and
apply cone property because at the end
of the for each loop account will have
the same value as available soon I can
remove this one okay cool a little bit
how many screams hi do we have a time
for we wanna check you want you to to an
alpha 2 and alpha yeah
so that's a lot of thing that wasn't me
listen like that okay okay this is a
code for the treasurer's topology
maybe we can rename it yeah okay
Trent apology oh yeah it's all wrong and
you can topology topology domain expert
was talking about technology so if it's
better talk to me the smart guys okay
things not rent math instruction
instance we asked to do been expressed
about dodgy say no I am not aware of any
trainings in my domain so should I be
trained on stones my video so let's
rename it into train yeah well you will
set the transform a train topology yeah
what's this guy maybe you can just
assume yeah and it is here for people in
the back okay okay yeah you see this one
the block of concern is it used
yeah huge isipatana actually we use
multi population we use I adore for for
nothing and just just in case the
collection that count is wrong maybe you
can have a maybe that's the president a
together I don't know no sometimes we
don't have to try to understand which is
just silly stuff okay okay so I can't
release this phone used okay so you get
rid of it get rid this is fun it's it's
it's yes from the collection of
against it and it's the citizens ethical
Reserve said we don't talk about said we
we ask we ask me the very first also do
we have set us and they say no this is a
look to but never use you already see
that kind of valuables the clutter in
the code not even used anymore
yeah legacy code is full of kind of
stuff and it's kind of polishing your
mind this one have a look of this one we
have mother if here and we have all
pretty much the same if with the knee
invest yeah I just heard we like
symmetry it's much better to to you know
to compare stuff to to so as you just a
to inverse yeah and to be a good I
thought yeah I'll tend to invert if and
then okay we can see pretty much the
same you everything like fast no no way
just illustrate it because here as you
can see there is a one if here and
pretty much the same here so yeah this
seems there is nothing in the middle we
can cut the cord into the if below and
put it into the at the end of the first
if this one just at the at the end to
respect algorithm so it will simplify a
little bit the because to achieve so
it's really great a green yeah okay so
now you can read but why what are you
doing that because yeah it's right yeah
entrance when the code is not cover put
white thicket oh yeah
so let code for us this one is not
necessary to okay remove some line so I
think we have some space so this one can
be crosses the user J the
okay so you closed the dicussion yeah
it's not perfect but we chose a little
bit not not so more it's not really a
deep refactoring just to be more
confident it's the first round with the
first pass and the code from improving
your mental model about it and trying to
clean up some so mess okay something
better you yeah can you see what's still
bothering okay it's still very
procedural code one method to screen hi
I am doing this and then doing that and
then do this okay
you know collection script yeah yeah but
here to get the train doesn't know is
usually such that we cut yes because we
know the problem is we we instantiate a
train but this one normally after with a
domain object and not a kind of Jesus we
which is that a trend that has a
physical of proxy to of the external web
api we will make into a adapter for in
the portal adapter pattern exec us to do
that we will have another view before
that so don't worry if you are not aware
of that but instead of returning a
string of design let's make that method
returning as a trainer stones yeah so
that we can get rid of G zone within the
resident method and to make it more
domain and purely them and not mixing
technical stuff with a functional domain
stuff okay for you yeah still okay
so I discover the file there is a
constructor of the Train so this is a
training okay yeah yeah I we see a lot
of stuff to this allies geez on cereal a
dog yeah this is a file actually this
one is not shoes
I hear at it I can at the artistry so
today it's okay this one is never used
to let's delete it also this one is gray
you can split into various files maybe
yeah
so here we are in the Train class yeah
and clang class does not have tons of
behaviors I would say except by passing
a JSON and then we I actually Scott
Richter Souls my geometric see sharp
okay so copper serum is using a lambda
yeah okay and I will move this one so
these are the member of I abilities are
the properties on the fields in okay and
then all we have it's a constructor is a
only technical stuff so what you what
would you suggest
refactoring yeah should we keep yeah
there is a better locations to do some
season passing but the trend which part
of the domain and we should not do that
here do that yeah okay so to do that I
have to create a little to encapsulate
the code I want to move okay this is
something that we will do a lot extract
and move extract the method excited
video into a method and move into the
prop allocation we do that a lot during
the session first time we will do it
okay I I take all the code I want to
remove extract this one is okay
you're one more okay of this one okay
the screen is very high okay so extract
the method from that and it still will
be instance method yeah that Trent
apology because while passing the design
the thing is setting some value to the
property of the Train it's a nice method
here so who is extracting into a new
method yeah
public to be able to move it to continue
to use it yeah a good way to see if I
have some dependency because I want to
move this one but I don't want to have
dependency from this one I won't be to
insulate so I use static and I have some
squeezer
squeezes yeah and yeah because this is
static this is where we try to change
the install second test also see if it's
static it's made for Miro yeah so how
can we how can we get those yeah
Russian ship yeah to remove the
differences those two actually we're
trying to alright send the dependency as
an argument yes yeah yeah it's a good
idea but there is something like we can
do also it's a so far the if is not
Miriam empty then I increment the
reserve seats instead of changing that
value of kinds of seeds from that point
we may be able to cut the behavior
within the property and every time I
call the property the property is doing
compute the test so it may be one way of
doing it so you think yeah let's try
that and as I sit here instead of
letting the method changing the value it
will be something like sit return on
that collection of seeds
so that as we're not not that were
called count not neuro oMG something
like that yeah
Richard so it's a kind of think you for
so much aware of Java streams it's a
more Ducati fictional way of dealing
with collection and with enumerables
it's reserved so it's not so here below
is writing something like I take the
list of the seats and I count every six
where that lambda is valid meaning all
seats where they don't have a booking at
first new OMG so okay I can I can
surprise this one so now you can get rid
of that it will be done at the other
level and this one maybe I can make as
you propose something seminar associate
to list
yeah of seats of and and show some that
method into a function actually because
it it may be a static function yeah so I
have a sit I change the future I make a
list of suits it okay
and and then here I shape the local
variable yesterday yeah now I return it
so we can solve that method into a
function so that where we call it we get
the results directly so sis we adapt to
anthropology this is a first step
because we have to move it into the
proper location why is it trend is
because it's because it's running yeah
it's a matter of time after eventually
it's on to to be okay maybe so you
extract the method you make its static
function so we can move it kind of
easily let's put it if you get back to
the resonated well it has been called
yes
well adjourn here here we have a get
trained yeah so it might be interesting
instead of having the genome topology to
get the train to return a train so maybe
we can put that static function into the
tender the service yeah
so let's move so you move the method
into the train that I say is okay
so far we still have a awkward
dependency in the trend class but we
will change it in a second
so you make it to a public user yes and
the goal is to change this one the get
train the gate train every change the
signature so instead of returning a task
of string yeah touches before it's I
think where of requesting a Web API so
it's kind of actually on that complexity
but okay but you have to read it it's
written a train
yeah to be Bella for the business part
to take the trend already in some
okay so you trying to track from the
topology but the trend don't take the
topology we want to adapt the design so
we call it that adaption topology but
currently the train don't receive yeah
you have to change that yeah I have to
change that or so stead of that
let's accepting a list of seats yes so
to instantiate a train we will accept
the list of seats which will be much
more easy to discussed yet to play with
yeah and remove this one so we don't
have any kind of references from the
train to any kind of trend data service
or a structure code you know so that so
now I can take this one so gate trend
now is returning a train
estas so you don't need that anymore I
can remove this
and here we have some okay yes much
better
we asked the trend at our service to get
a train and we get a train
estas I compiled because maybe I have
brick yeah I read something it's
something that Bazar is unconscious even
if it does not compile it still green
yeah it's a Kenneth Berger I would say
but Bruno was compiled yes this is
within of test we did enough tests we
have made some LPS to estancia trend
from a given design for given topology
and this is where we have to do the same
we have to adjust the previous code that
we are expecting to the pharmacy at your
previous signature to the new one so
should I'm saying yeah okay just right
fine all right
I don't okay it's okay it's okay and
come back to let's get back to the house
okay so thank you Bruno
yeah
actually we move a technical code that
were part of the trend and we get put it
into a politician which is part of the
Constitution so I'm much better much
more comfortable with that code but
there's still lots of things that bother
me for instance let's see the trend okay
you clean the deck you improve the
situation but ok this is a train what is
it it's a pure data class without any
kind of behaviors without any color
responsibly and I'm not aware maybe it's
a follower or regular man that has said
once this kind of object is kind of
teenager object or child object you have
to take responsibilities somehow and yet
yet - so - let's let's do that also we
have a concept of seats yeah seat Wow
shiny stuff there is a name for that
yeah actually there is a name for that
kind of domain you have an idea of what
it is an amygdala analyser completely an
amygdala is a so we are lacking all the
concept of the domain within our code
but when we have we have kind of anemic
stupid data class yeah and all of you
have yours in easy that original method
kind of collections fit here very
positive are doing all the logic what I
suggest if you agree is to try to cap
some behaviors and to put it in the
proper location and try to Lhasa
our child objects yeah maybe you can
show something about our to check yeah
maybe we'll slide just since we will do
it a lot let's see visually what we will
do we have a Class A Class B Class A is
a web ticket manager has a message for
instance and the Class B is like say the
trial the train so what we will do a lot
it's to extract code to extract the
behavior and to a method so then we will
have a method
into the same type and then we will move
it into the proper location the train
for instance and at the end of the day
we will have more actually breaking the
balance balance
yeah domain and stuff like that okay so
let me switch back to the code so I
suggest that we will do that okay
each train reserved seats plus it's the
first business school a trend should not
exceed maximum capacity of the Train I
suggest that we extract a method here
but maybe does a lot if does not exceed
does not exceed overall trend capacity
once you like that are you okay you know
there are you
yeah capacity sorry I will make us a
non-static method a public one to be
able to move it easily so here I strike
that big if with that method where
should I move it according to a train
yeah and there is a hint if I have said
f6 to move we shall I say okay you pass
an argument a train instance of argument
so you can easily move that behavior to
the train okay do train I have the trend
does not exceed overall trend capacity
if I want to request that number of
seats okay actually what we have here is
available seats we are building a list
of available seats so let us call a
method with fine available seats for
instance find a vein bolts it's okay
non-static PP also remove it so here if
the trend does not exceed if I request
does not exceed the maximum trend
capacity we find some available seats
actually
there is some concept that we may
introduce here instead of that what do
you think a location a specification yes
[Music]
yeah certain coach at the end of the day
we need to have seats in a given coach
but before that the domain expert was
talking a lot about reservation attempts
it's a really important concept for him
so I suggest that we instead of just
dealing with available seats a list of
seats let's build an instance of
preservation attempt from that part
something yeah yeah good you know before
we are improving the code below as
something to show you
yeah maybe you some people know and
depend it's a tool to check the
parenthesis but it exists G architect
for Java or C++ basically an advanced
tools yes it's analyzing your code and
raising some warnings or mo and we were
working with ethics Macau etc in deeper
yeah and we asked him to introduce a way
to check that code base follow the
ubiquitous language for followed along
with the of the demand it's a prototype
is not a release and we try to imagine
imagine you you have a team you have a
legacy code and you know the vocabulary
of the domain expert and create a rule
it's called your code should rely on
your you basically language and we see
we have some problem and as you can see
we have the list of program and the
world not matching correctly irrevocable
the cap is there so we have to enter a
list of worlds that are part of our
domain yeah like train Cochise
a federation fulfilled etc currently we
have to define this list for each domain
you want and the tool we tried to check
that so it's still in alpha yeah but I
think it would be interesting where to
make some audit of some good is to is to
have a kind of code smell about that
okay okay so run it and what was the
result was a three yeah I I don't want
to actually okay so let's get back to to
the business we have some list of
available seats I suggest that we change
that you change the signature of that by
introducing the concept of reservation
attempt so here instead of returning a
list of seats let's make it return a
reservation attempt typo here the nation
at and thank you
okay yeah okay the type does not exist
so yes I'm aware of that maybe I will
rename it also but here as you can see
sorry I shouldn't wear did ya hear yes
the resurrection item type does not
exist yet so let's create it I'll tend
to create a presentation attempt okay
and here since the method is the
function is expecting to return me that
kind of reservation attempt all I have
to do is to install yet here at the end
return a new reservation attempt ok
providing it the list of seats I just
found all I have to do is to create the
constructor accepting a list of seats
for that reservation attempt ok and
that's it maybe return I shall attempt I
need to I will need to to walk with the
seats so let me start off creating a
field let me create now let's be real
and that it will be sits as a rational
attempt has a list of C and maybe to to
introduce a read property because I will
need to work with the the seats of that
reservation attempt okay so we just
introduced a reservation attempt which
has a property of seats and that's it
pretty much so that the fine available
seats now the name is maybe build
another Russian attempt would be better
yeah okay so now the method is built as
a Russian attempt its find available
seat within the Train and return a
resolution a talk with that it's okay
for everyone said okay yeah so the code
is not compiling anymore because I used
to work with the list of seats so what I
need is to rename available seat by
reservation turns first step and then to
add the in direction to the seats and to
work with the
the list of the weather of seeds of the
hydrogen atoms so just let me fill that
three location f12
oops got seeds left well okay that
should compile let me check
okay it's compiling is still green
so here what I just did is to create a
concept that is directly come from the
domain a reservation attempt and replace
a simple list or seat by a mate okay
what can I do here
reservation at tab that's it dot count
here it's like saying dot the
reservation attempt or easel reservation
attempt fulfilled the double experiment
talking a lot about that so let's create
a method for that extract and move
either fulfilled not complicated for me
to find out who writing in English okay
I think it's it's okay for that so we
asked the organization a table are you
fulfilled so first extract still on that
class and then to move it to the up
sorry
to the resurrection returned so I
extract to behavior and I put it into
the proper location which is as a
rational let something bother me because
you pass twice the seat
request kanji that is yeah you passed
there and pass you actually can provide
the seat requested code once when we
construct the resurrection attempt so
that we don't need anymore to ask to
provide it every time we want to to
check if it's fulfill a lot let's do
that okay I agree go to implementation
she requested counts I would provide it
into the constructor of the veneration
attempt here okay sorry I thinking I did
a huge mistake
so okay so I changed the constructor of
the reservation attempt I'll tend to add
parameter to the constructor yes please
sir do that and she requested code here
like what I can do is simply to keep a
read-only field meaning it's not public
it won't be accessible by the outside
world
freedom capsulated and now I had it what
I can do is to leverage on that instead
of the one that is provided as argument
in the each fulfill so here I replace it
the parameter with the internal field
and now can get safety nets this
parameter since I'm in c-sharp I can
transform it and to property expression
body okay let's let's move that now I
think it's okay okay so here getting
back to the each food fielder usage you
see I'm on a resume third I asked Reza
to build a reservation attempt to the
Train oh maybe you don't move on the
train
below that I shall attempt should be a
method from the Train so let's I just
extract the method first so let's move
it into the Train so now I can ask the
Train please train build me or as a
Russian attempt with that number of
seats I won't get a reservation attempt
and then if it's fulfilled then I can
continue I can continue to ask the
booking reference and also looking life
is not part of the domain he said always
booking reference yeah so let's stick to
the domain long edge in that case and
then what we do is to iterate on every
seats of the reservation attempt to
assign the booking levels yeah maybe we
can extract a method here and put it
into the resurrection attempt directly
which will be assigned booking reference
which one the which was the
the demo of the damage in the exact term
of the domain expert we assign a booking
ASEAN's
to someone I shall attempt ok I extract
the method what will be the next chain
stuff to do to move yeah move to the
other action attempt ok so we assign
booking a falls to the reservation
attempt ok if we look at the
implementation just two for you to
follow we take that booking a house and
assign it to every one of the seats of
the booking officials
ok I was thinking the same thing as you
and the domain expert was really saying
that we build we the process is to build
a reservation attempt and at the end of
the day to transform it into a
reservation so yes but I was the same
[Music]
idea yeah absolutely
good question actually we thought it's
like a technical term build you used to
do it to use it in technical but for the
domain expertise it was still a concept
of this realm so we have a train caching
save Wow well maybe it's time to morally
have a cache in this application within
this application on the yes you can yeah
- everywhere let's see if it's still
relevant here ok we have a declaration
of the cache here on what you get
manager then we associate it into the
constructor of the web ticket manager
then we clear it interesting we clear it
and crunch is changing the color in the
illustrating me that oh it takes 3
second average average of 2 second - -
to clear the cache I don't know what
it's there but ok I hope it was and then
we say yeah the book English fails and
the train I do care into into the cache
and then that's it it's just a so a
cache where we only save stuff
but think about our maybe it was a nap
tent unfinished that maybe that but even
now if we implement correctly it's a
mistake
as we said before we compete with all
the companion
so also company use of same service and
why we cash our topology American stuff
it's a mistake they can't change it
and so yes it's a it's kind of stupid
thing I would say let's get rid let's
burn that which up I remove it here I
remove that remove that and how it's
better I feel better now this is the
kind of discretion we may have with the
domain experts since it's not here we
call it before because it's not the
first time when you run that station but
yes I will be with that this is
something that we must discuss about the
strategy without talking about technical
details but saying that we can memorize
stuff that we get at that time is it
correct according to you so yeah so ok
we get back to the method we get a train
from 22 service then we have to train
our weeks of exceeded the over trial
capacity if we asked which it's yeah
if it's not the case we build a
reservation attempt yeah then we check
if it's fulfilled or not because we may
run out of seats I see the train is full
for instance or reached the next to the
limit then we ask booking a falls then
we assign the booking of a horse and
then we booked the seat and then we
return the the result I don't know for
you but now the method is one screen hi
we are embracing a little bit more the
concept of the domain
and we have kind of spreading the
behaviors into the proper location the
trend are some behavior the the seats
also the reservation attempt also yes we
can maybe now what would you suggest
because it's important to be time-boxed
so high because you can improve code a
lot but from some time we have an
objective so the objective below us is
to fix the bag to fix the bug yeah
concept yeah absolutely
you're right you are saying that you
what we can is to get rid of that CBG
zone here and it said to return to
travel as a national turn into a
reservation and then return a task of
preservation here so that has a method
is purely domain no string design inside
simply returning a reservation instance
we will do that we'll do that in a
circle but before that we will like to
introduce the missing concept because
when we build a reservation attempt here
we bill it from the Train perspective
and not from the coach perspective yeah
we use orders it is no notion of coach
okay so how to introduce the concept of
coach according to you what will be your
[Music]
basically the topology is taken from the
name of average every citizen name
including a 1 a 2 a 3 B 4 a is the name
of the coach it's a name of the coach
it's an implicit where I'll figure it
out these seats belongs to the coach
yeah absolutely yeah good idea but how
to introduce it right now what
we'll be over next move yeah okay yeah
okay
but how to do that how to do that we
start by what you suggest if you have
the keyboard yeah yeah why not but we
will start with widget test absolutely
yeah from from the train we will get we
will check that a train expose Cochise
for instance yeah for example so because
we totally addictive TDD and we want you
to create so let's add a trend should
yeah fixture go so far we don't we only
have some acceptance tests like it's a
system should do they do that do it so
we are three tests and here but it will
be our first unit test I would say it's
a should and maybe it would be should
expose Cochise something like that so we
get a train
so should trend show the expose coaches
yeah every much this one because I
attorney should expose Cochise yeah yeah
he talked a lot about it yeah yeah yeah
yeah actually yeah I had even in mind
some new rules for the related to the
coach he first us to fix that back but
when because money but he has some
inline to consolidate and to a new
business rules such as we should not
feed a coach more than 40 percents for
instance and stuff like that so it will
be the top allocation to to to make
so far we will need it we need to play
with the coach we need to ask to ask it
but yes if we want to keep it completely
private implementation details for your
capsulated we won't write that so just
for some explanation because I use a
snake name because we we use it in the
tests to mark some situations this is a
tenth apology dinner table yeah so he'll
probably have built a spawning yeah it's
a way to qualify the topology and it's
good to use because I know in this
topology I have to seat to coach and we
stand sit for each coach so the reason
why I use this one okay so you in your
test reassociate a train yeah okay
providing the train the list of seats
adapted from that train
topology okay so let's check that train
train the coaches yeah I'm sorry and I
hate coaches but does not exist at this
time we need to a size of true because
we have two coaches in the train
topology and you can also check that
every coach has ten seats maybe yeah
actually it won't be coaches I think it
would be like a dictionary for coach is
a coach is B okay okay I see coach a
that's it
not seats okay sorry a size 10 because I
stay every coach here
okay just to just to make it explore the
the what we have within the Trent
apology okay so it's time to generate
something yeah okay so you said the
dictionary we got first name
coach does not exist yet
the same you will create a type of for
coach yeah I would create because right
time
so here the train will have a list of
coach yeah and now I can start as a
dictionary but if you have more time we
won't expose it as a dictionary also we
expose that to read read only dictionary
or or even better a concept the
dedicated type for that but since we
would like to show you a lot of other
stuff we would rely here but to loop and
the sitter
so here in within the concept or dige it
would be okay I've got a list of we
said that the name of the coach was an
implicit information part of the name of
every six so for every six we just have
to check if there is a coach with that
name because seats has a capacity coach
named and if we don't have an entry in
the dictionary yet from that coach name
let's add it to the dictionary sorry yes
you can use a link you have a query on
sit for the beginning of the algorithm I
prefer to show without thinking ok and
by us to set a new coach a new coach we
also set a new coach and providing him
the name okay maybe so we iterate on
every seats of the trainer for every one
of them we
add the relating coach into the
dictionary on the fly then we have to
add the seats so which name okay okay
first step second step is to add the
city into the coach yeah just got choose
all right okay sit
coach Nate maybe yeah I introduced
available yeah we call it can you coach
no yes okay and new coach Adam sit are
you doing that for to expose the kind of
closure for a person but you want to
make it work and then we can refactor
something like that it's correct okay
okay okay okay
actually you have to associate oh yeah
okay I have to instance at first to
coach the coach is here yes oh yeah
coach Coach coach and on that coach you
had the seats I had to I suppose I kind
of list of sit so you are what blue is
doing is to make him else the data
structure and thing we will need to make
a coach a nice place to to find our list
of seats I would say but there is
something that bother me a little bit in
here but I'll let you finish
I've got to see greener I see just
complain I think it's not quite not okay
anymore so if you like that
oh yeah you have to expose sheets ah
yeah you're right
well sure yeah yeah yeah should be green
yeah it's okay
but it's really I don't really like that
kind of we add assets into a coach and
we change the coach actually if we have
more time there is something I would
like to do it's even to make it
everything immutable because what we do
is basically with when you reserve we
want to reserve some we get a Trent
apology which is something that we don't
own it's coming from the outside world
we walk on it and I really don't want us
to be tempted somehow to keep it in cash
because it will be stupid and I would
like to offer the fact that when we get
a Trent apology it should be immutable
all I can do is to work with to find
some information or to build a
reservation attempt but I don't want to
allow my mates or new joiners in the
team it start to to to break that by
introducing a cache and an estate where
I don't want to be so if we add more
time what I would like to do is to make
everything in the table the train will
be my table the coaches will be me table
and the seats also and and the only
thing that will be mutable which will be
the FSM I shall attempt you see a formal
direction a table which will be kind of
entity the thing that has a lifecycle
and allot CG but that can change another
another over the time at the end I will
transform the reservation attempt to a
reservation and no reservation will be
material to as Irish initialization we
it's a yeah you have a question
sorry yeah yeah absolutely we talking
about bed is of reasoning all salsa
Terra so if we get back to the to the
Adsit what I would like is maybe two to
one for sense it's to use what we call a
closure of operation its meaning the
coach will have a method which is at sit
ok I can add sit into a coach but
instead of mutating me the coach
installs what I would like is to for
that guy to reach on me the new coach a
new Aston soccer coach so I I call a
method
I'd sit on a couch installs all it can
do it to return me a new estas with that
sits involved but without changing the
the previous instance here where I call
the add seats method so the benefit its
to first time with ability for of course
or for passion but also to reduce
grouping it's easier to move to move
could cut contrary here the coach stand
by itself somehow you know method on the
coach which are mean you a source of a
coach so if I want to move that it's
more easy than if the coach we're
related to a new type which is related
to a new types and stuff like that ok
for everyone
ok yeah yeah yeah in any case it's
important to discuss with them
unfortunately we used to do that session
with one domain expert on stage with us
and we asked some question since he is
not here we know a lot of stuff so there
is a lot of implicit you know in our
heads but yes you're right we should
have kind of discussion but here it's
much more an implementation detail
I would say it's to all folks
the fact that I no want to talk any kind
of states relating to something that I
don't that I'm not owner of the topology
of the train I'm just a user and and
every time a request is is getting back
to me get a snapshot walk over snapshots
through my concept of the man and then
make the reservation
okay okay maybe not pop up yeah yeah
okay so let's turn it to instead of
changing the coach here let's switch our
new stance of coach yeah make it a
collision of attention here so adding a
seats doesn't mutate the existing coach
which will only return a new coach
installs the couch okay
it's the same with what with a list a
new list yeah actually this session is
best from a session of three hours we
have made in Paris with a little bit
expect onstage our left foot forward I
guess museum story with tons of stuff so
we had to pick a fight for that short
version of two heads there are many
thing that we may improve so we cannot
fault the fact that coach ships a train
our really value types so we would go
into that we will only make that coach
immaterial but maybe yeah there are lots
of things to improve respect so
producing a sure
yes to avoid the big issue to implement
the same constrictor as before okay so
now we have to fix as it's a coal yeah
yeah yeah we could existing code was
doing that so it's baby steps you know
you should call this oh my god so time
to change it yeah and to so so that you
will be to get the coach to add a seat
so through it new coach
yeah new coach and then to stalk the new
coach by a ball into the show okay so
it's still red here but I guess that
after saving that new coach value into
the dictionary it will be green again
fully new coach that's right okay okay
yeah
yeah sorry yeah I was in the test and
the coach yeah get back to the users
again yes if you're right
complete you yeah okay okay we will do
that because we would like to show you a
second architecture and lots of other
stuff but yes you're right you're right
yeah absolutely that was in the next
point actually we have a train which has
exposed a list of seats and a trying to
expose the list of coach but all the
seats belongs to the coaches so what we
should do is instead of having a
duplicate collection on the train
yeah instead to to have a projection and
the list of seats for the trend must be
the the projection of all the seeds of
every coach of the Train so let's do
that
select mini something like that so
cochis cochise let's take every coach
and return the value select any culture
change I just see better
- list new list this kind of linked you
again better so we met a projection we
take all the seats on every coach and we
return it at the this that's it for the
entire train so we have this one we
don't need to set it anymore because it
will be a get on me apology okay and
okay we need we have the coach compiled
yes good yeah
so maybe we can maybe who can fix the
beggar what do you think yes okay
absolutely
good idea yes idea is to move the find
available seats or the bill reservation
attempt to the coach level because if we
ask to the trade level there is no way
of properly there is a way that kind of
crappy so let's delegate it to the to
the coach so I'm removing this one so we
only do the test it will be red and red
green step so it's come back to the web
ticket and as you suggest maybe the
builders are short term is in charge to
to be verified and to tweet something
new so maybe we can change the algorithm
but respect so I go submit based on the
coach yeah yeah okay let's put that
logic of looking at cheat sheets
yeah at the coach level yeah so for
every coach yeah so we'll have you maybe
the same thing build a shortened I would
like to use this one please coach beat
me also rational touch if you can okay
and returning you a reservation attempt
okay
preservation adults attempt it's a
reservation
a time the core and creative reservation
at is fulfill okay
then return reservation reservation
attack
if not we continue to iterate on the
next coach asking the same thing and
once we have at least one coach
providing us its fulfill another Russian
attempt we are happy with that so this
one is actually the card I would like to
compliment on gettin pissed yeah in this
method so let's create the methods yeah
okay okay and I don't really like copy
and paste actually but in that case it
so justified its grain so we just fit
the bag by doing that maybe you can a
red green refactor yeah something to
effect oh because you know produce Peter
that I should attempt at the train level
we still let some code yeah so based on
what Oh Lolita yeah we have some kind of
we're happy code so let's replace it
with a link you request yeah so take me
please all seats where a booking arrest
is empty is empty rely on cheap right
string isn't it oMG okay
if we will create a method of yeah yeah
and and takes this number of yes it
request so here we are projecting a list
of seats that are available and then we
have a list of seats and we available
seats and then we take the first three
for whatever number we we ask and
replace this one it does exactly the
same thing of the for loop we have Jason
here to prove it you just have to what
you have to just to get get results get
rid of all that I think this was renamed
okay I remove okay so here mistake
so what we can do maybe seems we try to
missile because you could be more
diminutive yeah yeah thing so here is
quite difficult with semester we should
be it's available since we are working
on seats so non-static public and we
will extract that method and then we
will move it into the seat and the seat
level yeah so move it so here now if you
can zoom on the link us with a light on
the streets and we take all the seats
that are available and we take the first
number that we need it we needed that we
introduced that earlier for the each
fulfilled for another I should attempt
to be able to to say fulfil obtained a
good reservation yeah yeah I it's design
choice not good yeah okay so we are P
because which exact fix the bug we kind
of improving a little bit the decoder
yeah maybe we can have a tiny point
about aggregates yeah so just a tiny
point about aggregates I could get the
collection of objects with on tto value
types treated as a conceptual hole can
you see some aggregates in here
tray yeah this cultural aggregate yeah
why is that yeah it does not serve
aggregates maybe material actually it's
no because aggregates need in violence
need business rules need something to to
to to
yeah to be enforced I would say ed here
the only really in violent we have its
own at the trend never the must I do
must not exceed 70 percent of the
trendiest a limit this is a business I
own that the coach aggregates as to as
to to enforced when we discuss with the
domain expert he told that that he
wanted to add some new rules related to
the coach so that coach must not be
fulfilled also at must not be exceed a
given capacity so in that case it will
turn into an aggregate voice maybe it's
a kind of detail but something
interesting trained coaches and sit by
all be value types here as we discuss
earlier if we think about the way we
interact with the external back end we
get a kind of snapshot valid from a
moment of time and we will work on that
snapshot so we don't want to keep it in
cash we just want to work with all those
aggregates fine cells so to enforce that
we can make it all value types actually
in the long term Russian we that's what
we did
so that means that some aggregates may
be completely value types also yeah the
trend here it most of the case it's like
this message was to it was a one one
case where we could have this exception
if we have a level-two Business School
to be enforced at the course level it
may turn it you're right that in the
long run we do that so so far we
improved somehow the wet ticket manager
and the handle itself was a free screen
sigh full of imperative code with lots
of legacy stuff yeah I think we have
kind of improved a little bit it's one
screen high it's using the world of the
domain within the code what we call you
bitch to storage we extract some
behaviors and we put it into the popular
locations but there is still something
that bother us someone has told it
before this is that we have some jeezum
design into the domain method
and we still reach our task of strings
if she's also a jism yeah what we would
like to do here is to get rid of that
design strain stuff and to replace it by
your resolution sorry reservation so
that the relative method will return a
reservation and then on the f
constrictor side and we will transform
the Resurrection into a diesel version
if we have an adapter if you have
something that he proposed okay so I
suggest I will talk a little bit about
the second equation which slide I'm
sorry
I will work on the card yeah just you
don't see but it will explain when we
get back to the code and like an
architecture we explain my video yeah
okay
so who is aware of what our graph
structure is okay cool what executive
feature is its architecture pattern made
by Alice Taco Bell
I can't remember the long time long time
ago
and it has many benefits it's a pattern
that architectural level it's an OS to
embrace change it was the first idea of
Aleister was to plug and unplug external
dependencies plug and unplug stuff he
was talking about whether system able to
to be plugged with many different
standards as input and many different
stutters as output to broadcast news to
broadcast to to TV to radio to whatever
so it was it's melody was to have a kind
of clean code inside and every changes
in terms of i/o or way to interact with
the system to be a non-event to me
something like you plug a plug in and
you can plug a plug in and that's it so
it's it's come with it was introduced by
that idea in mind but when we think
about it it may allow us that we want to
foster on the domain to make some code
more value business value inside to
protect our domain code from the
technical stuff I don't know for you but
during long time I thought it was not
even possible to properly speed between
domain logic and and technical one we
try many times that we faced a lot and
since I discovered that that pattern
it's really a nice way to and for that
and also to enforce testability because
since everything is a pluggable and
pluggable we can stop we can mop we can
stop the input output of the of the
systems business logic inside and so for
today we will focus much more the how to
protect our domain Khan how does it work
it works
considering the world in two different
area there is our inside and there is
your outside
simple right no thousands of layers no
simply to area the inside is a domain
it's your double code like the has a
method like the trend the the
reservation at time the stuff like that
and the infrastructure code is at the
outside of your of your system so this
is where you will find your favorite
HTTP starch
your database drivers your
message-oriented middleware carriage
solution or whatever this is
infrastructure of silence which I've got
and what we want is to faster and to
improve the domain code so we have
diversity she is some kind of putting
some bubbles around your domain code and
defining some entry points to enter and
to leave the the domain code so you keep
the first which occurred at the other
side this is a nice capability actually
because I don't know for you but when
you start your theory as a developer you
need to improve your skill you need to
discover a new thing you need to do lot
of mistakes you need to implement you
all from last unit in order to realize
at one point that there are some silly
stuff like implementing or framework
stuff like that but before you focus on
the domain really it's still important
for some new young developers to be able
to to play in a kind of playground I'm
okay with that
as much as it does not jeopardize the
business value and the project and in
that case I'm happy with that because
there is a kind of location where you
can play it's a playground so first with
your code you can try new technology new
stuffs that are but without jeopardizing
the domain code so this is what I really
like in that in that pattern so how does
it work because there are okay Barbara's
but I need to enter two and to leave the
building I would say that to leave the
domain code so to do so in terms of
dependencies all dependencies are
towards inside believe the
infrastructure code is aware of can
reference domain code but of course the
main code should not be aware at all any
framework even Jesus toughest it seemed
like that so the domain is completely
independent from any kind of technology
even jeezum string or thing like that so
to do so to allow to us to move from the
inside to the outside to ask new thing
to talk with external web api and do
some stuff we will rely on post and
editors and to do sort of we actually
use
dependency inversion principle so that
from the inside we can go outside and do
some stuff at least Taco Bell recently
discussed with a new another guy I can't
remember the name and that was
suggesting the name of configurable
dependencies what Alistair was saying is
dependency injection passive and I don't
really like because this is like if
negative way of formulating things it's
you used to do that do the other way
around do the inverse so he was trying
to find a much more fluent intention way
of saying that so their leaders to
configurable dependencies so you plug
and unplug your dependencies run the
other main so if we get back to a case
here we say we have passed another tough
to enter and to leave the Z domain so
ports belongs to the domain and there
are some interfaces like lollipops here
so here I've got the I have seats which
is the entry point from the from the
transfer system so I had through an
adapter HTTP adapter IP dot net callback
I must call an interface which is a port
I another seat say please mate reserved
meal rather me something and I get a
reservation and that adapter will do the
rotation between the reservation and the
generation because he's Jesus that so it
will be the proper location to do so
when I need to form a business school
when I need some extra data some extra
thing if not provided by everything I
need from the beginning there are many
ways to do that but if let say I need to
ask one of the external
SNCF dependency you know the three web
api we call during the process we need
two exits we need to add something to
the outside so to do so we asked some
ports also made from the inside there is
a iBooks it interface there is I provide
trained topology interface and there is
I get booking reference interface these
are
domaine interface the the post still
belongs to the domain reason why the
lollipop is in blue
but the adapter is what belongs to Z
alpha structure
so basically rather turns something that
maps between the first Witcher code to
the domain one and vice-versa mr. K for
all of you yeah we'll see that in
recording in a few minutes so post an
adapter to go into God easy right okay
but when we try to implement it the
first time there's tons of question that
arouse and there are many ways to to to
do so so we'll show you one we have to
initialize we are twin it to initialize
eight to initiate you had to build you
have to build the stuff so I like I've
got a metaphor which is a keyring
metaphor to him to explain that to my
mate I try to explain to you first step
its we will talk here about the
composition of utopian application you
know the the place on your application
where you build all your dependencies
and then voila apply the system is able
to work and to do is work okay so we're
talking about the bootstrap of your
application here so three steps first
step is to Austin said I need to go out
adapters all the adapters to go to ask
to the SNCF back cam please give me a
topology please
so here are represented to send data
service adapter and booking a service
adapter these are like cheese to go
outside and to ask stuff so first step
is translate those keys then second step
is I've got those kids I wrapped them
with your executive I wrapped them with
the the domain the the exact one is
where the domain stem so it's a web to
get manager so the web ticket manager
will receive within its console tones
epochs interface to interact with the
extent I won and then whilst on set we
wrapped the exact goal with a new
adapter which will be the adapter to be
used in order to interior into to
interact with our system so it's I need
- I need to enter that it's the way to
communicate with our application but
once we do that all we have to keep in
our head from an application perspective
from the asp.net Web API perspective all
I have to keep in my hand will be Z and
three point adapter
so although the rest of the exact rule
and adapters it's an implementation
details once I've built the place all I
have to keep from our Web API
perspective is that adapter which is the
entry point from a formal system okay to
put it differently those three steps
looking at that diagram first we install
set the adapter we need to go out so V
for the three back ends then we wrap
them with Zigzagoon
whereas domain logic stands and then we
wrap that domain logic it's like Russian
doll you know I need to go out the exact
goal I need to go in and at the end of
the day all you keep in your hands - I
need to go in this is the only thing
that you need to interact with the with
a system from a reputation perspective
so all you keep in your line will be
only that adapter that you will inject
into your callback I speed up the
corners and stuff like that okay sure
you have some question we will call it
or hope you will have some questions so
just to have a look on the new version
you can notice now we have a reservation
and the modification has been to call a
confirm because after this line I know
there is no exception and I can return
the reservation so the did the
modification of the test desire yeah we
returned a reservation and I already
create a beginning of adapter the output
adapter with adapt reservation this this
this function will be called by Tomas in
two minutes so you start to move
the technical design annotation to the
proper place exactly okay what I suggest
is to for me to to reduce in that first
acceptance test what I will have to do
into my bootstrap my composition route
okay so first one is to step one is two
instances I want to go out adapter so
here ten data service for instance we
can even rico and rename it and sorry
senator it's a bad name it's not the
service that's obviously I was there
it's a proxy to and same thing for for
that adapter okay step one I instantiate
the dependencies I need to go to the
outside world
yeah all right then what I need is to
associate the exact good actually so the
exact on here is a web ticket manager so
let's call it exact only here for
pedagogical school perspective over your
life you don't you will call it with a
business name so please don't tell Eric
that we did that but just it's to focus
on the executor has to take you up on
topic it's better for me to to rename it
exact one here and then instead of
calling directly the egregore
all I have said before is the
application we would have to interact
with my my business logic through an
adapter yeah
so let's introduce hit yeah step 3
introduced D I want to go in a raptor so
here but I can do is to how can we
generation oh yeah oh yeah you already
came same name same name so I will
instantiate it providing what should I
provide okay I think I got a sense like
Russian dolls so those two first we are
providing to the exact goal here and the
exact one is provided to the to the to
the guy okay so I create a constructor
because so far you just had made a
static functions okay maybe you have to
make an abstraction
not to inject what ticket manager yes
actually yes you're right we talked
about personnel at the ports are like
interfaces so what I can do maybe is on
the web ticket manager here it's
introducing its we changed after so
let's create an interface for that and
let's say I reserve seats don't you like
that no it's sorry I I used to walk in
on a Mac so we try to pick a key border
to reservations it a lot
I was assets you work every day let me
see yes I reserved seats I tried to find
Susan as a stress yeah so I asked I add
the resume turd on that interface I go
here this is a port this is a port in
order to enter the exact word what I
mean so getting back to the code here
what I will provide to the external
adapter it will be the exact one but as
rubs go to implementation as charlie
reserved seats yeah I resisted
okay let me keep it into a private field
here I will need it so I start set a
reservation adapter okay so self step to
associate other nationality let's
introduce a variable for that with our
instance okay my idea will be to replace
the direct call to the exact code by
something going through the adapter you
know so just to make it compile I will
go to the controller to web controller
which is the place where I will use that
exact same adapter so in that column
here I will need to my entry point will
be together reservation request dto so I
will get a reservation request it you
give it to the adapter and the other
we'll get back to me with a diesel
relating to the reservation okay so to
do so I think the duration DT o is not
in the proper place I won't be able to
refuse it from the from the test yeah so
I suggest that we move that and maybe it
will be no envision is quite painful to
create project it's long so I will just
create a directories here I will create
returned that domain all right and
hundred aha
so that we can start to split infra
infrastructure and ha okay so that we
can we are able to speak properly every
type into the proper location I'd moved
typed into matching files for be sure
that every file match to type so booking
a national service where should I put
the manner of hot-looking referral
service it's a bad name nom label the
name will be different but yeah coach
domain yeah booking service i domain
yeah it's an interface so it's support
yeah actually here so domain yeah I
reserved seats support support so the
mainly yeah
I trained that I service its names but
it's a domain is it okay its interface
yeah reservation domain domain rights
reserved I shall attempt same
reservation hotel for you same
reservation failure also it's it's a
divine
actually it's much more something to
implement the biggest law where there is
no added value more than twelve toppling
seats the main main I'm kind of happy
because you have more domains than the
France feature which is not the case in
all my projects so far so citizen poco
sips reservation adapter adapter is part
of the infrastructure yeah solutely
trestle
capacity domain absolutely even if we
came in through the name trailer is it
the main and what do we have time data
service of course which is another time
and when ticket manager domain it it's
all exactly but so far it's seen as some
to HTTP rationale that we get rid no
it's okay so let's put it to the let's
keep it in the middle
let's keep it into the middle before we
completely clean the house and put it in
2009 Chester namespace
sorry I just enhancement yeah I would
adjust the namespace here for this for
the project so that everyone would be at
the proper location okay so what I was
saying is I will from the should Cochran
system should getting back to the test
okay
I said that I would like to introduce a
way to interact with the resolution
adapter so let's let's say it's a it's
supposed to do there is a better name to
find but new reservation request
diffuses I don't know if you you move it
I don't know I didn't move thanks below
so reservation request did you hear I
have to move is it's on the bad project
move to folder next nation for you okay
so now I will be able to reference it
from the test otherwise it will be part
of the Web API which has no reference so
far okay so we here I will instantiate a
new reservation request DT oh this is HP
detector Bob which used to instantiate
that for me but our number of seats here
will be it sits requested counts and
then the other
train ID so here I'm setting the
equivalent of the design we receive as
the input
it's a poco for a fight and it will be
trained AG here is my train
yeah okay so here I passed a new
requested yo maybe this thing's let's
make it viable to make it clean so I've
got a request it you okay and then I
pass the reservation request did you to
see to the adapter yeah I want to go in
a laptop great method okay create the
method and instead of returning void I
will return maybe a string which will be
the design I mean I can hear I can
return something much more like I speed
up net internal structure to make a
response but I won't go into that here
but as I rationalize it you okay
so here I am in the posts method yeah
that should we tell me the reason a
visual reservation something like that
why not
yeah so the adapter will return me that
and I will ascertain on that yeah so
instead of all that
general direction should be equal to
that Jesus that objective to target you
know that yeah so it's still right
because I didn't plug the janitor so
another term has three steps to
instantiate the entire exact on a stick
you but when I mean every method of the
other term of three step basically its
first step is to adapt from their first
ratio to the domain
second step is to call the business
logic and then the third step is to
adapt from domain answer to Z
infrastructure and to return it yeah you
know what is it about in every method of
adapter so let's make it here in that
case I don't have to adapt
here so I will just introduce a new
variable
for the number of seats and with a
machine liquid in the way your life
maybe you you have to sterilize yourself
and we simulate this tech because I spin
and do that for for us that sometimes
you have to translate the design in
local viable for a domain object so here
what I just did is to get some variables
but this is where you will have to
translate transform adjust whatever it
takes to to to be able to call the
domain logic yeah God so now I call the
exact room so exactly not reserved it's
a business domain Mossad and I put it
tonight local variable I get and number
of seats number of let me call me
requested okay I called the eggs egg on
its return me reservation is I think a
yeah
so has a ration but since it's an ascent
method I will have to await that and
truth sorry some like that stood up to
obtain and a second score but since your
method is I think because it's called
also a sink method I asked you to do so
and then adapt from a hot to this is a
method blood already done we had adapter
adapter damage sure I provide a
reservation and I get some string and
yeah I have to return you see I get a
resolution from the business logic and
then what I do is to add up back from
the domain to the design procedure this
is still read what did I miss
[Music]
you have to wait wait wait also because
of a weight this is Mexican Russian okay
it's room sorry it was a second way to
issue that's time to implement in SSP
net so here as you can see within one
acceptance test we have done what we
have to do is in composition note of the
application I don't know what you want
to do well we have less than 10 minutes
I think what that part should be the one
that we will put into the setup of the
application so I can do that plug into
the webosphere but maybe it's better to
keep some time for questions or for kind
of wrap up what do you think okay
yeah otherwise I think I will have to
run because we kind of little bit late
yeah so wrap up we started from
situation like this we have a web ticket
manager with a very procedural code do
this and then do that and then do this
and and and after we lead to some more
consistent and more I don't know what to
say not shot yeah God walking code also
after the method was kind of something
like this thing is yes pretty much what
we achieved what's important is that we
embrace the language of our domain
within our code plus legacy code very
crappy and when we if we had time to
executor and append
we will have less warnings we just you
know in second just just in front yeah
so we are we walk code now it's talking
about reservations but trains reception
at term present which is fulfilled you
see so much even if all the way expect
is not able to read our code we can read
occurred in front of him and
being yeah being able to have a
discussion and he's being able to say no
no this is not what I want for for that
system star star so there is less
friction there is less gaps between what
we implemented what we was talking about
so it's better if you want to follow him
yeah we had some independent show it in
a few seconds but just before that no no
yeah that's because it takes time to
switch as a final wrap-up we did not
have to time to to make you feel that
because automate expertise in Paris and
our first version was with him on stage
but it's crucial to talk to your domain
experts yeah most of the project has
issue because the river are not even
allowed to able to talk to Dominic spats
so for me so no it's a no-go I finish I
decide not to go to the project if it's
like this but it wasn't the case at the
beginning of my career so takes yes it
takes courage time determination to
enforce that but it's crucial otherwise
yeah not as if they don't buy the legacy
because I'm a coach and I learn how to
refactor the code generate people when
there is dependencies said my code is
not testable actually we can test any
code any code so don't be daunted by it
I guess you may have some cost yeah it
cost I but it's doable yeah and also do
it's we don't use a lot of techniques
here we basically use two basic
techniques from the refactoring book of
nothing further
it's extract and move methods so it's
pretty much simple as soon as you have a
test Alice which is the first steps you
can extract and move very very easily
the more complicated is to find some
proper semantics and to and to invest in
your domain design they we have great
in track of improvement as you just said
by some of you yes this is something
that is a living and ensuring you have
yeah you have been very interactive user
so thank you very much
[Applause]