the SCOTUS with
so come back from the beginning
Sookie near the deck you will have
another of you but trying to improve a
little bit yep
but before that is about that yeah well
typhoon 63 yeah yes for sure it's a
really early Jessica but you notice
something wrong with that yeah it's red
it's difficult to be confident if my
color is right because if I measure a
mistake I don't see the mistake I prefer
to see green light oh so to do that
we'll completely in do the test to the
strip in the burgh yeah it's a good
technique if you are in the same
situation why the test failing and you
need to you know so yeah there's a
technique that I like a lot which is a
golden master kundo master is you take a
legacy code you clone it and you wrote
you write acceptance test every time I
send that input into the legacy code and
the new instance which one I will
working on I must I'm expecting to see
the same output on both instances so
that without even understanding the
legacy I can't have a test unless
making me and forcing me I don't break
any existing behavior so this is a
strategy that we could have done but
here we are implementing the business
rule as the domain expert told us so we
will stick to that point for now but yes
it's a good amount so good so let's give
the decks below yes the first variable
this is notable everybody Sita I would
just have a look where it's using stuff
from the user so maybe I can decide to
move this one close to the user goes to
the usage yeah for example in the
backups room can you see all the code
every time I test is running in real
time I know I'm not breaking the code
still green
the div are of a C programmer because I
was a C programmer it was to put all the
way about as we know but right now so
this is your now it's not like okay
second one is called count what the name
yeah yeah count
wow what a stupid loop yeah we're
looping on a list actually the list of
property count it's exactly the same
number so we have a hint here is unused
maybe here
yeah yeah previous developer want to say
something that so why can I do
it's maybe to use I've ever sit and
apply cone property because at the end
of the for each loop account will have
the same value as available soon I can
remove this one okay cool a little bit
how many screams hi do we have a time
for we wanna check you want you to to an
alpha 2 and alpha yeah
so that's a lot of thing that wasn't me
listen like that okay okay this is a
code for the treasurer's topology
maybe we can rename it yeah okay
Trent apology oh yeah it's all wrong and
you can topology topology domain expert
was talking about technology so if it's
better talk to me the smart guys okay
things not rent math instruction
instance we asked to do been expressed
about dodgy say no I am not aware of any
trainings in my domain so should I be
trained on stones my video so let's
rename it into train yeah well you will
set the transform a train topology yeah
what's this guy maybe you can just
assume yeah and it is here for people in
the back okay okay yeah you see this one
the block of concern is it used
yeah huge isipatana actually we use
multi population we use I adore for for
nothing and just just in case the
collection that count is wrong maybe you
can have a maybe that's the president a
together I don't know no sometimes we
don't have to try to understand which is
just silly stuff okay okay so I can't
release this phone used okay so you get
rid of it get rid this is fun it's it's
it's yes from the collection of
against it and it's the citizens ethical
Reserve said we don't talk about said we
we ask we ask me the very first also do
we have set us and they say no this is a
look to but never use you already see
that kind of valuables the clutter in
the code not even used anymore
yeah legacy code is full of kind of
stuff and it's kind of polishing your
mind this one have a look of this one we
have mother if here and we have all
pretty much the same if with the knee
invest yeah I just heard we like
symmetry it's much better to to you know
to compare stuff to to so as you just a
to inverse yeah and to be a good I
thought yeah I'll tend to invert if and
then okay we can see pretty much the
same you everything like fast no no way
just illustrate it because here as you
can see there is a one if here and
pretty much the same here so yeah this
seems there is nothing in the middle we
can cut the cord into the if below and
put it into the at the end of the first
if this one just at the at the end to
respect algorithm so it will simplify a
little bit the because to achieve so
it's really great a green yeah okay so
now you can read but why what are you
doing that because yeah it's right yeah
entrance when the code is not cover put
white thicket oh yeah
so let code for us this one is not
necessary to okay remove some line so I
think we have some space so this one can
be crosses the user J the
okay so you closed the dicussion yeah
it's not perfect but we chose a little
bit not not so more it's not really a
deep refactoring just to be more
confident it's the first round with the
first pass and the code from improving
your mental model about it and trying to
clean up some so mess okay something
better you yeah can you see what's still
bothering okay it's still very
procedural code one method to screen hi
I am doing this and then doing that and
then do this okay
you know collection script yeah yeah but
here to get the train doesn't know is
usually such that we cut yes because we
know the problem is we we instantiate a
train but this one normally after with a
domain object and not a kind of Jesus we
which is that a trend that has a
physical of proxy to of the external web
api we will make into a adapter for in
the portal adapter pattern exec us to do
that we will have another view before
that so don't worry if you are not aware
of that but instead of returning a
string of design let's make that method
returning as a trainer stones yeah so
that we can get rid of G zone within the
resident method and to make it more
domain and purely them and not mixing
technical stuff with a functional domain
stuff okay for you yeah still okay
so I discover the file there is a
constructor of the Train so this is a
training okay yeah yeah I we see a lot
of stuff to this allies geez on cereal a
dog yeah this is a file actually this
one is not shoes
I hear at it I can at the artistry so
today it's okay this one is never used
to let's delete it also this one is gray
you can split into various files maybe
yeah
so here we are in the Train class yeah
and clang class does not have tons of
behaviors I would say except by passing
a JSON and then we I actually Scott
Richter Souls my geometric see sharp
okay so copper serum is using a lambda
yeah okay and I will move this one so
these are the member of I abilities are
the properties on the fields in okay and
then all we have it's a constructor is a
only technical stuff so what you what
would you suggest
refactoring yeah should we keep yeah
there is a better locations to do some
season passing but the trend which part
of the domain and we should not do that
here do that yeah okay so to do that I
have to create a little to encapsulate
the code I want to move okay this is
something that we will do a lot extract
and move extract the method excited
video into a method and move into the
prop allocation we do that a lot during
the session first time we will do it
okay I I take all the code I want to
remove extract this one is okay
you're one more okay of this one okay
the screen is very high okay so extract
the method from that and it still will
be instance method yeah that Trent
apology because while passing the design
the thing is setting some value to the
property of the Train it's a nice method
here so who is extracting into a new
method yeah
public to be able to move it to continue
to use it yeah a good way to see if I
have some dependency because I want to
move this one but I don't want to have
dependency from this one I won't be to
insulate so I use static and I have some
squeezer
squeezes yeah and yeah because this is
static this is where we try to change
the install second test also see if it's
static it's made for Miro yeah so how
can we how can we get those yeah
Russian ship yeah to remove the
differences those two actually we're
trying to alright send the dependency as
an argument yes yeah yeah it's a good
idea but there is something like we can
do also it's a so far the if is not
Miriam empty then I increment the
reserve seats instead of changing that
value of kinds of seeds from that point
we may be able to cut the behavior
within the property and every time I
call the property the property is doing
compute the test so it may be one way of
doing it so you think yeah let's try
that and as I sit here instead of
letting the method changing the value it
will be something like sit return on
that collection of seeds
so that as we're not not that were
called count not neuro oMG something
like that yeah
Richard so it's a kind of think you for
so much aware of Java streams it's a
more Ducati fictional way of dealing
with collection and with enumerables
it's reserved so it's not so here below
is writing something like I take the
list of the seats and I count every six
where that lambda is valid meaning all
seats where they don't have a booking at
first new OMG so okay I can I can
surprise this one so now you can get rid
of that it will be done at the other
level and this one maybe I can make as
you propose something seminar associate
to list
yeah of seats of and and show some that
method into a function actually because
it it may be a static function yeah so I
have a sit I change the future I make a
list of suits it okay
and and then here I shape the local
variable yesterday yeah now I return it
so we can solve that method into a
function so that where we call it we get
the results directly so sis we adapt to
anthropology this is a first step
because we have to move it into the
proper location why is it trend is
because it's because it's running yeah
it's a matter of time after eventually
it's on to to be okay maybe so you
extract the method you make its static
function so we can move it kind of
easily let's put it if you get back to
the resonated well it has been called
yes
well adjourn here here we have a get
trained yeah so it might be interesting
instead of having the genome topology to
get the train to return a train so maybe
we can put that static function into the
tender the service yeah
so let's move so you move the method
into the train that I say is okay
so far we still have a awkward
dependency in the trend class but we
will change it in a second
so you make it to a public user yes and
the goal is to change this one the get
train the gate train every change the
signature so instead of returning a task
of string yeah touches before it's I
think where of requesting a Web API so
it's kind of actually on that complexity
but okay but you have to read it it's
written a train
yeah to be Bella for the business part
to take the trend already in some
okay so you trying to track from the
topology but the trend don't take the
topology we want to adapt the design so
we call it that adaption topology but
currently the train don't receive yeah
you have to change that yeah I have to
change that or so stead of that
let's accepting a list of seats yes so
to instantiate a train we will accept
the list of seats which will be much
more easy to discussed yet to play with
yeah and remove this one so we don't
have any kind of references from the
train to any kind of trend data service
or a structure code you know so that so
now I can take this one so gate trend
now is returning a train
estas so you don't need that anymore I
can remove this
and here we have some okay yes much
better
we asked the trend at our service to get
a train and we get a train
estas I compiled because maybe I have
brick yeah I read something it's
something that Bazar is unconscious even
if it does not compile it still green
yeah it's a Kenneth Berger I would say
but Bruno was compiled yes this is
within of test we did enough tests we
have made some LPS to estancia trend
from a given design for given topology
and this is where we have to do the same
we have to adjust the previous code that
we are expecting to the pharmacy at your
previous signature to the new one so
should I'm saying yeah okay just right
fine all right
I don't okay it's okay it's okay and
come back to let's get back to the house
okay so thank you Bruno
yeah
actually we move a technical code that
were part of the trend and we get put it
into a politician which is part of the
Constitution so I'm much better much
more comfortable with that code but
there's still lots of things that bother
me for instance let's see the trend okay
you clean the deck you improve the
situation but ok this is a train what is
it it's a pure data class without any
kind of behaviors without any color
responsibly and I'm not aware maybe it's
a follower or regular man that has said
once this kind of object is kind of
teenager object or child object you have
to take responsibilities somehow and yet
yet - so - let's let's do that also we
have a concept of seats yeah seat Wow
shiny stuff there is a name for that
yeah actually there is a name for that
kind of domain you have an idea of what
it is an amygdala analyser completely an
amygdala is a so we are lacking all the
concept of the domain within our code
but when we have we have kind of anemic
stupid data class yeah and all of you
have yours in easy that original method
kind of collections fit here very
positive are doing all the logic what I
suggest if you agree is to try to cap
some behaviors and to put it in the
proper location and try to Lhasa
our child objects yeah maybe you can
show something about our to check yeah
maybe we'll slide just since we will do
it a lot let's see visually what we will
do we have a Class A Class B Class A is
a web ticket manager has a message for
instance and the Class B is like say the
trial the train so what we will do a lot
it's to extract code to extract the
behavior and to a method so then we will
have a method
into the same type and then we will move
it into the proper location the train
for instance and at the end of the day
we will have more actually breaking the
balance balance
yeah domain and stuff like that okay so
let me switch back to the code so I
suggest that we will do that okay
each train reserved seats plus it's the
first business school a trend should not
exceed maximum capacity of the Train I
suggest that we extract a method here
but maybe does a lot if does not exceed
does not exceed overall trend capacity
once you like that are you okay you know
there are you
yeah capacity sorry I will make us a
non-static method a public one to be
able to move it easily so here I strike
that big if with that method where
should I move it according to a train
yeah and there is a hint if I have said
f6 to move we shall I say okay you pass
an argument a train instance of argument
so you can easily move that behavior to
the train okay do train I have the trend
does not exceed overall trend capacity
if I want to request that number of
seats okay actually what we have here is
available seats we are building a list
of available seats so let us call a
method with fine available seats for