are you ready yeah okay first question
such question for you who already
experienced some difficulties to grasp
DDD concept at the very beginning while
it was the time to put it into your
project or into your code yeah okay so
you you're not alone and we yeah I have
to confess I have a sin problem I see a
lot of talk about DDD and I tried to
apply on legacy akhada
that's not no result why we imagine
cessation absolutely so the as this
camera here we will talk mostly talk
about tactical patterns and lost like he
talking about ubiquitous always and how
to put the long wave of your domain
expert of your business into your code
much more than strategical pattern we
will talk a little bit about it but it's
rather tactical yeah I wanted session
maybe before no no sorry
so I'm blue car I've come from Paris and
coach and teaching and I'm in charge of
BDD meetup in Paris okay my name is
tilapia use case driven on Twitter I'm
I'm working software since 18 euros and
I'm also Corgan either of the DDD Paris
meetup I'm kind of upset by use cases
and problem space because I think we
jump too much too soon into the solution
space we all our golden armors and stuff
like that our solutions so this is one
of my obsession okay we have some gifts
for you so we have two books two Bibles
the blue one and the one and refactoring
by Sola and voila
so to win those books you will have to
tweet as hell during this session using
the abstract DDD you you you thank you
we have a referee here so you will
have a look at that as tagging the most
funny tweet or you can you can quote you
can take picture you can do jokes about
us about you whatever and Jerome will
tell us the two winners at the end of
the shell session all right okay fine
cool all the other men for today will be
trained trainees kind of labs actually
so we will focus more on the city
Federation optimization yeah just in
front here it's the model of a train a
train which has three coaches coach a
could be in coach C which has some seats
already reserved in the orange empty
seats in in in white and here we are
asking six seats to be reserving the
Train in blue this is a simple model but
that may helps to illustrate some
something okay we have two business rule
for today for the system the first one
is you should not we should not with
there more than 70% of the entire
training capability capacity okay so
this is the first rule business rule and
the second business rule is when I want
to reserve I want all my city into the
same coach I don't we we don't want to
split families and friends between
coaches right simple we taking the rule
from amid abashed rank at our
reservation and we put some crappy code
on top of that but okay our domain
expert could have managed to be with us
in Amsterdam today but we talked a lot
with him before previous weeks so he
talked a lot about train I talked about
train IG or identifier it talks about
seats coach's reservation attempts and
whether or not they are not automation
attempt is fulfilled and you know they
also can we find to book working affair
as we explain what is it reservation
reservation failure that's a world from
the yeah you know the session we have
with it those words were the kind of
ubiquitous
so we will work for a startup company
which name is Tata
they provide the reservation service
which is basically a web api and this
will apply to do its work he has to rely
on external backends provided by
external companies so in front it's SNCF
so the first back-end provided by SMSF
which is external to our company it's a
trend data basically it's a hand
topology service meaning we we provide a
trend in Australia and we get back the
topology of the trend meaning the all
the coaches and for every coaches all
the seats and for every seat whether or
not it's available or already reserved
ok quite easy second one is the booking
reference physical kind of tricky one
because not working with when you buy a
ticket you have an ID on your train
ticket this Israeli actually yeah but
this is a service that only provides a
unique identifier so we can't booked
anything with that all we can do is to
get unique identifiers to play with and
once our seat reservation service on the
Left we'll have get a topology find
available seats then getting a booking
reference we actually booked the
reservation
through the National Train appellate of
service through that last train booking
sighs all right in terms of we are kind
of done streams we are a tiny startup in
that open market that has been opened
recently so these are the the back-end
provided by the National Train operator
is it ok for all of you yeah we will
continue maybe a balloon can do a demo
of the Web API so it will takes few
seconds to to switch
yeah ok so I use postman
where you can see the URL to call the
API and we can see the body the payload
with to fail to an ID
is a the notifier of the Train and the
number of teeth requested okay so if you
post yeah that one take a while yeah we
have some same an answer
transfer the first is a train ID okay
second one is a famous booking reference
I located by the serving as Tom I
described before and the list of sit we
get in back okay so basically that's
quite simple way to interact with our
system yes that's okay
basically we have a problem and this is
really why we are here today at startup
call us because they face rechromed
penalties exist excess of penalties by
europe national trainer patents is why
every call you met on all those back
ends you pages so that means that
started crossed our top every time you
call one of those where the pie is
charged from fees so they were expected
to do so but the thing they are paying
too much so they asked us to have a look
at the code and to see what may be the
reason and can can we troubleshoot and
fix if you have something to fix okay
but before touching any legacy code if
you are like Bruno and and I what would
you recommend us to do that test yeah
absolutely
in fact we this is really one we missed
the keynote we have built test arrest
this morning
discovering the the code and trying to
highlights all those business rules so
we've made so far three acceptance tests
first one first one is a happy pasta we
have a trend with only one coach we
stand sit and we
allocate a reserve twisted and as you
can see exactly what I do with postman
yeah and it is exactly the same answer
okay
simple IP pass okay second one is the
yeah this is the first business rule we
can exceed 70 percent for reservation in
all the Train and we if we ask to sit
and you can see I already six C reserved
yeah and because I applies the rule so
70 percent seven seeing exactly transit
the way to response an arrow is this one
I get that will ID but the booking
reference is empty and the list of the
city's empty this is how transfer is
telling us no reservation has been made
for you okay and the third test was test
highlighting the old seat must be in the
same coach please the second business
rule and in that case we found we
followed bag we found about because we
asked here we have a sorry a train with
two two coaches and one is almost full
the other is completely free and when we
ask two seats actually we get here one
seat in coach a one sitting could be
which was unexpected because we don't
want to split families and friends so we
are thinking about that is we know we
were saying that it's may explain some
things related to the field you have
some ideas about what may explain the
extra fees
imagine you use the website you call the
service and you prepare a trip with your
family or your girlfriend boyfriend
what's happen exactly it's to to counsel
because I'm not pleased to have two
seats in two different countries or
Council maybe we try it concern retry
consul retire at the end of the day I
will
which switch to another provider we left
control poor experience but that may
explain that because every time every
attempt will be charged actually so that
was our epithet ease and we discussed it
with Dominic's path through foreign aid
say yeah that might be the one so please
guys can you please fix that bugger so
we are here to fix that back
altogether and we will ask you to help
us in that journey so what would you
recommend to fix that back what would be
your strategy yeah sorry we are we are
the ten data service 20 Direction
service on the left on your range yeah
okay we are only working on that seat
reservation in in yellow these are
dependencies we don't have leverage on
that actually yeah not only consumers
now will complete with all the companion
we all start up and we compete with
other we need some information from
those two and we need to set and to
confirm and to book to make a
transaction with that guy so is that a
kind of interaction we have so in terms
of strategy what will you recommend
right test yeah right to test so
actually we already wrote a test so that
highlighted the bug so we'll have to fix
that test actually okay so let's dive
into the code yeah you know what set a
breakpoint you can call it yeah that's
okay asking me it's lunch in the bug mud
so here if you just to the side of the
screen it's a web it says AC sharp code
it's a high-speed Metco API it's simply
father doing Java spring boots it's tied
so simply for when we request that post
on that so sauce with that name we get
that callback
so and it's an emotional question we
receive just to have a look under the
TiVo is very simple exactly the payload
or the design absolutely and so after
that we instance yet you can slide to
the left so yeah thank you
so we associate a web ticket manager
which is seems to be the entry point of
the system and we call herself method on
it providing the energy you know the
bonus it's requested okay so this is
what we have test so far if we have a
look at the test that is failing our
three test is I kind of acceptance test
we consider the system as a black box
and we send so my quest and we checked
it done syringes on the last one is the
test demonstrate the program okay so
what we why we have a tool that is named
and crunch we see every time we changed
something we type something we change
the code it will run the test in in
background execute it and provide us a
feedback loop with a colored arrow on
the margins or greens is fine and ready
either there's a problem and there is an
arrow in in red below you you know yeah
a lot of you of the arrow is basically
it's the problem we were expecting to
have to sit in one Bo and to be and
actually we get 10 I 10 a and 1 B so
this is the bug we discussed earlier
okay okay all right well I think it
would be a good things to stuff to have
another view of what the hell method is
is doing oh yeah I just aligned the code
okay for you let's have a first author
of you let's we discover that this
morning so we have a little bit much
more knowledge about it so I will try to
help you to to have another view first
we
we associate a list of available seats
that should be probably the ritual of
the of the method then we call a get
trained on a trend at a service and we
get something like we call G's entrain I
need so G's on topology you will see
that yeah then we associate the Train a
trainer stalls from that design topology
and on that trailer stalls we do some
business rules here and there so here we
if the number of seats already reserved
in the Train plus number of sittin being
requesting is below is below something
like get max raise let me check should
be some percentage or something like
that
celebration yeah okay so eighty percent
of the overall trend capacity so if I
respect the the first business rule I'm
continue I continue is a number of K
over K 0 seems to be an accumulative
viable here and we tried to find some
available seats unavailable sits in that
system is the one that a booking life is
empty we have a property and if it's
empty string that means that the seat is
available and then we can add it into
the list beliefs that we will return at
the end of the of the method still ok
for you so far ok then we have a kind of
stupid for which we will see that in a
second then what do we have
yes if we can't find the number of seats
requested but we do we do we get the
answer you know the the answer that is
saying that you can even count reserved
for another spelling around so failing
methods if it work that when we call the
booking FF series 3-1 in the middle on
the right side and called get booking
reference then we assign that booking
reference to every one of the available
see that we have found so far we had a
bunch of accumulator here and then again
it's pretty much the same if if you look
at me right
you know now yeah first one is not
really insane but if it's still okay we
owe we use a cash yeah thirsting see
that why okay and then what we do we do
we actually this is the one that that is
making the booking I know tours i
transaction actually it will be the
external web app I would call through to
book a seat if I enter to that
let me check here the implementation
Emily we call a web app I know plenty is
on to call the web app yeah no real
interest in that and if we assume that
if we don't have any kind of exception
here what do we do we jump the answer
and the answer is the one dumping the
least receipts we were found so far okay
and in the case here what in the case
yes in the case of the trunk capacity
limit as X C has been exceeded we return
the empty
you can't reserve anything in that
trailer at the fella okay for every one
of you we will make a few review while
working on it but do you have some
feedback about that so far what are we
string concatenating to create didn't we
actually this is not awkward as a
disclaimer this is the car we discovered
this morning so yes but this is a good
remark why do we say allies attendees on
here in the middle of something that is
expected to be some kind of business
knowledge yeah sorry
[Laughter]
they don't know they don't even use
gates in that project in you know I
can't do that
yeah yeah yeah you're right yeah
absolutely
yeah that is a strategy we will try to
apply with with you we try to discover
the domain expert concept it's for this
card we try to figure out how can we
improve that because so far there is
something that's really bother me we
were talking about the domain expert
talking with us with terms of concepts
can you see about the Train and the
concept of seat do you Trina
do you see any other concept of the
domain there is something missing coach
coach the concept of coach is completely
missing here and and other stuff
reservation the reservation no
reservation no reservation no
reservation attempt so far so who
already expense code like this in this
carrier has yeah so we are not alone so
the ID here for us will be to have a
kind of way of improving it because
since we don't have any kind of coach
here the strategy for us to fix the bug
would be to make it MLG but before that
it still there is so much crappy thing
in like that so let's clean first came
the deck yeah do you know the name
cleans the deck the expression clean the
deck now clean the deck is the first
phase when you discover a code you
because you need to be more confident
before to apply a deep refactoring it's
a way to discover fix a little name of
the variables for example and after get
into the program it's a way to prepare a
mental model yeah you know heads from