and allot CG but that can change another
another over the time at the end I will
transform the reservation attempt to a
reservation and no reservation will be
material to as Irish initialization we
it's a yeah you have a question
sorry yeah yeah absolutely we talking
about bed is of reasoning all salsa
Terra so if we get back to the to the
Adsit what I would like is maybe two to
one for sense it's to use what we call a
closure of operation its meaning the
coach will have a method which is at sit
ok I can add sit into a coach but
instead of mutating me the coach
installs what I would like is to for
that guy to reach on me the new coach a
new Aston soccer coach so I I call a
method
I'd sit on a couch installs all it can
do it to return me a new estas with that
sits involved but without changing the
the previous instance here where I call
the add seats method so the benefit its
to first time with ability for of course
or for passion but also to reduce
grouping it's easier to move to move
could cut contrary here the coach stand
by itself somehow you know method on the
coach which are mean you a source of a
coach so if I want to move that it's
more easy than if the coach we're
related to a new type which is related
to a new types and stuff like that ok
for everyone
ok yeah yeah yeah in any case it's
important to discuss with them
unfortunately we used to do that session
with one domain expert on stage with us
and we asked some question since he is
not here we know a lot of stuff so there
is a lot of implicit you know in our
heads but yes you're right we should
have kind of discussion but here it's
much more an implementation detail
I would say it's to all folks
the fact that I no want to talk any kind
of states relating to something that I
don't that I'm not owner of the topology
of the train I'm just a user and and
every time a request is is getting back
to me get a snapshot walk over snapshots
through my concept of the man and then
make the reservation
okay okay maybe not pop up yeah yeah
okay so let's turn it to instead of
changing the coach here let's switch our
new stance of coach yeah make it a
collision of attention here so adding a
seats doesn't mutate the existing coach
which will only return a new coach
installs the couch okay
it's the same with what with a list a
new list yeah actually this session is
best from a session of three hours we
have made in Paris with a little bit
expect onstage our left foot forward I
guess museum story with tons of stuff so
we had to pick a fight for that short
version of two heads there are many
thing that we may improve so we cannot
fault the fact that coach ships a train
our really value types so we would go
into that we will only make that coach
immaterial but maybe yeah there are lots
of things to improve respect so
producing a sure
yes to avoid the big issue to implement
the same constrictor as before okay so
now we have to fix as it's a coal yeah
yeah yeah we could existing code was
doing that so it's baby steps you know
you should call this oh my god so time
to change it yeah and to so so that you
will be to get the coach to add a seat
so through it new coach
yeah new coach and then to stalk the new
coach by a ball into the show okay so
it's still red here but I guess that
after saving that new coach value into
the dictionary it will be green again
fully new coach that's right okay okay
yeah
yeah sorry yeah I was in the test and
the coach yeah get back to the users
again yes if you're right
complete you yeah okay okay we will do
that because we would like to show you a
second architecture and lots of other
stuff but yes you're right you're right
yeah absolutely that was in the next
point actually we have a train which has
exposed a list of seats and a trying to
expose the list of coach but all the
seats belongs to the coaches so what we
should do is instead of having a
duplicate collection on the train
yeah instead to to have a projection and
the list of seats for the trend must be
the the projection of all the seeds of
every coach of the Train so let's do
that
select mini something like that so
cochis cochise let's take every coach
and return the value select any culture
change I just see better
- list new list this kind of linked you
again better so we met a projection we
take all the seats on every coach and we
return it at the this that's it for the
entire train so we have this one we
don't need to set it anymore because it
will be a get on me apology okay and
okay we need we have the coach compiled
yes good yeah
so maybe we can maybe who can fix the
beggar what do you think yes okay
absolutely
good idea yes idea is to move the find
available seats or the bill reservation
attempt to the coach level because if we
ask to the trade level there is no way
of properly there is a way that kind of
crappy so let's delegate it to the to
the coach so I'm removing this one so we
only do the test it will be red and red
green step so it's come back to the web
ticket and as you suggest maybe the
builders are short term is in charge to
to be verified and to tweet something
new so maybe we can change the algorithm
but respect so I go submit based on the
coach yeah yeah okay let's put that
logic of looking at cheat sheets
yeah at the coach level yeah so for
every coach yeah so we'll have you maybe
the same thing build a shortened I would
like to use this one please coach beat
me also rational touch if you can okay
and returning you a reservation attempt
okay
preservation adults attempt it's a
reservation
a time the core and creative reservation
at is fulfill okay
then return reservation reservation
attack
if not we continue to iterate on the
next coach asking the same thing and
once we have at least one coach
providing us its fulfill another Russian
attempt we are happy with that so this
one is actually the card I would like to
compliment on gettin pissed yeah in this
method so let's create the methods yeah
okay okay and I don't really like copy
and paste actually but in that case it
so justified its grain so we just fit
the bag by doing that maybe you can a
red green refactor yeah something to
effect oh because you know produce Peter
that I should attempt at the train level
we still let some code yeah so based on
what Oh Lolita yeah we have some kind of
we're happy code so let's replace it
with a link you request yeah so take me
please all seats where a booking arrest
is empty is empty rely on cheap right
string isn't it oMG okay
if we will create a method of yeah yeah
and and takes this number of yes it
request so here we are projecting a list
of seats that are available and then we
have a list of seats and we available
seats and then we take the first three
for whatever number we we ask and
replace this one it does exactly the
same thing of the for loop we have Jason
here to prove it you just have to what
you have to just to get get results get
rid of all that I think this was renamed
okay I remove okay so here mistake
so what we can do maybe seems we try to
missile because you could be more
diminutive yeah yeah thing so here is
quite difficult with semester we should
be it's available since we are working
on seats so non-static public and we
will extract that method and then we
will move it into the seat and the seat
level yeah so move it so here now if you
can zoom on the link us with a light on
the streets and we take all the seats
that are available and we take the first
number that we need it we needed that we
introduced that earlier for the each
fulfilled for another I should attempt
to be able to to say fulfil obtained a
good reservation yeah yeah I it's design
choice not good yeah okay so we are P
because which exact fix the bug we kind
of improving a little bit the decoder
yeah maybe we can have a tiny point
about aggregates yeah so just a tiny
point about aggregates I could get the
collection of objects with on tto value
types treated as a conceptual hole can
you see some aggregates in here
tray yeah this cultural aggregate yeah
why is that yeah it does not serve
aggregates maybe material actually it's
no because aggregates need in violence
need business rules need something to to
to to
yeah to be enforced I would say ed here
the only really in violent we have its
own at the trend never the must I do
must not exceed 70 percent of the
trendiest a limit this is a business I
own that the coach aggregates as to as
to to enforced when we discuss with the
domain expert he told that that he
wanted to add some new rules related to
the coach so that coach must not be
fulfilled also at must not be exceed a
given capacity so in that case it will
turn into an aggregate voice maybe it's
a kind of detail but something
interesting trained coaches and sit by
all be value types here as we discuss
earlier if we think about the way we
interact with the external back end we
get a kind of snapshot valid from a
moment of time and we will work on that
snapshot so we don't want to keep it in
cash we just want to work with all those
aggregates fine cells so to enforce that
we can make it all value types actually
in the long term Russian we that's what
we did
so that means that some aggregates may
be completely value types also yeah the
trend here it most of the case it's like
this message was to it was a one one
case where we could have this exception
if we have a level-two Business School
to be enforced at the course level it
may turn it you're right that in the
long run we do that so so far we
improved somehow the wet ticket manager
and the handle itself was a free screen
sigh full of imperative code with lots
of legacy stuff yeah I think we have
kind of improved a little bit it's one
screen high it's using the world of the
domain within the code what we call you
bitch to storage we extract some
behaviors and we put it into the popular
locations but there is still something
that bother us someone has told it
before this is that we have some jeezum
design into the domain method
and we still reach our task of strings
if she's also a jism yeah what we would
like to do here is to get rid of that
design strain stuff and to replace it by
your resolution sorry reservation so
that the relative method will return a
reservation and then on the f
constrictor side and we will transform
the Resurrection into a diesel version
if we have an adapter if you have
something that he proposed okay so I
suggest I will talk a little bit about
the second equation which slide I'm
sorry
I will work on the card yeah just you
don't see but it will explain when we
get back to the code and like an
architecture we explain my video yeah
okay
so who is aware of what our graph
structure is okay cool what executive
feature is its architecture pattern made
by Alice Taco Bell
I can't remember the long time long time
ago
and it has many benefits it's a pattern
that architectural level it's an OS to
embrace change it was the first idea of
Aleister was to plug and unplug external
dependencies plug and unplug stuff he
was talking about whether system able to
to be plugged with many different
standards as input and many different
stutters as output to broadcast news to
broadcast to to TV to radio to whatever
so it was it's melody was to have a kind
of clean code inside and every changes
in terms of i/o or way to interact with
the system to be a non-event to me
something like you plug a plug in and
you can plug a plug in and that's it so
it's it's come with it was introduced by
that idea in mind but when we think
about it it may allow us that we want to
foster on the domain to make some code
more value business value inside to
protect our domain code from the
technical stuff I don't know for you but
during long time I thought it was not
even possible to properly speed between
domain logic and and technical one we
try many times that we faced a lot and
since I discovered that that pattern
it's really a nice way to and for that
and also to enforce testability because
since everything is a pluggable and
pluggable we can stop we can mop we can
stop the input output of the of the
systems business logic inside and so for
today we will focus much more the how to
protect our domain Khan how does it work
it works
considering the world in two different
area there is our inside and there is
your outside
simple right no thousands of layers no
simply to area the inside is a domain
it's your double code like the has a
method like the trend the the
reservation at time the stuff like that
and the infrastructure code is at the
outside of your of your system so this
is where you will find your favorite
HTTP starch
your database drivers your
message-oriented middleware carriage
solution or whatever this is
infrastructure of silence which I've got
and what we want is to faster and to
improve the domain code so we have
diversity she is some kind of putting
some bubbles around your domain code and
defining some entry points to enter and
to leave the the domain code so you keep
the first which occurred at the other
side this is a nice capability actually
because I don't know for you but when
you start your theory as a developer you
need to improve your skill you need to
discover a new thing you need to do lot
of mistakes you need to implement you
all from last unit in order to realize
at one point that there are some silly
stuff like implementing or framework
stuff like that but before you focus on
the domain really it's still important
for some new young developers to be able
to to play in a kind of playground I'm
okay with that
as much as it does not jeopardize the
business value and the project and in
that case I'm happy with that because
there is a kind of location where you
can play it's a playground so first with
your code you can try new technology new
stuffs that are but without jeopardizing
the domain code so this is what I really
like in that in that pattern so how does
it work because there are okay Barbara's
but I need to enter two and to leave the
building I would say that to leave the
domain code so to do so in terms of
dependencies all dependencies are
towards inside believe the
infrastructure code is aware of can
reference domain code but of course the
main code should not be aware at all any
framework even Jesus toughest it seemed
like that so the domain is completely
independent from any kind of technology
even jeezum string or thing like that so
to do so to allow to us to move from the
inside to the outside to ask new thing
to talk with external web api and do
some stuff we will rely on post and
editors and to do sort of we actually
use
dependency inversion principle so that
from the inside we can go outside and do
some stuff at least Taco Bell recently
discussed with a new another guy I can't
remember the name and that was
suggesting the name of configurable
dependencies what Alistair was saying is
dependency injection passive and I don't
really like because this is like if
negative way of formulating things it's
you used to do that do the other way
around do the inverse so he was trying
to find a much more fluent intention way
of saying that so their leaders to
configurable dependencies so you plug
and unplug your dependencies run the
other main so if we get back to a case
here we say we have passed another tough
to enter and to leave the Z domain so
ports belongs to the domain and there
are some interfaces like lollipops here
so here I've got the I have seats which
is the entry point from the from the
transfer system so I had through an
adapter HTTP adapter IP dot net callback
I must call an interface which is a port
I another seat say please mate reserved
meal rather me something and I get a
reservation and that adapter will do the
rotation between the reservation and the
generation because he's Jesus that so it
will be the proper location to do so
when I need to form a business school
when I need some extra data some extra
thing if not provided by everything I
need from the beginning there are many
ways to do that but if let say I need to
ask one of the external
SNCF dependency you know the three web
api we call during the process we need
two exits we need to add something to
the outside so to do so we asked some
ports also made from the inside there is
a iBooks it interface there is I provide
trained topology interface and there is
I get booking reference interface these
are
domaine interface the the post still
belongs to the domain reason why the
lollipop is in blue
but the adapter is what belongs to Z
alpha structure
so basically rather turns something that
maps between the first Witcher code to
the domain one and vice-versa mr. K for
all of you yeah we'll see that in
recording in a few minutes so post an
adapter to go into God easy right okay
but when we try to implement it the
first time there's tons of question that
arouse and there are many ways to to to
do so so we'll show you one we have to
initialize we are twin it to initialize
eight to initiate you had to build you
have to build the stuff so I like I've
got a metaphor which is a keyring
metaphor to him to explain that to my
mate I try to explain to you first step
its we will talk here about the
composition of utopian application you
know the the place on your application
where you build all your dependencies
and then voila apply the system is able
to work and to do is work okay so we're
talking about the bootstrap of your
application here so three steps first
step is to Austin said I need to go out
adapters all the adapters to go to ask
to the SNCF back cam please give me a
topology please
so here are represented to send data
service adapter and booking a service
adapter these are like cheese to go
outside and to ask stuff so first step
is translate those keys then second step
is I've got those kids I wrapped them
with your executive I wrapped them with
the the domain the the exact one is
where the domain stem so it's a web to
get manager so the web ticket manager
will receive within its console tones
epochs interface to interact with the
extent I won and then whilst on set we
wrapped the exact goal with a new
adapter which will be the adapter to be
used in order to interior into to
interact with our system so it's I need
- I need to enter that it's the way to
communicate with our application but
once we do that all we have to keep in
our head from an application perspective
from the asp.net Web API perspective all
I have to keep in my hand will be Z and
three point adapter
so although the rest of the exact rule
and adapters it's an implementation
details once I've built the place all I
have to keep from our Web API
perspective is that adapter which is the
entry point from a formal system okay to
put it differently those three steps
looking at that diagram first we install
set the adapter we need to go out so V
for the three back ends then we wrap
them with Zigzagoon
whereas domain logic stands and then we
wrap that domain logic it's like Russian
doll you know I need to go out the exact
goal I need to go in and at the end of
the day all you keep in your hands - I
need to go in this is the only thing
that you need to interact with the with
a system from a reputation perspective
so all you keep in your line will be
only that adapter that you will inject
into your callback I speed up the
corners and stuff like that okay sure
you have some question we will call it
or hope you will have some questions so
just to have a look on the new version
you can notice now we have a reservation
and the modification has been to call a
confirm because after this line I know
there is no exception and I can return
the reservation so the did the
modification of the test desire yeah we
returned a reservation and I already
create a beginning of adapter the output
adapter with adapt reservation this this
this function will be called by Tomas in
two minutes so you start to move
the technical design annotation to the
proper place exactly okay what I suggest
is to for me to to reduce in that first
acceptance test what I will have to do
into my bootstrap my composition route
okay so first one is to step one is two
instances I want to go out adapter so
here ten data service for instance we
can even rico and rename it and sorry
senator it's a bad name it's not the
service that's obviously I was there
it's a proxy to and same thing for for
that adapter okay step one I instantiate
the dependencies I need to go to the
outside world
yeah all right then what I need is to
associate the exact good actually so the
exact on here is a web ticket manager so
let's call it exact only here for
pedagogical school perspective over your
life you don't you will call it with a
business name so please don't tell Eric
that we did that but just it's to focus
on the executor has to take you up on
topic it's better for me to to rename it
exact one here and then instead of
calling directly the egregore
all I have said before is the
application we would have to interact
with my my business logic through an
adapter yeah
so let's introduce hit yeah step 3
introduced D I want to go in a raptor so
here but I can do is to how can we
generation oh yeah oh yeah you already
came same name same name so I will
instantiate it providing what should I
provide okay I think I got a sense like
Russian dolls so those two first we are
providing to the exact goal here and the
exact one is provided to the to the to
the guy okay so I create a constructor
because so far you just had made a
static functions okay maybe you have to
make an abstraction
not to inject what ticket manager yes
actually yes you're right we talked
about personnel at the ports are like
interfaces so what I can do maybe is on
the web ticket manager here it's
introducing its we changed after so
let's create an interface for that and
let's say I reserve seats don't you like
that no it's sorry I I used to walk in
on a Mac so we try to pick a key border
to reservations it a lot
I was assets you work every day let me
see yes I reserved seats I tried to find
Susan as a stress yeah so I asked I add
the resume turd on that interface I go
here this is a port this is a port in
order to enter the exact word what I
mean so getting back to the code here
what I will provide to the external
adapter it will be the exact one but as
rubs go to implementation as charlie
reserved seats yeah I resisted
okay let me keep it into a private field
here I will need it so I start set a
reservation adapter okay so self step to
associate other nationality let's
introduce a variable for that with our
instance okay my idea will be to replace
the direct call to the exact code by
something going through the adapter you
know so just to make it compile I will
go to the controller to web controller
which is the place where I will use that
exact same adapter so in that column
here I will need to my entry point will
be together reservation request dto so I
will get a reservation request it you
give it to the adapter and the other
we'll get back to me with a diesel
relating to the reservation okay so to
do so I think the duration DT o is not
in the proper place I won't be able to
refuse it from the from the test yeah so
I suggest that we move that and maybe it
will be no envision is quite painful to
create project it's long so I will just
create a directories here I will create
returned that domain all right and
hundred aha
so that we can start to split infra
infrastructure and ha okay so that we
can we are able to speak properly every
type into the proper location I'd moved
typed into matching files for be sure
that every file match to type so booking
a national service where should I put
the manner of hot-looking referral
service it's a bad name nom label the
name will be different but yeah coach
domain yeah booking service i domain
yeah it's an interface so it's support
yeah actually here so domain yeah I
reserved seats support support so the
mainly yeah
I trained that I service its names but
it's a domain is it okay its interface
yeah reservation domain domain rights
reserved I shall attempt same
reservation hotel for you same
reservation failure also it's it's a
divine
actually it's much more something to
implement the biggest law where there is
no added value more than twelve toppling
seats the main main I'm kind of happy
because you have more domains than the
France feature which is not the case in
all my projects so far so citizen poco
sips reservation adapter adapter is part
of the infrastructure yeah solutely
trestle
capacity domain absolutely even if we
came in through the name trailer is it
the main and what do we have time data
service of course which is another time
and when ticket manager domain it it's
all exactly but so far it's seen as some
to HTTP rationale that we get rid no
it's okay so let's put it to the let's
keep it in the middle
let's keep it into the middle before we
completely clean the house and put it in
2009 Chester namespace
sorry I just enhancement yeah I would
adjust the namespace here for this for
the project so that everyone would be at
the proper location okay so what I was
saying is I will from the should Cochran
system should getting back to the test
okay
I said that I would like to introduce a
way to interact with the resolution
adapter so let's let's say it's a it's
supposed to do there is a better name to
find but new reservation request
diffuses I don't know if you you move it
I don't know I didn't move thanks below
so reservation request did you hear I
have to move is it's on the bad project
move to folder next nation for you okay
so now I will be able to reference it
from the test otherwise it will be part
of the Web API which has no reference so
far okay so we here I will instantiate a
new reservation request DT oh this is HP
detector Bob which used to instantiate
that for me but our number of seats here
will be it sits requested counts and
then the other
train ID so here I'm setting the
equivalent of the design we receive as
the input
it's a poco for a fight and it will be
trained AG here is my train
yeah okay so here I passed a new
requested yo maybe this thing's let's
make it viable to make it clean so I've
got a request it you okay and then I
pass the reservation request did you to
see to the adapter yeah I want to go in
a laptop great method okay create the
method and instead of returning void I
will return maybe a string which will be
the design I mean I can hear I can
return something much more like I speed
up net internal structure to make a
response but I won't go into that here
but as I rationalize it you okay
so here I am in the posts method yeah
that should we tell me the reason a
visual reservation something like that
why not
yeah so the adapter will return me that
and I will ascertain on that yeah so
instead of all that
general direction should be equal to
that Jesus that objective to target you
know that yeah so it's still right
because I didn't plug the janitor so
another term has three steps to
instantiate the entire exact on a stick
you but when I mean every method of the
other term of three step basically its
first step is to adapt from their first
ratio to the domain
second step is to call the business
logic and then the third step is to
adapt from domain answer to Z
infrastructure and to return it yeah you
know what is it about in every method of
adapter so let's make it here in that
case I don't have to adapt
here so I will just introduce a new
variable
for the number of seats and with a
machine liquid in the way your life
maybe you you have to sterilize yourself
and we simulate this tech because I spin
and do that for for us that sometimes
you have to translate the design in
local viable for a domain object so here
what I just did is to get some variables
but this is where you will have to
translate transform adjust whatever it
takes to to to be able to call the
domain logic yeah God so now I call the
exact room so exactly not reserved it's
a business domain Mossad and I put it
tonight local variable I get and number
of seats number of let me call me
requested okay I called the eggs egg on
its return me reservation is I think a
yeah
so has a ration but since it's an ascent
method I will have to await that and
truth sorry some like that stood up to
obtain and a second score but since your
method is I think because it's called
also a sink method I asked you to do so
and then adapt from a hot to this is a
method blood already done we had adapter
adapter damage sure I provide a
reservation and I get some string and
yeah I have to return you see I get a
resolution from the business logic and
then what I do is to add up back from
the domain to the design procedure this
is still read what did I miss
[Music]
you have to wait wait wait also because
of a weight this is Mexican Russian okay
it's room sorry it was a second way to
issue that's time to implement in SSP
net so here as you can see within one
acceptance test we have done what we
have to do is in composition note of the
application I don't know what you want
to do well we have less than 10 minutes
I think what that part should be the one
that we will put into the setup of the
application so I can do that plug into
the webosphere but maybe it's better to
keep some time for questions or for kind
of wrap up what do you think okay
yeah otherwise I think I will have to
run because we kind of little bit late
yeah so wrap up we started from
situation like this we have a web ticket
manager with a very procedural code do
this and then do that and then do this
and and and after we lead to some more
consistent and more I don't know what to
say not shot yeah God walking code also
after the method was kind of something
like this thing is yes pretty much what
we achieved what's important is that we
embrace the language of our domain
within our code plus legacy code very
crappy and when we if we had time to
executor and append
we will have less warnings we just you
know in second just just in front yeah
so we are we walk code now it's talking
about reservations but trains reception
at term present which is fulfilled you
see so much even if all the way expect
is not able to read our code we can read
occurred in front of him and
being yeah being able to have a
discussion and he's being able to say no
no this is not what I want for for that
system star star so there is less
friction there is less gaps between what
we implemented what we was talking about
so it's better if you want to follow him
yeah we had some independent show it in
a few seconds but just before that no no
yeah that's because it takes time to
switch as a final wrap-up we did not
have to time to to make you feel that
because automate expertise in Paris and
our first version was with him on stage
but it's crucial to talk to your domain
experts yeah most of the project has
issue because the river are not even
allowed to able to talk to Dominic spats
so for me so no it's a no-go I finish I
decide not to go to the project if it's
like this but it wasn't the case at the
beginning of my career so takes yes it
takes courage time determination to
enforce that but it's crucial otherwise
yeah not as if they don't buy the legacy
because I'm a coach and I learn how to
refactor the code generate people when
there is dependencies said my code is
not testable actually we can test any
code any code so don't be daunted by it
I guess you may have some cost yeah it
cost I but it's doable yeah and also do
it's we don't use a lot of techniques
here we basically use two basic
techniques from the refactoring book of
nothing further
it's extract and move methods so it's
pretty much simple as soon as you have a
test Alice which is the first steps you
can extract and move very very easily
the more complicated is to find some
proper semantics and to and to invest in
your domain design they we have great
in track of improvement as you just said
by some of you yes this is something
that is a living and ensuring you have
yeah you have been very interactive user
so thank you very much
[Applause]