Thank you
I think my job today is to introduce to new ways of thinking the new concert so I thought I'd start you off with the picture
This is from when I finish work
Dismounting here
And is called tripping
About two or three people dying everyday
But if they don't take it seriously it's only just 3000 feet
But that's a territory I'm going to come back and reference that in a minute but that's kind like where I grew up that's what I feel at home
How much is another concept finding a country
Know what I want to do today is to introduce some new ways of thinking some new ideas to move things forward
I want to start off by some thoughts on language
Are you may or may not have grown up with Winnie the Pooh if you're British you did
And you find the Disney version quite a falling
But there's a whole set of structural throat which goes on on the web of people using Winnie the Pooh pictures
My favourite sayings
Have you look at both of these are right you have to be a Star Trek fan to understand the second
The reference to the episode of Monk and the use of metaphor
How we use very complex metaphors to explain various complex ideas in Simple Words
Also language change is very very quickly if you look at the left-hand one
It's almost getting out of date now because the level of stupidity is gone even before above that alright or below that
But the actual contacted I from the subtlety of all the messages and all the stories that lie behind it
Goes way beyond traditional methods of codification
So I can start think about language a bit and this goes back to a quote from the philosopher Martin heidegger
I'm sorry about this but when he was writing I should
I can't change his language to say woman and man or whatever but he basically said
Man thinks he's a master of language but actually language is the master of Man
And the important thing to realise is the language you speak
Largely determines how you see the world
Yeah I'm getting the language right is there for Keith
And it isn't just the fact that my first degree in physics and philosophy joint honours
Which give me a Desire for simplicity and purpose in beauty and lots of the stuff
And language is actually quite important
Now in order to fully understand this what I want to do
Is the comeback to
This particular picture
Yeah and start to think about a couple of things
Festival I want to make a distinction between sense making with a hyphen
And sensemaking as One World in the original
For those of you are familiar with calverts working if you haven't read that I recommend it
He talks about sensemaking
But it comes from an academic tradition where you study cases
I'm from cases you derive Theory you should all be better to be fully familiar with that
It's an empirical approach
Sensemaking which is myself climbing others comes from a different perspective
It says what do we know from natural science
And how do we apply natural science to human systems
And use that to create a different level of certainty
The reason we do that is natural science can replicate his experiments
Social science can't
And I'll come back and validate that in a minute just come make a background of the key distinction
The next key distinction I make which is not used to efficiently
It's between typologies and taxonomies
Data taxonomy people are familiar with we liked
Put things into categories
The problem is that in English taxonomy rhymes with taxidermy
And produces very similar results
Over rigid structures in which the boundary conditions become very dangerous
Because you make things fit into space even if they don't
I'm a typology on the other hand is a way of looking at things from different perspectives
At 9 going to be mainly today talking about typologies
Looking at things from different perspectives to actually make sense of the world
Rather try and create rigid plastic
Patience
And then we get into the stuff we were talking about in the bar last night
Which is the whole issue of Max
Models and frameworks
And he's often get conflated or confused
So I'll give you my basic distinctions at the moment yeah
A model seeks to represent the world
I'm going to come back later from a complexity perspective
And quote Murray gell-mann
The only valid model of a human system is the system itself
Nothing that starts to give us problems
A model seeks to represent the world and we see this a lot in systems architecture in elsewhere
And then people work within the model framework
But the trouble is there are limits to the application of models
It doesn't mean they're not useful but we need to
Be careful
A framework on the other hand is gently a typology
It's a way of looking at things from different perspectives so you can make distinctions
And therefore by those making distinctions do things in different ways
And then a map gives you somewhere placing yourself
Have understanding where you are
So this is the actual map of the area that you show the picture of earlier this is the Nutcracker
Ogwen Valley this ribbon
You can see a bit
Now that's a 1:25000 scale map
It's a really good planning map you're not going to make any major mistakes on that
That you can see the tracks you can see the contour lines
No most of us if we're walking there use Harvey maps
Which work on A12 40000 scale
If you actually look at that that's been designed very specifically for walkers
It's got much more detail on it you can actually see where there a cliff somewhere there aren't
The golden rule if you have a walk on different by the way it's if you get lost state of the crest
It may be scary but you won't die
If you try and take a short cut you'll die
I'm in total eclipse
And of course no matter how come anywhere with Maps you can make mistakes the danger with Maps as you become overconfident
We don't read them again we see forward
If I go back to Rafi this time last year I made exactly that mistake on the top of Tryfan
Out with that net result in its stitches
So Maps don't design that should never taken a selfie the family never forgave me for that
I said I realised it was bad I fell over on the top and I walked down the field I'll just take a picture before I wash my head in
Go and give a lecture at the university
And took the picture and realise oh my god I'm gonna have to go to hospital
And then the perfect sweet came to mind red Dawn on tripping so that kept me going to the bottom because I really wanted
The tweet with the picture
And shall we say cause some problems
The point is that Maps give you a starting point but you still got to be careful and familiarity breeds contempt
I'm trying to create some basic language at the moment
The other points in this is one of the biggest is.it with architekten elsewhere this is from an Pendleton Julian
A good friend of mine and she's currently actually just about to publish a new book with John CD Brown on design
Working with a Sonic impact the approach to design thinking with Stanford University
How to make him back that a bit later
She says and this is a critical point the whole point about scaffolding is you take it away when you've completed the building
Get the scaffolding isn't the Endpoint it's a means to an end
How many things I see far too much within the whole of the IT industry
Is a focus on scaffolding in the end
In fact often it's the way the truth and the life
Yep methods are elevated to the pub the level of religion
Yeah I need a allergy in terms of the way it works
Has somebody's just launched a new approach to business agility
And guess what the approach is a two-day course with a certificate at the end of it
That's a level of trivialisation we now getting to
So understanding that is key the other thing to realise
Is it there are no recipes
I'm going to justify this more as I come onto complexity
And I want to make a key distinction between a recipe book user and a chef
A recipe book user follow the recipe
If I have all the right equipment and all the right ingredients there's no problem it works
But if anything goes wrong
They haven't got the ability the resilience to adjust
A chef on the other hand
Can make a brilliant meal with whatever they have
Newham
And the reason is they have two types of knowledge would Aristotle called producers and Sophia
They have the theoretical knowledge of taste
And the practical knowledge about apprenticeship
And it's the combination of 4 or 5 years of apprenticeship
With deep
Theoretical knowledge about the nature of food
It's the combination which gives them resilient it's not one or the other
And at the moment we turn people to argue for theory or practice or practice of a theory
And that's a mistake we need to build more chefs and fuel recipe book uses
Do what I want to do is to go through three basic bits of Science and then start to apply them
First is the reality of the way that human beings perceive things
A second thing is how do we create novelty this is going to be really important
Because we try and remove accidents in system design
When acting in the history of evolution accidents of the most important thing
It's called serendipity if you want the English language word for it
I'll go through that again finally
We can't predict your model and that's what I introduce complexity theory and runs for the Canadian framework
For the first in terms of perception
And this experiment which is been repeated many times
If anybody comes to you and says I've done for a pi projects let me tell you from my experience this is what
What you should do
They really don't understand the Core Science
If they do three projects which partly succeed and create a worldwide method and accreditation scheme on it
And that's called snake oil salesman and charlatan
And there's a lot of them around at the moment
Fundamentally if you give it back of radiologists Now Remember radiologists are coming off of 45 generation body
Body of knowledge
This is important to realise architecture it's probably a 3 generation body of knowledge
Doctors are a 5000 generation body of knowledge
Let us more Generations build knowledge practice gets built into the processes the training
You got more reliability
That's a radiologist have a full five generation body of knowledge
Are dealing with the limited information set
Yeah in a controlled environment and most of them I got 10 or 15 years training
If you give them a batch of X-rays and ask them to look for anomalies
And I'm one of the x-rays you hide a picture of a gorilla which is 48 times the size of an average cancer nodule
83% don't see it
Even though the right physically scanner
We do not see
What we do not intend to see
We actually only see what we expect to see
And the scary thing is the 17% to do see it
Come to believe they were wrong
When they talk with the others
Alright now that one slide
Undermines any approach
Based on anybody observing what other
People do
Because if you're an academic or a consultant to you going steady companies
You only see what you expect to see
That's just life
It's called confirmation bias in attentional bias in Inception
Simon is being berating management textbooks most of this week
I'm quite pleased about this I normally the nasty going the internet is now becoming even nastier so that's good news
Antique at the think he's been generous I haven't yet seen a single popular management textbook
Which actually didn't Commit This fundamental error
Yeah they go and observe things interview people
They believe what people say when they're interviewed inform that they construct method
The good news on this is there's a huge amount there at to be discovered
If we architect systems in the right way
But we won't know
What we need until we discover it
Is the the second thing key aspects from evolutionary biology
This is called exaptation
I know we had a general problem with creationist will we still have a problem in the States
Which is growing right
We thought we'd eliminated that's everything and I think is now 52% of people in the United
2 States believe the world was created in the last 6000 years
Which is really scary
I'm doing work with your boner management teams in Dallas
And I was told I couldn't talk about creep about evolution because it's a controversial Theory
And that's it your boner management teams alright this gets really scary
Yeah but we did have a general problem with it because there isn't enough time in the evolutionary timescale
The human intelligence to have evolved
On a linear basis it just won't work
The other side of crude
Neo-darwinian night near darwinian ISM
A people like Richard Dawkins in the light
When is linear approach it's causal approach actually just doesn't work we got a problem
Then with Robin Hood linksmi Gorgon others we discovered a thing called acceptation
A2 illustration of that
Dinosaurs feathers evolved for warmth we can see it in the fossil record
It's over a long period of time
Yeah it's cold like
Dinosaurs with no feathers or warmer
Therefore they survive more to breed that's a classic adaptation linear process
And then by luck and it turns out the actual evolution isn't survival of the fittest it's survivor the luckiest
Something into that in Darwin's notebooks but he says this is too going too far so decide not to say it
Is that to be true
Amazon arboreal species of dinosaurs because it's cold at the top of tree so you get more feathers
But you also fall from trees
Which means you learn to fly
Actually flight is a nonlinear
Acceptation
A trait which evolved for one function and the stress
Exit through different functions
I couldn't handle anyway because if dinosaurs threw themselves off trees in the hope of evolving feathers before they hit the ground
The timescale for breeding is very short and the consequences are quite dangerous
I'm now course once you've got acceptation you get adaptation I was tracked by the bikes not so many months ago
Buy a tawny owl who actually literally followed me from mild and a bit of queues it was fascinating experience at dusk
And you can't hear an owl fly
Because of feathers have involved silence that's just literally can't hear them absolutely sign up
So after accepting you get adaptation
But the adaptation is based on where it started
There's any design in this the starting point determines the path way forwards
You should stop at the scene where I'm going with some of the stuff now
At the other one I love it's a cerebellum at the base of your brain evolved to manipulate muscles in fingers
It accepts in humans to manage the control of grammar in language
Sarah Hughes sophistication of human language
Was a radical repurposing not a linear adaptation
Have you don't think that's relevant
Then look at what connects
The Magneto of a radar machine
A Hershey bar
And a microwave oven
In 1945 a racing engineer
Maintaining the Magneto of a ride-on machine noticed that a chocolate bar melted in the pocket
Now
99 out of 100 engineers you notice this would swear and have their trousers cleaned
This guy realises significance
And we got microwave ovens
If you look at the history of technology
It's a history of x active moments a radical Republican
Some of the stuff I'll talk about in the strategy session with Simon later on this afternoon
Is if you look at it you get first mover advantage by repurposing existing technology
The novel purpose
IBM does it with punch cards
Microsoft does it with software developer IBM
An apple does it with next
After next went bankrupt
Get the radical evolution of a new apex predator
Is generally based on radical repurposing of an existing technology
Under conditions of stress
Who won the big things when they're starting to work on in terms of Architecture and design
Is how do you design for serendipity
Serendipity is a wonderful English word it comes from Earth
Ancient I think Italian story retold by Walpole
About the Two Princes Of serendip Who get sent on quests
And I never found what they were looking for
But they find more useful things instead
That and that's called serendipity
And reality is human invention human inside human understanding
Is generally accepted not additive
But that architectural structures tend to be drawn from engineering diagrams
Not from ecosystem
That's the big thing I'm going to start to argue for
Need to start to think about human systems is a complex psychology
Not a something which can be reduced to an engineering diagram
Because that reduces much of the Richmond
It's leads me onto complexity
I need a some of the most misuse words that we know about
Complexity zanotti problem and people use complex and complicated in the same way
And people make statements like they want to reduce complexity
And I'm sorry about this refugee speak about complex he doesn't fail
The nature of a complex system is it it always fails
No again
The failure is actually quite important to know come back and describe that
When you architect the complex system you design it for early failure
Big is only through of your failure could you discover what's possible anyway
So let me go through and build on this now build a canary in French
So basically we have three types of system in nature ordered systems complex systems and chaotic systems
Wrangler define these in terms of constraints
An audit system is highly constrained
There's very little degree of freedom is very little ability for anything to do anything outside
The rules
That you don't see these in nature by the way then work more less unique to human beings
An example I often give is an operating theatre
In an operating theatre we no count the number of surgical instruments left at the end of an operation
And jackets the same as were there at the start
Yeah as I get older I think this sort of stuff is of increasing importance
Yeah I know how many people had to have a second operation because surgical instruments will left in the body
That is actually over 10% on average across the world before the checklist were introduced
If you ever been into an operating theatre it's pretty goddamn messy it's easy to lose things alright
And the trouble is that losing things inside somebody's body
Has major consequences yes the order is good
But the cost of that is high
When a doctor or a nurse goes into an operating theatre anybody been into an operating theatre vertically
I've been in once horizontally in twice vertically alright and I almost got divorced I need to the vertical locations
Made my two children were both to quote William Shakespeare from their mother's womb untimely ripped
Said it was Cesarean section
The trouble is I grew up in a veterinary household with animals being detected on the kitchen table over breakfast
So from my point for your Cesarean section was a really interesting operation and can I look more closely
And I forgot that was meant to be there for the purposes
But either way if you go to into the operating theatre you go through some elaborate ritual of washing up
What that does
Is it's a ritual carpet of activation is what ritual does for humans
It aligns the individual
To the role that they are occupied
The reason you don't see what you don't expect to see is it best your scanning 3% of what's in front of you
And matching it against dominant patterns based on recent experience
What ritual does Easter change their patterns
So you see the world differently
When are playing with experiments for software testers
I'm getting them to change clothes before they pass their coat
Because you actually want me to have a different cognitive activation pattern
From me I develop this it's going to work
Into the side of testing and support type environments
Ritual is used extensively military Mart
So that's good
Valuable
The trouble is we then take it to excess
I work for IBM for 7 years
I hasten to add I was conscripted I didn't volunteer
It worked out quite well for me I'm still proud of the fact I didn't fill out a timesheet in 7 years that's a
World record breath
It takes a level of defiance which are here even I didn't think I was capable but I managed it
And I managed to avoid the school cross country run for 9 years so I think you know that was a slightly better achievement alright
Either way that took me more about bureaucracy than anything else I can remember
I said I take a survey we were in Anglo Dutch company called data Sciences we had a flat management hierarchy everybody
Can you everybody else
Can't we got things done
And then we became part of the world's largest
Bureaucracy
And the first thing they did was to charges for coffee and buying alcohol
Now this is completely unreasonable the alcohol coffee cycle
Is critical for good software development
Nobody should be expected to talk to users without alcohol first
You don't have to sober up to write the code and then you need even more alcohol
Because users never want what you can prove they asked for
When you give them the what they asked what they discover they wanted something else instead
I'm going to come back to that later because also I can text you it is about dealing with an articulated needs
Not articulated needs
That technology capability is progressing faster
Then uses know what to ask for
Yeah and I current models don't actually cope with it
We have to overcome this
I smuggle the alcohol I kept for my stuff out of the office one night
And then we have meetings in hotels which would charge of to meeting space and wouldn't mention the coffee in the alcohol
So that was fairly easy
I got worse
They banned us for buying food from staff
Anybody been in Widnes corporate environments
Yeah no food may be bought for staff it's a waste of money it's the improper reproach
Mama by now we've learnt you didn't argue with I being bureaucrats on an evidence base
From the perspective of customer or employee need that wouldn't work
The only thing which occasionally work was the Socratic technique if anybody knows their philosophy
It was Socrates did was to ask people questions until late or themselves apart on there own contradictions
It's an extremely enjoyable process you get train to do it in philosophy I enjoyed it thoroughly
But you always have to remember that eventually the people of Athens get together and decide they had enough for your corrupting the Young
And vote for you to take hemlock for right so you have to be careful on this one
Anyway so that's what we did
So we said ok this is a brilliant move we would never have thought of banning food for staff
This is one of the benefits of joining IBM
And then you realise because they look pleased that irony is a deadly weapon
You can switch on and off with HTML code here inside chats during conference calls
I'm so they actually think with we generally like this
I said I got a problem
Yeah I know I C level executives that means I only see customers when they're very very angry
The high you get promoted
The last chance you are of ever having a good relationship with a customer
Because you're the poor side gets thrown the problems when they finally stop trying to solve It For Themselves
And give up the right side in that position
I got called out it's 4 o'clock in the morning we got a Vax clusterdown
Yeah I got three sisters programmazione we've only got three three Sisters program is left in the entire company on the sent back to Gloucester
Define grateful we still got them
We got an emergency service which just has to be up at 9 a.m. in the morning
If we don't have it up we got massive penalty clauses anybody been there with one of those other things
I can't do anything at all technically anymore all I can do is get ready to deal with the customer
Stop other managers interfering with the technical people in fact that's my main role to give them the space
And buy them pizza and Coke so they stay awake so I can take what do I do if I have to buy them pizza and Co
It looked really worried and I realise they could have made a mistake so I said I did mean Coca-Cola
And there was another side relief but I must admit we did start the think about options there is Elstree
And they looked at me and I said well ok we understand that may occasionally necessary tell you what it will make an exception clause in the
The rules
If you get vice presidential approval 48 hours in advance
You can buy food for your staff
At this point you breathe deeply remember Socratic technique
You say god that's brilliant we really would never have thought of that and
No sarcasm get added to irony as a weapon
What happens on the extremely rare occasion
When we can't get 48 hours notice for major crisis
You can tell there is a chart
And they look worried about points and now you're the Socratic technique is working so they actually made another exception
Is it OK country general manager approval after the event
Now that is the classic bureaucrat response
I say yes in a way which means no
They really are very good at this
You know that means your expenses will disappear into the Southbank there'll never be signed
And if you complain about it your name will start to appear on the wrong list so right
You don't want to be on those lists out there bad places to be
So I gather because I would never do this you understand and nobody I know we're never do this but we did hear rumours about friends
Sending equipment ships remotes from our own business units who did this
Over tipping London taxi drivers
But if you ever tip a London taxi driver they give you a blank receipt
The blank receipt was then filled out for the amount of money spent on the pizza and Coke
A parallel set of books for cat so that you could say to the other people can prove
But they haven't wasted company money
And the responsible manager took a book bus and to actually playing for the taxi
That became widespread
I gave this example at the scrum Alliance conference in Berlin 2 years ago
Free people from IBM run up to me afterwards
And said we're still doing that did you invent it
And that's 15 years late
Last year in Dubai one of them came up and opened his wallet and showed me all the blackberries
Was collected in case you needed them
If you over constrained system which can't be naturally constrained
People work around it
And actually if that's a key issue in system design
People will work around the system they won't follow the pattern if it doesn't work for me
So there's nothing wrong with hardly constrained or they provide you don't take it to excess
The chaotic system
In my language is a system without constraints
All-rounder without effective constraints
That means there's no structure to it
Everything is random
At which actually means if it happens accidentally it's a major crisis but it will never last for long
If you can deliberately create the conditions you have a hugely powerful tool
Where can I get the working on North Korea
Where are we presenting infographics to tens of thousands of people
Getting in to interpret them in real time
Enjoying the Max from the interpretation so we can show out loud opinions dominant opinions and there is Ascot
The reason we can do that is there is no connection no constraint
Between any of the agents making a decision
Yeah if you can actually remove all constraints you can get radical innovation
So chaos as advantages
Protects a lot of energy
City creator
Most human systems are complex
That means they have what they call enabling constraints
And the whole point about a complex system
Is it it doesn't have linear causality
It has disposition at 8
It means I can make statements about how it's disposed to evolve
But I can never say if I do it it will always produce why result
Is sometimes known as the science of inherent uncertainty
Is the science of systems in which there is no linear relationship between cause and effect
All that we have is dispositional States
Not the key thing which goes with this is dependent on what type of system you're in you will manage in a different way
And
That's collector Corps concert for gonna move on to
If you're in a complex world
You have to manage by creating boundary conditions
Running experiments and responding to what happens
If you're in an audit system you can plan and design
And Chaos is something you can use
To get new insight but you want to invade
How to say engineering diagrams always assume order
The ecosystems.
And this is from Brian Arthur the first book complexity into economics
Rodger defining book corner
The evolution of technology
The trouble is that even scientists don't like complexity very much
Visit means you're dealing with systems Which have perpetual novelty
Get constant change
I sometimes use the metaphor as a children's party to illustrate this
Yeah you wouldn't manager children's party with key objectives targets mission goals project plans and milestones
Because everything would go wrong
You can see a more elaborate version of that on the web
That from that we get another couple of Simple Rules
If you want a very simple rule about when something is complex
If the evidence supports contradictory hypotheses
And you can't resolve the contradiction within the available time
Then it's complex
This is actually where we move into a massive new approach to conflict resolution
Because the whole point here is nobody is right or wrong
Because everything we do will change the system anyway
There's something which might have been right last time could be wrong this time
Anybody's managed to children's party
Yeah a football can catalyser good pattern the play
In the outdoors in summer
But you really don't want to bounce football in your living room in winter
Because the pattern the play will be radically different
The context of shifted
Yeah and damage will be massive
Yeah different things work well in different context
So basically
What we know stuff to do
Is we look at every coherent and coherence is a really important word in complexity
Camps and Philosophy of science
I can say that evolution is coherent to the fact even though we know it's wrong
Where's creationism is incoherent to the fact
It avoids that you were wrong therefore your hypothesis everything is a hypothesis
The issue is what's coherent the fact what incoherent to it
So we'll have to do is to agree your idea is coherent
I don't have to agree you're right in fact that can be pretty sure you're wrong but I agree
Your argument is coherent
At which point you get a small amount of resource
To run what's called the safety foil experiment
Been in the complex world you run small safe to fail experiments
Around every single coherent
Approach
And then you see what happens
And you stabilizer systems
You understand the complex system
By interacting with it
Not by analysing it
Or modelling it
I repeat that because it's key
You can't understand the Complex Adaptive system
Through modelling or analysis
You can only understand it by interaction
With real-time feedback loops
Over multiple agents
So you don't get cognitive bias
This is going like 101 science
And again that's going to change the way we design and work
The only thing I can say with absolute certain about a Complex Adaptive system
Is there ever I do will produce unintended consequences
If I show this in Australia everybody gets it straight away
And that's a cane toad
Introduced to reduce pest is now the dominant pest
Naturally that's important to realise it's alright
If you have a complex system and you intervene
The only thing I can guarantee you
Is it you'll have unintended consequences
That means you are ethically responsible for me
This is a big new thing on government
If you do a massive intervention and something happens you didn't expect
Oh sorry it's a complex system unexpected things were going to happen
It's your responsibility when they do
Which means you want to do small experiments in parallel much faster
So the bad unintended consequences you can destroy
And the good ones you can have T4
Is actually the unintended consequences will be the accepted moments
The discovery of novel ways of working
And that's actually quite important as what we all do
Save from net
We move onto the Canavan framework
And basically
At the camera framework by the way is not drawn like this
It's not drawn like this adding that later just to shut me up
Is actually John like this
No the whole body of theory behind this but basically you don't want a structured model
Canavan is a typology
And in full use the framework emerges from the data
The framework doesn't proceed the date
That's really important
If you give people a categorisation framework
Don't make things fit the framework
Even if they don't
It's the one you're working with sensemaking
You like the model boundaries to emerge from the data itself through Discovery process
And then you can use it and that's a really important distinction
The basically Canavan divided into 2
Spaces where
The relationship
Between cause and effect is obvious
Access example in civilised countries we drive on the left-hand side of the road
There's no particular reason for it I remember when Sweden was civilized until the 1960s
They had a national referendum where the people voted to stay civilised but the government have the sense to ignore the referendum
I'm talking about that example lot at the moment
Yeah and I moved over to driving on the right
Is that a universal I mean
Yeah you don't drive on the left
In the bin Sweden if a child runs on the road in the UK
If a child runs on the road in front of you drive anywhere to avoid them
So there is still exceptions evening rigidly constrained systems
Are there if you have a work Friday that was a bit different I remember
Something moved on the road in front of me in the middle of a Welsh Mountain Road and I stand the brakes on if you do
Discovered it was a sheet that the car was a write off and I phoned up car admin and they said next time kill the sheep pants
Still slightly worried about that one
Yes, had an overdose she put kids in till much later but never mind
I'm so basically and obviously mean we got it we can basically sense categorize respond
And we can apply best practice
Because there is one right way of doing things
Remember went to the complicated demand which is most engineering approaches set
That's actually where there is a relationship
Between cause and effect there is a right answer
Billy can only be discovered through analysis or by the deployment of the right type of expert
Get me can we do expertise as universal by the way
But at this point we can absolutely trust the expert decision
So basically at this point I sent
Amylose respond
And I apply good practice not best practice
Not going to argue at the moment
90% of systems architecture
90% of design sits in that domain
Busy assumption is there a right hand so we can discover it we can design for it that's it
I'll qualify that in a minute
We don't get if we over constrained system here
You get this catastrophic failure
Which is why chaos
Is a temporary space
And I get out of it by accident
Respond
The good news is
I get novelty
Is nothing like a crisis
To produce innovation
If I did a version is all about starvation pressure and perspective shift
If you look at it
Is when we can't use existing frameworks or existing ways of doing things
Then we get invented
Yeah that goes back to the cognitive entrainement patterns earlier
So basically you're saying that we get the complex to me
In the complex domain
What I actually do is
Probe
Sense respond
But I probe in parallel
Not in sync
That's really important
Because if I do one thing it will nearly always work
You know about the Hawthorne effect
Ok that that's
Cable manufacturers in New York State 1920 site of scientific management
Increase lighting levels and people became more productive that's good news
Pistes de with no publisher book
Cold Light
The secret to productivity
And have a certificate and training course based on how to switch on and off lights and change light bulbs
Then they had some pretension to be real scientist so they lowered the lighting level
People became more productive
What they actually found his people respond to novelty
Anything done which is new with attention will work the first time
It doesn't mean it will scale or repeat
Can you get somebody terrible management books that way one of my least favourite at the moment is lean startup if anybody's read that
Guy goes interviews people who know who's been successful as a whole body problems there because the way you remember things have your say
Successful
Is different from the way you remember them if you fail
And both of them are different from the way they actually happened for right so you can't just what people say
Another same time at the conference and did you study the companies who failed and he said no why would we do that
I said we did it when I was in IBM with Dorothy Leonard at Harvard Business School
We discovered all the companies have failed
Did exactly the same things as the companies who succeeded
Sjsu had a market
So a certain percentage would bound to succeed
And that's the trouble we got this very lightweight research throwing at simplistic recipes it's really dangerous
Here we go back to complexity I've tried Sainsbury's phone
And practice here will effectively be a merchant
I will always see a pattern
No important thing in the latest version I can have in call the liminal version
Looks like this
Secrets to liminal spaces
Illuminati is a really important concept in anthropology
And if you really want to understand humans go and do an answer
Topology course alright don't go on some cultural conversion course
Most anthropologists
No more about culture in the first year of studies
And cultural change consultants will now in their entire life Style
I basically liminality is a sense of transition if you put on a mask
Is a point where you start to become what the mask represents but there's a state of transition before you do it
Add a liminal concept in software design
Isobel actually not committing until you really have to
The longer you hold things in the state of transition the more options you've got
And actually in software development which is I know far better than architecture
This is actually where things like scrumpet
Because they are linear iterations based on a defined requirement with a degree of ambiguity
Therefore we're going to explore it
That's the trouble we eliminate ambiguity too early on
Big V12 restricted set to do linear experiments
In a mixed methods approach
What we start to do is to say and I use development that same as I know that better
Yeah there's nothing wrong with water for
Absolutely nothing wrong with Hardy structure processes you can use a togaf framework you can use rigid frameworks
You know exactly what you got to deliver you know the resource with an acceptable time friends why would you not take a waterfall approach
Am I working with telstra on this and telstra just gonna go
Therefore nobody got promoted unless they were Roger
So the waterfall guys rang one year sprint
So they could say they would really add you alright
That's what the thing is very very Common
Human beings a candy
You can't just the way the is language
I'm over here
One of the Big Things We Lost in architecture and I'll swear to concept
The time boxers
A2B got obsessed with two week time boxers
Certainly when I was involved in architect in last decision support systems
We will play around with three months
With a guaranteed delivery at the end of three months
But we very resource or weed very delivery
To meet the date
I actually gave us a lot of flexibility and definition phase and people looking like forgotten that stuff
Was it created the rights of the focus
Over here we're experimenting with radically different approaches and I'll just mention three of them
At this point
When is winter starting to look at an articulated needs
Before we even get
The design of any type
What we need to do is to surface the an articulated needs the things that people don't yet know they what they want
So when the ways we do that
Is we get people to interpret all of their technologies into Watts
Call obstruction metadata
We capture continuous narratives from users about day today for stations about their work
And then we merge the two databases together
Can we look at clusters
Abuser anecdotes with technology
Inside one of those come together
And that gives us novel ideas
He actually did this with Philips lighting
Yeah taking all of the technology capability customer stories
Putting the two together
Five clusters three of which became multi million dollar businesses
Is what you're doing is you're forcing accepted moments or insights
By moving up to a level of abstraction remember I started this on language
Ok if you don't know it we learn to paint
Before we learn to speak
Is a species
Art comes before language in human evolution
And it turns out that has major evolution invented you was an accident when it happened
Somebody sketch some pictures on a wall it can like work for the hunt
But then it started to really work
But if you move up a level of abstraction
You make connections in completely novel works
Engineers
Actually I musicians
Will tell you they have their best problem solving capability
When they play music
Art is critical to human invention
It's where the problem is Stem education is really scary
Because we reducing human beings down to the level of Aon
Hannah Stephanie doing this is about to start with University of California San Diego
And this is actually much more about infrastructure management
If you come to the university to do computing
You have to phone 0300 with somebody from the humanities and somebody from the pure sciences
When you're given pass by the University of Leeds 3 months
What we're doing is building across silent network of people who focus on a task
So that we can bring things together in novel unexpected ways
And a lot of this is about creating an architecture for Discovery
Raven trading architectures deliver
What people have asked for
Did you get the discovery architecture right
The recipe comes a lot easier
Because you got actually more structure in terms of the way you work
I could go on and that but there's a lot more material that was I can move onto
Keeping I want to finish office it's question and modelling
Are you a fine people in complexity Theory
This is what I call the computational complexity guys
My field is cool down through complexity
And the study of complexity in human system
The computational guys think everything is like blocking
Anyway but it's block around in sky schoolboys algorithm
It's follow the next bird max speed avoid collision
At that also works by the way if you want
To drive south of Naples in Italy
It's a much more effective heuristic than following the rules alright if you max speed avoid collision
Yeah and follow the next car you actually have a stressful driving experience even in Sorrento if you assume they follow the rules
Oh forget it alright
That's not the way it works
It will be in that human beings on hands
Because we haven't got see how you can predict
The entire complexity of the termites nest
Visit genetically encoded rules responding consistently to phone them stimulation
The human beings can see things through metaphors
We see things for abstraction
We can change identity overnight when I'm with my children I'm a completely different person than on stage
We don't have single agency we don't have single rules with complex pattern based creatures
So basically human beings on time
And that means you got a real problem with modelling
I gave the keynote of the European complexity conference all academics this Edward I speak about why you can't model of Complex Adaptive
I said no problem nobody told me the entire audience will be academics who built models
Yeah that would like Daniel going into the lines then that was when I met girl man he was the other here
And you can't challenge get on my knees when the world's most famous physicist
He backed me up and said you can't model the human system
The only valid model of human system is a system itself
A map to some extent is where we're starting to go but it's also part of the general concern
About an increase of artificial turf
Official intelligence
This is actually real problems anybody hasn't ready in M Banks books surface detail
I am back is a brilliant science fiction writer tragically died of cancer
Are you then propose to his long-term girlfriend by asking her if she would do the honour of becoming his widow
Is that sort of sense of humour alright
Read that and be terrified I've just been involved in a big think tank in California
General Hughes actor is actually as second most
Highest existential threat
The humanity after nuclear war
And ecological
Change is actually number for
When the reasons is with reducing human beings to information retrieval and process
Nai is better at that
And we won't go onto 101 machines and things like that
We need to be very careful about that because a human being is more than this
And then of course we get all the culture nonsense
Everybody wants to engineer if in doubt blame culture
If your pet project didn't work it was their fault
Because they have the wrong culture or the wrong mindset and this is
Appalling science
There is no such thing as a mindset
Is a complex set of interactions overtimes in a series of
The tropes
But it's not an individual mindset
You get people who will gather people stories that's good news we gather people stories
But we let
People interpret than themselves
We don't interpret them or let computers interpret them
Because that restricts us to text
And by the way you can write down
10% of what you know
Anything which is processing text
Is again dealing with a very very limited set
There's a power issue here as well
Who interprets people's narrative is there
This is from work with just doing with the BBC
Weather presenting cartoons
Employees are choosing cartoons which represent their culture
Interpreting those on the high abstraction metadata
I'm from that with an actually drawing a series of maps
How many reasons does we don't want to fall into one of these traps
Yep mansplaining postcolonialism
All that lovely one about the expert must be right
Ok
I'm giving you three illustration as there
If you really want to understand the human system
You got a hand over the power of interpretation
To the people themselves
Does it mean you don't have a room for experts
We got to distribute the property function you can't tell that centrally
Save from net
That allows us to do some very interest
This example is a dispositional map
And this is actually where we are starting to go with systems architecture
Bolsover things like kanban
So if you look at categories and kanban
Ok the key Concepts and kanban is working progress
Yeah not the representation of those who hear the advocaat she would think it was all about Post-it notes moving between columns
Key Concepts is working progress
In an audit system work in progress is a series of discrete job unit
The kanban Works
In a complex system is a series of unrealised
Potentialities
So the representation has to change
This is actually a landscape drawing from mass observation self interpretation of the point of origin
Anything actually cultural change map so if I actually want to change culture on this one
If my desires Stacey's appear
You can see I've got some things up there sexy
What's a tick in the box
This is very very negative
To move them up there is a Step Too Far
What I do instead is I look at this
And I say what can I do tomorrow
To create more like these
If you would like those
What I'm doing this is a key principle of complex design
Is an shift in the system to an adjacent possible
And once I get enough stability at that point
I can use more conventional approaches
This is what I'm talking about about architect into under the discovery
Before you architect for delivery
Did you actually start with the start with delivery
You miss the discovery phase
Are you going to miss opportunities as well as threats
That's actually from a hospital
Autolyse answer key Concepts call fractal engagement
So the same data can produce frameworks at the level of responsibility of every individual
And again I haven't got time to go into this I'll go to this in the strategy session
Fractal engagement is the way we actually achieve change
People don't make decisions about what other people should do
They make decisions about what they can do tomorrow within their own sphere of competence
Then the system as a whole torrent extra multiple actions
That's a big concept by just hinting at it now
And I thought we call fractal change
EBay
It's all about multiple perspectives
This is actually from again this is work on the whole variety.
This is Peace and Conflict resolution
What we doing here is present in an infographic and when are doing this in system design Discovery architecture
Representing infographics about where we think we should be
We're getting every employee to interpret that
Enjoying the max of the interpretation before anybody talks to anybody else
In that space is actually from Columbia this is
Yeah big one
You can see that blue and green see the same data in such radically different ways
Sitting down to talk to each other is a waste of time
The only thing they both agree on his they hate the red guys
Get the strategy here
Is there actually make these more extreme
Will it be getting new consensus in the middle
The other reason we do this is I want to find outliers
Agama talk about Discovery architecture
I want to see groups of people were seeing the world differently from everybody else
Because those are the things the 17%
Who seen the Cancer nodule
Rob and people were going with orthodoxy so again that's the concept of Discovery architecture
RAM delivery architect
And the final slide finish off on this How You scale a complex system
Again this is a big field but the one thing you don't do is you never scale the complex adaptor
The system
By aggregation or imitation
You don't take everything and aggregated up into some massive diagram
And you don't say that worked will do more of it
What do you actually doing to decompose things and there's a whole body working on this by the way an object orientation
Remember to going back to at the moment
You decompose things to the lowest coherent object
You define protocols for the interactions be
Between the objects
Annual animal patterns to emergency stimulator system
So you staying but scale by decomposition and recombination
Not by aggregation
And not bite imitation
Have a challenge for design the Challenge for architecture
Is the move much further back in the cycle
Video with an articulated knees
To discover on an objective basis
Novel possibilities unexpected consequences
Andy bell systems with the responsive capability
To exploit opportunities as they present themselves
Before they're fully now
In order to do that we need to have a sound understanding of the science
Behind human cognition
And the science behind system
Is under conditions of extreme uncertainty
Falling back for the constraints of natural science gives us security
Falling back to empirical past memories of what work before
Makes it very very random
Thank you very much for your time