yeah maybe we can have a tiny part
about aggregates yeah so just a tiny
part about aggregates. Aggregates is a
collection of objects which is entity and value types
treated as a conceptual whole. Can
you see some aggregates in here
train? yeah. Is coach an aggregate? no.
why is that?[Audience]yeah some aggregates mayby immutable.
Actually it's
no because aggregates need invariants,
need business rules need something to to
to to
yeah to be enforced I would say. And here
the only variants we have is train level.
they must not exceed 70 percent of the
train tickets limited which is the business I
own and the coach aggregates as to as
to to enforced when we discuss with the
domain expert he told us that he
wanted to add some new rules related to the coach.
so that coach must not be
fulfilled also at must not be exceed
given capacity so in that case it will
turn into an aggregate voice maybe it's
a kind of detail. But something
interesting. Train, coach and seat may
all be value types here. as we discuss
earlier if we think about the way we
interact with the external backend we
get a kind of snapshot valid from a
moment of time and we will work on that
snapshot. so we don't want to keep it in
cache. We just want to work with all those
aggregates. fine cells so to enforce that
we can make it all value types. actually
in the long term Russian we that's what
we did
so that means that some aggregates may
be completely value types also.[Audience] yeah the
trend here it most of the case it's like
this message was to it was one
case where we could have this exception [Audience]
if we have a level-two Business School
to be enforced at the coach level it.
Yeah, in the long version we do that. So so far we
improved somehow the web ticket manager
and the before it was a free screen
high, full of legacy code with lots
of legacy stuff yeah. I think we have
kind of improved a little bit it's one
screen high. It's using the word of the
domain within the code what we call
ubiquitous language. we extract some
behaviors and we put them into the proper
locations, but there is still something
that botheres us. someone has told it
before this is that we have some Json
design into the domain method
and we still have our Task of strings
which is also a jism. yeah what we would
like to do here is to get rid of that
design, and stuff and to replace it by
reserve. sorry, reservation. So
that the Reserve method will return a
reservation. then on the infrastructure side
side and we will transform
the Reservation into a json version,
if we have an adapter if we have
something pluggable. okay so I
suggest I will talk a little bit about
the second equation which slide. I'm
sorry
I will work on the code you
don't see. but it will explain when we
get back to the code and like an
architecture we explain what we have done.
okay
so who is aware of what hexagonal architecture is?
okay cool what hexagonal
architecture pattern is made
by Alistair Cockburn.
I can't remember, the long time ago.
and it has many benefits. it's a pattern
at the architectural level it's known as to
embrace change it was the first idea of
Alistair was to plug and unplug external
dependencies plug and unplug stuff he
was talking about whether system able to
to be plugged with many different
standards as input and many different
stutters as output to broadcast news to
broadcast to TV to radio to whatever.
so it was kind of to have
of clean code inside and every changes
in terms of i/o or way to interact with
the system to be a non-event to be
something like you plug a plug in and
you can plug a plug in and that's it so
it's it's come with it was introduced by
that idea in mind but when we think
about it, it may allow us that we want to
first on the domain to make some code
more value, business value inside to
protect our domain code from the
technical stuff. I don't know for you but
during long time I thought it was not
even possible to properly split between
domain logic and and technical. We
tried many times that we failed a lot and
seems I discovered that pattern.
it's really a nice way to and for that
and I also want to enforce testability because
since everything is a pluggable and
We can stub, we can mock, we can
stub the input output of the
systems, business logic inside and so for
today we will focus much more the how to
protect our domain code. So how does it work?
It works
considering the world in two different
area there is inside and there is
outside
simple, right? No thousands of layers, no...
simply two area, the inside is a domain
it's your domain code like
method like the train, the
reservationAttempt, the stuff like that
and the infrastructure code is at the
outside of your system. So this
is where you will find your favorite
HTTP stack,
your database drivers, your
message middleware, your favorite solution.
or whatever. This is
infrastructure side, code. which I've got
and what we want is to first
improve the domain code so we have
diversity she is some kind of putting
some  barriers around your domain code and
defining some entry points to enter and
to leave the the domain code. So you keep
the infrasturcture code at the other
side. This is a nice capability actually
because I don't know for you but when
you start your career as a developer you
need to improve your skills, you need to
discover new thing you need to do lot
of mistakes you need to implement you
own framework in order to realize
at one point that there are some silly
stuff like implementing your framework
stuff like that. But before you focus on
the domain really, it's still important
for some new young developers to be able
to play in a kind of playground. I'm
okay with that
as much as it does not jeopardize the
business value and the project and in
that case I'm happy with that because
there is a kind of location where you
can play. It's a playground your infrastructure
code. You can try new technology new
stuffs without jeopardizing
the domain code. So this is what I really
like in that pattern. So how does
it work, because there are barriers
but I need to enter and to leave the
building, I would say that, to leave the
domain code. So to do so in terms of
dependencies, all dependencies are
towards inside. believes the
infrastructure code is aware of
reference of domain code, but of course the
domain code should not be aware to any
framework. Even Jesus stuff. It seemed
like that so the domain is completely
independent from any kind of technology
even Json string or thing like that. So
to allow us to move from the
inside to the outside to ask new thing
to talk with external web api and do
some stuff, we will rely on ports and
adapters. And to do so we are actually
using
inversion dependency principle, so that
from the inside we can go outside and do
some stuff. Alistair Cockbrun recently
discussed with an another guy I can't
remember the name and that was
suggesting the name of configurable
dependencies. What Alistair was saying is
dependency injection principle I don't
really like because this is like if
negative way of formulating things. It's
you used to do that do the other way
around do the inverse so he was trying
to find a much more fluent intention way
of saying that, so they lead to
configurable dependencies so you plug
and unplug your dependencies around your main.
So if we get back to a case
here we say we have ports and adapter
to enter and to leave the domain. So
ports belongs to the domain and there
are some interfaces like lollipops here
so here I've got the IReserveSeats which
is the entry point from the
tata system. so I had through an
adapter HTTP adapter IP dot net callback
I must call an interface which is a port
I have another seat, say please reserve
me something and I get a
reservation and that adapter will do the
rotation between the reservation and the
Json version because the Json that so it
will be the proper location to do so
when I need to form a business rule
when I need some extra data some extra
thing if not provided by everything I
need from the beginning there are many
ways to do that but if let say I need to
ask one of the external
SSL dependency you know the three web
api we call during the process, we need
to access, we need to add something to
the outside, so to do so we asked some
ports also made from the inside there is
IBookSeats interface there is IProvideTrainTopology
interface and there is
IGetBookingRef interface. these
are domain interface
the port still
belongs to the domain reason why the
lollipop is in blue
but the adapter is what belongs to infrastructure
so basically adapter is something that
maps between the infrastructure code to
the domain one and vice-versa. Is that OK for
all of you? yeah? we'll see that in
the code in a few minutes. so port and
adapter to go in and to go out. easy, right? okay
but when we try to implement it the
first time there's tons of question that
arouse and there are many ways to
do so. We'll show you one. we have to
initialize we have to init to initiate
you are to build you
have to build the stuff so I like I've
got a metaphor which is a key ring
metaphor to explain that to my
mate I try to explain to you. First step,
its we will talk here about the
composition of utopian application, you
know, the place on your application
where you build all your dependencies
and then voila apply the system is able
to work and to do is work okay so we're
talking about the bootstrap of your
application here so three steps first
step is to instantiate I need to go out
adapters. All the adapters go to ask
to the SSL back-end "please give me a
topology please
so here represented twp Train Data Service Adapter
and Booking Reference Service Adapter
adapter these are like keys to go
outside and to ask stuff, so the first step
is access those keys. Then second step
is I've got those keys, I wrapped them
with
hexagon, with the domain. the hexagon is
where the domain stay so it's a web ticket manager.
So the web ticket manager
will receive within its console ports
interface to interact with the
outside world and then we instantiate we
wrapped the hexagon with a new
adapter which will be the adapter to be
used in order to
interact with our system so it's "I need to enter" adapters
that it's the way to
communicate with our application, but
once we do that all we have to keep in
our hand from an application perspective
from the asp.net Web API perspective all
I have to keep in my hand will be the entrypoint adapter
so all the rest of the hexagon
and adapters it's an implementation
details once I've built the place all I
have to keep from our Web API
perspective is that adapter which is the
entry point from a formal system. okay? to
put it differently those three steps
looking at them in the diagram. First we instantiate
the adapter we need to go out, so
the three back ends then we wrap
them with hexagon
whereas domain logic stands and then we
wrap that domain logic it's like Russian
doll you know I need to go out the hexagon I need to go in and at the end of
the day all you keep in your hands - I
need to go in. This is the only thing
that you need to interact with
system from application perspective
so all you keep in your line will be
only that adapter that you will inject
into your callback I speed up the
corners and stuff like that. okay? sure
you have some question we will call it
or hope you will have some questions. so
just to have a look on the new version
you can notice now we have a reservation
and the modification has been to call a
confirm because after this line I know
there is no exception and I can return
the reservation. so the did, the
modification of the test is there, yeah, we
returned a reservation and I already
create a beginning of adapter, the output
adapter with AdaptReservation.
This function will be called by Thomas in
a few minutes, so you start to move
the technical json implementation to the
proper place. exactly. okay. what I suggest
is to for me to to reduce in that first
acceptance test what I will have to do
into my bootstrap my composition route
okay, so first one is to step one is to
instantiate "I want to go out" adapter. so
here trainDataService for instance we
can even rename it to trainDataServicesAdapter.
it's a bad name, it's still the
service. that's obviously I was there
it's a proxy too. and same thing for
that bookingReferenceServiceAdapter. okay, step one I instantiate
the dependencies I need to go to the
outside world
yeah? all right, then what I need is to
instantiate the hexagon. actually so the
exact on here is a web ticket manager. so
let's call it hexagon only here for
pedagogical school perspective over your
life you don't you will call it with a
business name so please don't tell Eric
that we did that but just it's to focus
on the hexagon and infrastructure here.
it's better for me to rename it hexagon
here and then instead of
calling directly the hexagon
all I have said before is the
application we would have to interact
with my business logic through an
adapter yeah
so let's introduce it. yeah, step 3
instantiate "I want to go in" adaptor, so
here but I can do is to how can we
generation oh yeah you already
came same name, so I will
instantiate it providing what should I
provide. okay I think I got a sense like
Russian dolls so those two first we are
providing to the hexagon here and the
hexagon is provided to the
guy. okay so I create a constructor
because so far you just had made a
static functions. okay maybe you have to
make that abstraction
not to inject what ticket manager yes
actually yes you're right, we talked
about personnel at the ports are like
interfaces so what I can do maybe is on
the web ticket manager here it's
introducing its we changed after so
let's create an interface for that and
let's say I reserve seats, something like that? em...
Sorry, I used to work on the Mac,
so we try to pick a keyboard
IReserveSeats
you work every day on the PC
yes, but not the same keyboard  I tried to find
exeucise, stress yeah so I asked I add
the reserve method on that interface.
here this is a port this is a port in
order to enter the hexagon
so getting back to the code here
what I will provide to the external
adapter it will be the hexagon but as
oops, go to implementation as charlie
reserved seats yeah IReserveSeat.
okay let me keep it into a private field
here I will need it. so I start set a
reservation adapter okay so third step to
associate other nationality let's
introduce a variable for that with our
instance okay my idea will be to replace
the direct call to the hexagon by
something going through the adapter you
know. so just to make it compile I will
go to the controller to web controller
which is the place where I will use that
exact same adapter so in that controller
here I will need to my entry point will
be together reservation request dto so I
will get a reservation request dto
give it to the adapter and the adapter
will get back to me with a Json
relating to the reservation okay? so to
do so I think the reservation dto is not
in the proper place. I won't be able to
access it from the from the test. So
I suggest that we move that and maybe it
will be no envision is quite painful to
create project it's long so I will just
create a directory here. I will create
Train Train domain all right and
infra
so that we can start to split infra
(infrastructure) and so that we
can we are able to speak properly every
type into the proper location. I'd moved
typed into matching files for be sure
that every file match to type so
BookingReferenceService where should I put
domain or infra
service. it's a bad name, the
name will be different but yeah coach
domain yeah IBookingReferenceService
yeah it's an interface so it's a port
yeah actually here so domain yeah. IReservedSeats?
port, so the domain, yeah
ITrainDataservice, its names but
it's a domain is it okay its interface
yeah reservation domain, right?
reserved I shall attempt same
reservation hotel for you , same
reservationFailure also it's a
domain.
actually it's much more something to
implement the biggest law where there is
no added value more than twelve toppling
seats? domain. I'm kind of happy
because you have more domains than the
infrastructur which is not the case in
all my projects so far so SeatJsonPoco
SeatsReservationAdapter? infrastructure, yeah
ThreadsholdTrainCapacity? domain, absolutely even if we
came in through the name. Train? is it
domain and what do we have? TimeDataSservice,
of course which is another time
and WebTicketManager, domain. it's
all exactly but so far it's seen as some
to HTTP rationale that we get rid no
it's okay so let's put it to the... let's
keep it in the middle
let's keep it into the middle before we
completely clean the house and put it in
adjust the namespace
sorry I just enhancement yeah I would
adjust the namespace here for the project.
so that everyone would be at
the proper location okay. so what I was
saying is I will from the should TrainTrainShould
getting back to the test
okay
I said that I would like to introduce a
way to interact with the ReservationAdapter,
so let's say it's a Post dto.
there is a better name to
find but new reservation request
diffuses I don't know if you you move it
I don't know I didn't move thanks below
so ReservationRequestDto I
have to move is it's on the bad project.
move to folder... TrainTrain infra
so now I will be able to reference it
from the test, otherwise it will be part
of the Web API which has no reference so
far okay. so we here I will instantiate a
new reservation request dto. This is ASP.net
which used to instantiate
that for me but our number_of_seats here
will be seatsRequestedCount and
the other train_id
setting the
equivalent of the Json we receive as
the input
it's a poco for it will be
TraineId. here is my train
yeah okay so here I post a new
request dto, maybe this thing's, let's
make it a variable, to make it clean so I've
got a reservationRequestDto and then I
pass the reservation request to the adapter yeah,
I want to go into adapter. create method okay create the
method and instead of returning void I
will return maybe a string which will be
the Json. Here I can
return something much more like asp.net
internal structure to make a
response but I won't go into that here
but as I rationalize it you okay
so here I am in the posts method yeah
that should return me a jsonReservation.
something like that
why not
yeah so the adapter will return me that
and I will assert on that yeah so
instead of all that
jsonReservation should be equal to
that Json. that objective to target you
know that yeah so it's still right
because I didn't plug the adapter. so
adapter has three steps to
instantiate the entire hexagon structure
but when I mean every method of the
adapter has three steps basically its
first step is to adapt from their infrastructure
to the domain
second step is to call the business
logic and then the third step is to
adapt from domain answer to the
infrastructure and to return it. yeah you
know what is it about in every method of
adapter so let's make it here, in that
case I don't have to adapt
here so I will just introduce a new
variable
for the number_of_seats and with a
machine liquid in the real life
maybe you you have to serialize yourself
and we simulate this tech because asp.net
do that for us but sometimes
you have to translate the Json in
local variable for a domain object. so here
what I just did is to get some variables
but this is where you will have to
translate transform adjust whatever it
takes to be able to call the
domain logic. yeah Good. so now I call the
hexagon so hexagon.Reserve, it's
a business domain method and I put it
to put it local variable I get and numberOfSeats
number of let me call me
requested okay I called the hexagon,
its return me reservation, since it is a method a
yeah
so has a ration but since it's an async
method I will have to await that and
truth sorry some like that c# to
obtain the sequence call. but since your
method is I think because it's called
also async method I asked you to do so
and then adapt from domain to this is a
method Bruno already done we had adapter
adapter damage sure I provide a
reservation and I get some string and
yeah I guess, to return. you see I get a
reservation from the business logic and
then what I do is to adapt back from
the domain to the json infrastructure. this
is still red what did I miss
[Music]
you have to await also because
of a weight this is Mexican Russian okay
it's green sorry it was async/await
issue. that's time to implement in SSP
net. so here as you can see within one
acceptance test we have done what we
have to do is in composition note of the
application I don't know what you want
to do, well, we have less than 10 minutes
I think what that parts should be the one
that we will put into the setup of the
application so I can do that plug into
the webosphere but maybe it's better to
keep some time for questions or for kind
of wrap up, what do you think? okay
yeah otherwise I think I will have to
run because we kind of little bit late
yeah so wrap up, we started from
situation like this we have a web ticket
manager with a very procedural code do
this and after we lead to some more
consistent and more, I don't know what to
say, short working code also
after Reserve method was kind of something
like this. thing is yes pretty much what
we achieved what's important is that we
embrace the language of our domain
within our code plus legacy code very
crappy and when we if we had time to
executor and append
we will have less warnings we just you
know in second just just in front yeah
so we are talking
about reservations, trains reception
at term present which is fulfilled you
see so much, even if our domain experts
is not able to read our code we can read
in front of him and
being, yeah, being able to have a
discussion and he's being able to say no
no this is not what I want for that
system. so there is less
friction there is less gaps between what
we implemented what we was talking about.
so it's better if you want to follow him
yeah we had some called ndependent show it in
a few seconds, but just before that
yeah that's because it takes time to
switch as a final wrap-up we did not
have to time to to make you feel that
because automate expertise in Paris and
our first version was with him on stage
but it's crucial to talk to your domain
experts yeah most of the project has
issue because the developers are not even
allowed to talk to domain experts.
so for me so no it's a no-go I finish I
decide not to go to the project if it's
like this, but it wasn't the case at the
beginning of my career so takes yes it
takes courage time determination to
enforce that. but it's crucial otherwise
yeah not as if they don't buy the legacy
because I'm a coach and I learn how to
refactor the code generate people when
there is dependencies said my code is
not testable actually we can test any
code any code so don't be daunted by it
I guess you may have some gut to do so yeah it
cost I but it's doable yeah and also
it's we don't use a lot of techniques
here we basically use two basic
techniques from the refactoring book of
Martin Fowler
it's extract and move methods so it's
pretty much simple as soon as you have a
test Alice which is the first steps you
can extract and move very very easily
the more complicated is to find some
proper semantics and to and to invest in
your domain design they we have great
in track of improvement as you just said
by some of you. yes this is something
that is a living and ensuring you have
yeah you have been very interactive user
so thank you very much
[Applause]